{"Question": "DAD + ODDS = SOON", "Answer": "565 + 1552 = 2117"}
{"Question": "EYE + BEER = APPLY", "Answer": "525 + 9557 = 10082"}
{"Question": "EYE + BEER = ARAB", "Answer": "636 + 8662 = 9298"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODDS = LABEL", "Answer": "606 + 9665 = 10271"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODDS = AFTER", "Answer": "616 + 9667 = 10283"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODDS = ABUSE", "Answer": "616 + 9668 = 10284"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODDS = PIANO", "Answer": "626 + 9663 = 10289"}
{"Question": "EYE + TEEN = MONTH", "Answer": "636 + 9662 = 10298"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODDS = CHEEK", "Answer": "676 + 9662 = 10338"}
{"Question": "EYE + DEEP = RAPID", "Answer": "686 + 9663 = 10349"}
{"Question": "EYE + SEED = EASY", "Answer": "797 + 6772 = 7569"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODDS = LEVEL", "Answer": "727 + 9774 = 10501"}
{"Question": "EYE + TEEN = LIMIT", "Answer": "737 + 9772 = 10509"}
{"Question": "EYE + NEED = ASIAN", "Answer": "747 + 9772 = 10519"}
{"Question": "EYE + BEER = CLIMB", "Answer": "767 + 9772 = 10539"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODDS = HELLO", "Answer": "787 + 9772 = 10559"}
{"Question": "EYE + BEER = DIRTY", "Answer": "858 + 9887 = 10745"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODDS = LEAVE", "Answer": "878 + 9882 = 10760"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODDS = CHASE", "Answer": "878 + 9886 = 10764"}
{"Question": "TOO + TOOL = BIBLE", "Answer": "922 + 9224 = 10146"}
{"Question": "TOO + TOOL = ADAPT", "Answer": "922 + 9227 = 10149"}
{"Question": "ALL + ALLY = YEAH", "Answer": "733 + 7338 = 8071"}
{"Question": "SEE + SEEK = WORKS", "Answer": "933 + 9336 = 10269"}
{"Question": "ODD + ODDS = ELITE", "Answer": "933 + 9338 = 10271"}
{"Question": "ALL + ALLY = EXTRA", "Answer": "944 + 9445 = 10389"}
{"Question": "ODD + ODDS = PRIOR", "Answer": "944 + 9446 = 10390"}
{"Question": "ALL + ALLY = TREAT", "Answer": "944 + 9447 = 10391"}
{"Question": "ALL + ALLY = BREAD", "Answer": "944 + 9448 = 10392"}
{"Question": "ODD + ODDS = DESK", "Answer": "677 + 6775 = 7452"}
{"Question": "FEE + FEAR = APART", "Answer": "922 + 9213 = 10135"}
{"Question": "TOO + TOUR = APART", "Answer": "922 + 9257 = 10179"}
{"Question": "ALL + ALSO = TOTAL", "Answer": "922 + 9270 = 10192"}
{"Question": "THE + TEEN = FIFTH", "Answer": "972 + 9225 = 10197"}
{"Question": "SEE + SELF = FINAL", "Answer": "933 + 9341 = 10274"}
{"Question": "SEE + SELF = AWFUL", "Answer": "933 + 9352 = 10285"}
{"Question": "THE + TEEN = NORTH", "Answer": "954 + 9441 = 10395"}
{"Question": "TOO + TOWN = ONTO", "Answer": "455 + 4590 = 5045"}
{"Question": "DIE + DEER = TIRED", "Answer": "905 + 9554 = 10459"}
{"Question": "SEE + SELF = IRAQI", "Answer": "955 + 9526 = 10481"}
{"Question": "ALL + ALSO = ENJOY", "Answer": "955 + 9528 = 10483"}
{"Question": "CEO + COOK = DANCE", "Answer": "935 + 9558 = 10493"}
{"Question": "DIE + DEER = PRIDE", "Answer": "945 + 9550 = 10495"}
{"Question": "FEE + FEAR = PARTY", "Answer": "977 + 9706 = 10683"}
{"Question": "CEO + COOK = FENCE", "Answer": "908 + 9882 = 10790"}
{"Question": "TOE + TEEN = MONTH", "Answer": "908 + 9887 = 10795"}
{"Question": "TOO + ROOT = WHERE", "Answer": "844 + 9448 = 10292"}
{"Question": "TOO + BOOT = TEEN", "Answer": "455 + 3554 = 4009"}
{"Question": "FEE + DEER = AWARD", "Answer": "833 + 9336 = 10169"}
{"Question": "TOO + LOOK = APPLE", "Answer": "644 + 9448 = 10092"}
{"Question": "FEE + PEER = ADAPT", "Answer": "744 + 9448 = 10192"}
{"Question": "FEE + TEEN = CRAFT", "Answer": "844 + 9445 = 10289"}
{"Question": "TOO + COOK = FENCE", "Answer": "844 + 9446 = 10290"}
{"Question": "FEE + HEEL = TIGHT", "Answer": "844 + 9447 = 10291"}
{"Question": "TOO + COOL = LIMIT", "Answer": "655 + 9551 = 10206"}
{"Question": "ADD + ODDS = SOON", "Answer": "566 + 2663 = 3229"}
{"Question": "FEE + HEEL = ALLY", "Answer": "566 + 3662 = 4228"}
{"Question": "FEE + SEED = ODDS", "Answer": "566 + 8662 = 9228"}
{"Question": "SEE + FEEL = SELF", "Answer": "966 + 8662 = 9628"}
{"Question": "FEE + BEER = CARRY", "Answer": "566 + 9662 = 10228"}
{"Question": "ADD + ODDS = ALSO", "Answer": "377 + 2775 = 3152"}
{"Question": "SEE + HEEL = SELF", "Answer": "977 + 8775 = 9752"}
{"Question": "ILL + ALLY = ERROR", "Answer": "277 + 9773 = 10050"}
{"Question": "FEE + BEER = STAFF", "Answer": "577 + 9778 = 10355"}
{"Question": "TOO + NONE = QUIET", "Answer": "744 + 9493 = 10237"}
{"Question": "TOO + NONE = ONTO", "Answer": "955 + 4540 = 5495"}
{"Question": "DAD + AIDE = IDEA", "Answer": "585 + 8953 = 9538"}
{"Question": "TOO + NONE = ADMIT", "Answer": "755 + 9592 = 10347"}
{"Question": "TOO + NONE = GREEN", "Answer": "855 + 9594 = 10449"}
{"Question": "DAD + AIDE = DEEP", "Answer": "656 + 5461 = 6117"}
{"Question": "DAD + AIDE = THEIR", "Answer": "696 + 9562 = 10258"}
{"Question": "TOO + NONE = CLEAN", "Answer": "477 + 9792 = 10269"}
{"Question": "ETC + TREE = CHART", "Answer": "891 + 9788 = 10679"}
{"Question": "LET + TELL = ELSE", "Answer": "198 + 8911 = 9109"}
{"Question": "LET + TELL = LAKE", "Answer": "473 + 3744 = 4217"}
{"Question": "SEE + TEST = STAR", "Answer": "288 + 1821 = 2109"}
{"Question": "DAD + FADE = BUYER", "Answer": "484 + 9842 = 10326"}
{"Question": "LET + BELL = TASTE", "Answer": "561 + 9655 = 10216"}
{"Question": "DAD + FADE = SHELF", "Answer": "585 + 9854 = 10439"}
{"Question": "DAD + LADY = EXTRA", "Answer": "686 + 9862 = 10548"}
{"Question": "LET + HELL = CATCH", "Answer": "742 + 9477 = 10219"}
{"Question": "POP + ROPE = EAGER", "Answer": "838 + 9381 = 10219"}
{"Question": "EYE + FREE = ROOF", "Answer": "383 + 6733 = 7116"}
{"Question": "EYE + FREE = ALLY", "Answer": "484 + 5744 = 6228"}
{"Question": "SEE + GENE = SOON", "Answer": "744 + 6484 = 7228"}
{"Question": "EYE + TREE = FIFTH", "Answer": "454 + 9744 = 10198"}
{"Question": "EYE + FLEE = CARRY", "Answer": "484 + 9744 = 10228"}
{"Question": "FEE + HERE = BRIEF", "Answer": "844 + 9404 = 10248"}
{"Question": "EYE + FLEE = CIVIL", "Answer": "464 + 9844 = 10308"}
{"Question": "EYE + FREE = START", "Answer": "525 + 9855 = 10380"}
{"Question": "FEE + MERE = IRISH", "Answer": "566 + 9606 = 10172"}
{"Question": "EYE + FLEE = YOUNG", "Answer": "616 + 9766 = 10382"}
{"Question": "EYE + FREE = YOURS", "Answer": "616 + 9866 = 10482"}
{"Question": "SEE + HERE = RUSH", "Answer": "377 + 4757 = 5134"}
{"Question": "EYE + FREE = RELY", "Answer": "747 + 8977 = 9724"}
{"Question": "EYE + FLEE = APPLY", "Answer": "747 + 9277 = 10024"}
{"Question": "EYE + FLEE = BADLY", "Answer": "868 + 9588 = 10456"}
{"Question": "SAD + DATA = TEST", "Answer": "917 + 7181 = 8098"}
{"Question": "ADD + EDGE = AREA", "Answer": "911 + 8178 = 9089"}
{"Question": "LAB + BELL = ASSET", "Answer": "419 + 9644 = 10063"}
{"Question": "LOT + TALL = AUTO", "Answer": "583 + 3455 = 4038"}
{"Question": "LAB + BELL = PAPER", "Answer": "509 + 9655 = 10164"}
{"Question": "ODD + EDGE = ANGER", "Answer": "855 + 9539 = 10394"}
{"Question": "LET + TALL = LESS", "Answer": "645 + 5766 = 6411"}
{"Question": "LAB + BELL = AWARE", "Answer": "619 + 9566 = 10185"}
{"Question": "ODD + EDGE = ALLOW", "Answer": "277 + 9749 = 10026"}
{"Question": "LAP + POLL = ADAPT", "Answer": "719 + 9477 = 10196"}
{"Question": "ALL + ELSE = VISIT", "Answer": "477 + 9729 = 10206"}
{"Question": "TOO + BOMB = SMART", "Answer": "677 + 9709 = 10386"}
{"Question": "ILL + ELSE = ASSET", "Answer": "288 + 9809 = 10097"}
{"Question": "SIT + TOSS = FIFTH", "Answer": "809 + 9388 = 10197"}
{"Question": "LAB + BELL = MAYBE", "Answer": "809 + 9788 = 10597"}
{"Question": "TOE + MEET = ONTO", "Answer": "495 + 8554 = 9049"}
{"Question": "SEA + MASS = THEME", "Answer": "538 + 9855 = 10393"}
{"Question": "FEE + SELF = COLOR", "Answer": "855 + 9548 = 10403"}
{"Question": "TOO + SOFT = REFER", "Answer": "477 + 9724 = 10201"}
{"Question": "TOO + PORT = REFER", "Answer": "388 + 9813 = 10201"}
{"Question": "ALL + FLEE = DRESS", "Answer": "844 + 9422 = 10266"}
{"Question": "EGG + FLEE = APPLY", "Answer": "588 + 9455 = 10043"}
{"Question": "FEE + BELL = STAFF", "Answer": "866 + 9622 = 10488"}
{"Question": "DAD + CODE = ASSET", "Answer": "212 + 9823 = 10035"}
{"Question": "TOO + BONE = ASSET", "Answer": "822 + 9246 = 10068"}
{"Question": "DAD + RIDE = OFFER", "Answer": "252 + 9827 = 10079"}
{"Question": "OWE + BEER = ALLOW", "Answer": "862 + 9224 = 10086"}
{"Question": "CEO + LOOK = APPLE", "Answer": "872 + 9225 = 10097"}
{"Question": "POP + TYPE = ESSAY", "Answer": "484 + 9541 = 10025"}
{"Question": "LIE + ROLL = INNER", "Answer": "415 + 9644 = 10059"}
{"Question": "DAD + BODY = ALLOW", "Answer": "414 + 9648 = 10062"}
{"Question": "SEA + LOSS = APPLE", "Answer": "451 + 9644 = 10095"}
{"Question": "FEE + TEAR = APART", "Answer": "744 + 9415 = 10159"}
{"Question": "SET + LOSS = TITLE", "Answer": "451 + 9744 = 10195"}
{"Question": "ODD + IDEA = STATE", "Answer": "744 + 9462 = 10206"}
{"Question": "DAD + CODE = GREEN", "Answer": "484 + 9742 = 10226"}
{"Question": "FEE + BEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "844 + 9402 = 10246"}
{"Question": "DAD + CODE = AGENT", "Answer": "414 + 9842 = 10256"}
{"Question": "DAD + RIDE = AFTER", "Answer": "414 + 9845 = 10259"}
{"Question": "MOM + GAME = ORDER", "Answer": "414 + 9846 = 10260"}
{"Question": "DAD + HIDE = EXACT", "Answer": "424 + 9841 = 10265"}
{"Question": "DAD + RIDE = EXTRA", "Answer": "454 + 9841 = 10295"}
{"Question": "DAD + SIDE = CHEST", "Answer": "454 + 9842 = 10296"}
{"Question": "SHE + MEET = TOOTH", "Answer": "465 + 9551 = 10016"}
{"Question": "ALL + PLUS = USUAL", "Answer": "655 + 9510 = 10165"}
{"Question": "EYE + THEM = FIFTY", "Answer": "535 + 9658 = 10193"}
{"Question": "TOO + CODE = ELECT", "Answer": "655 + 9541 = 10196"}
{"Question": "DAD + BODY = CHEEK", "Answer": "575 + 9653 = 10228"}
{"Question": "EYE + THEM = DIRTY", "Answer": "535 + 9758 = 10293"}
{"Question": "MOM + CAMP = KNOCK", "Answer": "535 + 9856 = 10391"}
{"Question": "BET + HERE = CATCH", "Answer": "854 + 9565 = 10419"}
{"Question": "DIE + TEEN = DATA", "Answer": "356 + 2664 = 3020"}
{"Question": "MOM + NAME = OCEAN", "Answer": "616 + 9763 = 10379"}
{"Question": "MOM + CAMP = ORDER", "Answer": "616 + 9764 = 10380"}
{"Question": "DAD + CODE = WHICH", "Answer": "626 + 9764 = 10390"}
{"Question": "LAP + SELL = PHASE", "Answer": "631 + 9766 = 10397"}
{"Question": "EYE + CHEF = MARRY", "Answer": "686 + 9762 = 10448"}
{"Question": "FEE + HERO = BRIEF", "Answer": "866 + 9602 = 10468"}
{"Question": "EYE + CHEF = YOUTH", "Answer": "616 + 9862 = 10478"}
{"Question": "DAD + CODE = ENJOY", "Answer": "626 + 9861 = 10487"}
{"Question": "TOO + CORN = FENCE", "Answer": "866 + 9624 = 10490"}
{"Question": "EYE + CHEF = BUNCH", "Answer": "636 + 9862 = 10498"}
{"Question": "EYE + STEP = TYPE", "Answer": "737 + 4570 = 5307"}
{"Question": "BAN + DATA = BAND", "Answer": "971 + 8747 = 9718"}
{"Question": "DAD + BODY = ERROR", "Answer": "747 + 9273 = 10020"}
{"Question": "SAD + LESS = APPLE", "Answer": "716 + 9377 = 10093"}
{"Question": "EYE + THEM = LIMIT", "Answer": "737 + 9472 = 10209"}
{"Question": "MOM + NAME = GREEN", "Answer": "757 + 9472 = 10229"}
{"Question": "EYE + DIET = BASIS", "Answer": "767 + 9475 = 10242"}
{"Question": "POP + TYPE = HONEY", "Answer": "707 + 9578 = 10285"}
{"Question": "FEE + TEAM = ADMIT", "Answer": "577 + 9712 = 10289"}
{"Question": "EYE + THEM = YOUTH", "Answer": "717 + 9578 = 10295"}
{"Question": "DAD + CODE = EXACT", "Answer": "727 + 9571 = 10298"}
{"Question": "BAD + ODDS = STATE", "Answer": "537 + 9771 = 10308"}
{"Question": "EYE + STEP = PARTY", "Answer": "787 + 9571 = 10358"}
{"Question": "DAD + BODY = CLASS", "Answer": "747 + 9675 = 10422"}
{"Question": "DAD + BODY = MAYOR", "Answer": "707 + 9875 = 10582"}
{"Question": "RAW + DATA = THIRD", "Answer": "872 + 9717 = 10589"}
{"Question": "TOO + LOSE = SHELF", "Answer": "877 + 9715 = 10592"}
{"Question": "EYE + IDEA = AVOID", "Answer": "727 + 9871 = 10598"}
{"Question": "TOO + BOWL = LIMIT", "Answer": "877 + 9731 = 10608"}
{"Question": "TOO + COAL = LEAST", "Answer": "877 + 9761 = 10638"}
{"Question": "THE + BEER = TOOTH", "Answer": "128 + 9884 = 10012"}
{"Question": "TOO + ROPE = APART", "Answer": "388 + 9805 = 10193"}
{"Question": "TWO + ROOF = FEWER", "Answer": "328 + 9881 = 10209"}
{"Question": "CAN + DATA = FENCE", "Answer": "382 + 9848 = 10230"}
{"Question": "FEE + BEAR = START", "Answer": "488 + 9832 = 10320"}
{"Question": "RED + RARE = AIDE", "Answer": "730 + 7873 = 8603"}
{"Question": "NET + NONE = TOOTH", "Answer": "921 + 9092 = 10013"}
{"Question": "PIE + PIPE = AREA", "Answer": "583 + 5853 = 6436"}
{"Question": "RAW + RARE = AREA", "Answer": "892 + 8987 = 9879"}
{"Question": "EAR + EVER = HERE", "Answer": "482 + 4942 = 5424"}
{"Question": "EAR + EVER = VARY", "Answer": "517 + 5657 = 6174"}
{"Question": "EAR + EVER = RARE", "Answer": "809 + 8289 = 9098"}
{"Question": "OFF + FOOT = ONTO", "Answer": "655 + 5661 = 6316"}
{"Question": "OFF + FOOD = DATA", "Answer": "833 + 3884 = 4717"}
{"Question": "ODD + DOOR = HERO", "Answer": "855 + 5883 = 6738"}
{"Question": "ODD + DOOR = WORD", "Answer": "911 + 1990 = 2901"}
{"Question": "OUR + ROOT = TURN", "Answer": "506 + 6557 = 7063"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = APPLE", "Answer": "519 + 9556 = 10075"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = ISSUE", "Answer": "529 + 9556 = 10085"}
{"Question": "OUT + TOOL = APPLE", "Answer": "529 + 9558 = 10087"}
{"Question": "OLD + DOOR = CLASS", "Answer": "609 + 9668 = 10277"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = ABOVE", "Answer": "619 + 9667 = 10286"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = ALONG", "Answer": "619 + 9668 = 10287"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = PLATE", "Answer": "629 + 9667 = 10296"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = RARE", "Answer": "751 + 1776 = 2527"}
{"Question": "OUR + ROOT = ONTO", "Answer": "746 + 6771 = 7517"}
{"Question": "OLD + DOOR = ELITE", "Answer": "709 + 9772 = 10481"}
{"Question": "OUR + ROOM = HUMAN", "Answer": "709 + 9774 = 10483"}
{"Question": "OLD + DOOR = CIVIL", "Answer": "729 + 9773 = 10502"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = CIVIL", "Answer": "729 + 9774 = 10503"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = HONOR", "Answer": "729 + 9775 = 10504"}
{"Question": "END + DEEP = STATE", "Answer": "729 + 9778 = 10507"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = CLASS", "Answer": "759 + 9774 = 10533"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = DRAMA", "Answer": "759 + 9776 = 10535"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEEN = BLADE", "Answer": "759 + 9778 = 10537"}
{"Question": "OIL + LOOK = KISS", "Answer": "872 + 2883 = 3755"}
{"Question": "OLD + DOOR = LEVEL", "Answer": "819 + 9882 = 10701"}
{"Question": "MOM + MOON = EVENT", "Answer": "929 + 9225 = 10154"}
{"Question": "POP + POOL = LESS", "Answer": "838 + 8339 = 9177"}
{"Question": "MOM + MOON = NERVE", "Answer": "939 + 9331 = 10270"}
{"Question": "POP + POOL = SALES", "Answer": "939 + 9332 = 10271"}
{"Question": "MOM + MOOD = PIANO", "Answer": "939 + 9334 = 10273"}
{"Question": "MOM + MOOD = ASIDE", "Answer": "939 + 9337 = 10276"}
{"Question": "MOM + MOOD = AGREE", "Answer": "939 + 9338 = 10277"}
{"Question": "MOM + MOOD = ODDS", "Answer": "565 + 5662 = 6227"}
{"Question": "MOM + MOON = KNEE", "Answer": "868 + 8665 = 9533"}
{"Question": "MOM + MOON = ONCE", "Answer": "676 + 6774 = 7450"}
{"Question": "POP + POOL = ONLY", "Answer": "676 + 6775 = 7451"}
{"Question": "TEN + TENT = AWARE", "Answer": "923 + 9239 = 10162"}
{"Question": "POP + POLL = ADAPT", "Answer": "929 + 9266 = 10195"}
{"Question": "TEN + TENT = PIPE", "Answer": "835 + 8358 = 9193"}
{"Question": "POP + POLL = SALES", "Answer": "939 + 9322 = 10261"}
{"Question": "POP + POLL = RADIO", "Answer": "939 + 9344 = 10283"}
{"Question": "POP + POLL = DELAY", "Answer": "949 + 9433 = 10382"}
{"Question": "TEN + TENT = ONTO", "Answer": "651 + 6516 = 7167"}
{"Question": "TEN + TENT = INTO", "Answer": "752 + 7527 = 8279"}
{"Question": "TEN + TENT = DATA", "Answer": "467 + 4674 = 5141"}
{"Question": "POP + POLL = ALSO", "Answer": "575 + 5722 = 6297"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEEP = AWARE", "Answer": "919 + 9223 = 10142"}
{"Question": "POP + POEM = ENEMY", "Answer": "929 + 9214 = 10143"}
{"Question": "THE + THAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "923 + 9269 = 10192"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEEP = TAPE", "Answer": "818 + 8335 = 9153"}
{"Question": "MOM + MORE = TREAT", "Answer": "939 + 9302 = 10241"}
{"Question": "ONE + ONTO = TREAT", "Answer": "932 + 9319 = 10251"}
{"Question": "DAD + DARK = THREE", "Answer": "939 + 9327 = 10266"}
{"Question": "MOM + MODE = TREAT", "Answer": "939 + 9342 = 10281"}
{"Question": "DAD + DARE = THEIR", "Answer": "949 + 9423 = 10372"}
{"Question": "DAD + DARE = SKILL", "Answer": "949 + 9428 = 10377"}
{"Question": "POP + POEM = TREAT", "Answer": "949 + 9432 = 10381"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEER = RARE", "Answer": "727 + 7558 = 8285"}
{"Question": "DAD + DARE = CHEST", "Answer": "959 + 9524 = 10483"}
{"Question": "ARM + AREA = LOCAL", "Answer": "952 + 9539 = 10491"}
{"Question": "THE + THAT = HALL", "Answer": "562 + 5615 = 6177"}
{"Question": "ARM + AREA = HUMAN", "Answer": "965 + 9629 = 10594"}
{"Question": "DAD + DARE = AREA", "Answer": "676 + 6741 = 7417"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEEP = PIPE", "Answer": "818 + 8779 = 9597"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEEP = PACE", "Answer": "868 + 8779 = 9647"}
{"Question": "BOY + BOMB = MAYBE", "Answer": "976 + 9719 = 10695"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEEP = ASIDE", "Answer": "919 + 9778 = 10697"}
{"Question": "EAT + EASE = STEP", "Answer": "685 + 6876 = 7561"}
{"Question": "DAD + DARK = AREA", "Answer": "787 + 7861 = 8648"}
{"Question": "ARM + AREA = LEGAL", "Answer": "982 + 9809 = 10791"}
{"Question": "ART + AREA = METAL", "Answer": "987 + 9809 = 10796"}
{"Question": "DOG + GOOD = APPLE", "Answer": "829 + 9228 = 10057"}
{"Question": "FOR + ROOF = APART", "Answer": "749 + 9447 = 10196"}
{"Question": "DOG + GOOD = IMAGE", "Answer": "849 + 9448 = 10297"}
{"Question": "NET + TEEN = NAME", "Answer": "857 + 7558 = 8415"}
{"Question": "RED + DEER = TOOTH", "Answer": "459 + 9554 = 10013"}
{"Question": "RED + DEER = TASTE", "Answer": "659 + 9556 = 10215"}
{"Question": "RED + DEER = ODDS", "Answer": "562 + 2665 = 3227"}
{"Question": "LOT + TOOL = ONLY", "Answer": "576 + 6775 = 7351"}
{"Question": "FOR + ROOF = ADAPT", "Answer": "379 + 9773 = 10152"}
{"Question": "DOG + GOOD = ASIDE", "Answer": "579 + 9775 = 10354"}
{"Question": "DOG + GOOD = CLASS", "Answer": "679 + 9776 = 10455"}
{"Question": "DOG + GOOD = HIGH", "Answer": "186 + 6881 = 7067"}
{"Question": "NET + TEEN = EASE", "Answer": "187 + 7881 = 8068"}
{"Question": "NOR + ROOT = TURN", "Answer": "924 + 4225 = 5149"}
{"Question": "NEW + WEEK = NINE", "Answer": "948 + 8446 = 9394"}
{"Question": "YES + SEED = LOOSE", "Answer": "649 + 9445 = 10094"}
{"Question": "TOP + POOL = ADAPT", "Answer": "749 + 9448 = 10197"}
{"Question": "BET + TEEN = PHOTO", "Answer": "849 + 9443 = 10292"}
{"Question": "BED + DEEP = ASIDE", "Answer": "849 + 9445 = 10294"}
{"Question": "TOP + POOR = TREE", "Answer": "857 + 7554 = 8411"}
{"Question": "BED + DEEP = ODDS", "Answer": "562 + 2667 = 3229"}
{"Question": "NOW + WOOD = DOWN", "Answer": "974 + 4775 = 5749"}
{"Question": "RED + DEEP = PURE", "Answer": "578 + 8779 = 9357"}
{"Question": "RED + DEEP = OCCUR", "Answer": "279 + 9773 = 10052"}
{"Question": "TEN + NEED = PHOTO", "Answer": "579 + 9774 = 10353"}
{"Question": "FEW + WEEK = STAFF", "Answer": "579 + 9776 = 10355"}
{"Question": "BED + DEEP = MAYBE", "Answer": "579 + 9778 = 10357"}
{"Question": "NOR + ROOT = TEEN", "Answer": "783 + 3884 = 4667"}
{"Question": "TOO + ONTO = TEST", "Answer": "211 + 1821 = 2032"}
{"Question": "SEE + EASE = DEAD", "Answer": "511 + 1651 = 2162"}
{"Question": "SEE + EASE = SEAT", "Answer": "544 + 4954 = 5498"}
{"Question": "ADD + DEAD = ELSE", "Answer": "811 + 1281 = 2092"}
{"Question": "SEE + EASE = ODDS", "Answer": "844 + 4384 = 5228"}
{"Question": "EAR + AREA = BALL", "Answer": "647 + 4764 = 5411"}
{"Question": "SEA + EASE = SOON", "Answer": "654 + 5465 = 6119"}
{"Question": "SEA + EASE = ODDS", "Answer": "743 + 4374 = 5117"}
{"Question": "SEA + EASE = SELL", "Answer": "768 + 6876 = 7644"}
{"Question": "SEA + EASE = THAT", "Answer": "831 + 3183 = 4014"}
{"Question": "EAR + AREA = EDGE", "Answer": "871 + 7187 = 8058"}
{"Question": "SEA + EASE = SAFE", "Answer": "980 + 8098 = 9078"}
{"Question": "ALL + LEAN = NINE", "Answer": "144 + 4915 = 5059"}
{"Question": "TOO + ODDS = COST", "Answer": "822 + 2446 = 3268"}
{"Question": "TOO + ODDS = DATA", "Answer": "833 + 3449 = 4282"}
{"Question": "ADD + DEAL = MALE", "Answer": "577 + 7952 = 8529"}
{"Question": "BAR + RARE = AREA", "Answer": "865 + 5651 = 6516"}
{"Question": "TOO + ODDS = SEED", "Answer": "233 + 3774 = 4007"}
{"Question": "ADD + DRAG = EDGE", "Answer": "744 + 4671 = 5415"}
{"Question": "SET + ELSE = LOTS", "Answer": "752 + 5675 = 6427"}
{"Question": "ADD + DEAL = ALLY", "Answer": "766 + 6573 = 7339"}
{"Question": "EAT + AREA = TIRE", "Answer": "789 + 8678 = 9467"}
{"Question": "EAT + AREA = RATE", "Answer": "853 + 5685 = 6538"}
{"Question": "ADD + DEAL = AREA", "Answer": "877 + 7581 = 8458"}
{"Question": "SEE + EAST = STAR", "Answer": "877 + 7685 = 8562"}
{"Question": "ERA + ARAB = BEER", "Answer": "394 + 4945 = 5339"}
{"Question": "ERA + AREA = EASE", "Answer": "281 + 1821 = 2102"}
{"Question": "ERA + AREA = BAKE", "Answer": "472 + 2742 = 3214"}
{"Question": "NET + TENT = NAME", "Answer": "463 + 3643 = 4106"}
{"Question": "ERA + AREA = RACE", "Answer": "854 + 4584 = 5438"}
{"Question": "SEA + TEST = SEAT", "Answer": "910 + 8198 = 9108"}
{"Question": "CAR + RACE = AREA", "Answer": "832 + 2381 = 3213"}
{"Question": "NOT + TONE = EVEN", "Answer": "582 + 2853 = 3435"}
{"Question": "NET + TEND = DOWN", "Answer": "783 + 3874 = 4657"}
{"Question": "SET + TENT = EASE", "Answer": "821 + 1261 = 2082"}
{"Question": "SHE + EASE = TOOTH", "Answer": "289 + 9729 = 10018"}
{"Question": "NOT + TENT = LOOSE", "Answer": "209 + 9829 = 10038"}
{"Question": "AID + DEAD = ISSUE", "Answer": "219 + 9829 = 10048"}
{"Question": "ART + THAT = ARAB", "Answer": "302 + 2732 = 3034"}
{"Question": "BED + DEAD = BALL", "Answer": "938 + 8328 = 9266"}
{"Question": "BED + DEAD = ALLOW", "Answer": "739 + 9319 = 10058"}
{"Question": "LET + TEST = USUAL", "Answer": "839 + 9309 = 10148"}
{"Question": "NET + TEST = AGAIN", "Answer": "839 + 9329 = 10168"}
{"Question": "YET + TENT = FIFTY", "Answer": "839 + 9359 = 10198"}
{"Question": "TWO + ONTO = BOOT", "Answer": "482 + 2742 = 3224"}
{"Question": "NOT + TENT = NONE", "Answer": "403 + 3643 = 4046"}
{"Question": "TWO + ONTO = TEEN", "Answer": "473 + 3643 = 4116"}
{"Question": "BED + DEAD = RARE", "Answer": "947 + 7437 = 8384"}
{"Question": "AID + DEAD = INNER", "Answer": "419 + 9649 = 10068"}
{"Question": "AND + DEAD = KNEE", "Answer": "513 + 3653 = 4166"}
{"Question": "SUE + EASE = RURAL", "Answer": "509 + 9659 = 10168"}
{"Question": "JOB + BOMB = EMPTY", "Answer": "759 + 9509 = 10268"}
{"Question": "RED + DEAD = ANGRY", "Answer": "759 + 9519 = 10278"}
{"Question": "BED + DEAD = CLASS", "Answer": "759 + 9529 = 10288"}
{"Question": "AID + DEAD = GUIDE", "Answer": "539 + 9859 = 10398"}
{"Question": "AND + DEAD = IDEA", "Answer": "613 + 3763 = 4376"}
{"Question": "SHE + ELSE = BELL", "Answer": "624 + 4864 = 5488"}
{"Question": "AID + DEAD = FIBER", "Answer": "609 + 9769 = 10378"}
{"Question": "BET + TEST = SHALL", "Answer": "769 + 9619 = 10388"}
{"Question": "LET + TEST = SHALL", "Answer": "869 + 9619 = 10488"}
{"Question": "YET + TENT = DIRTY", "Answer": "869 + 9629 = 10498"}
{"Question": "SHE + EASE = AREA", "Answer": "741 + 1271 = 2012"}
{"Question": "PET + TEST = STOP", "Answer": "472 + 2732 = 3204"}
{"Question": "SHE + ELSE = FEEL", "Answer": "752 + 2472 = 3224"}
{"Question": "SHE + EASE = YEAH", "Answer": "705 + 5875 = 6580"}
{"Question": "LET + TENT = APPLY", "Answer": "279 + 9749 = 10028"}
{"Question": "SUE + EASE = UPPER", "Answer": "719 + 9379 = 10098"}
{"Question": "JOB + BOMB = LIMIT", "Answer": "479 + 9729 = 10208"}
{"Question": "RED + DEAD = COURT", "Answer": "479 + 9769 = 10248"}
{"Question": "JOB + BOMB = ADMIT", "Answer": "679 + 9749 = 10428"}
{"Question": "SHE + ELSE = HOTEL", "Answer": "719 + 9879 = 10598"}
{"Question": "TWO + ONTO = TWIN", "Answer": "837 + 7487 = 8324"}
{"Question": "LET + TENT = BIBLE", "Answer": "289 + 9839 = 10128"}
{"Question": "TOP + POST = ODDS", "Answer": "721 + 1287 = 2008"}
{"Question": "EAR + RACE = CREW", "Answer": "842 + 2438 = 3280"}
{"Question": "SUE + TEST = UPPER", "Answer": "416 + 9649 = 10065"}
{"Question": "DAD + EASE = SHIFT", "Answer": "848 + 9419 = 10267"}
{"Question": "DAY + YARD = THREE", "Answer": "849 + 9428 = 10277"}
{"Question": "TEN + ONTO = TONE", "Answer": "539 + 4954 = 5493"}
{"Question": "HEY + YEAH = AWARE", "Answer": "659 + 9516 = 10175"}
{"Question": "TEN + NEXT = AWARE", "Answer": "659 + 9526 = 10185"}
{"Question": "DAD + EASE = SKILL", "Answer": "858 + 9519 = 10377"}
{"Question": "NUT + TURN = BIRTH", "Answer": "859 + 9538 = 10397"}
{"Question": "HEY + YEAH = ABOVE", "Answer": "769 + 9617 = 10386"}
{"Question": "RED + DEAR = GUIDE", "Answer": "769 + 9627 = 10396"}
{"Question": "DAY + YARD = DEER", "Answer": "271 + 1732 = 2003"}
{"Question": "GOD + EDGE = OFFER", "Answer": "713 + 9379 = 10092"}
{"Question": "LAP + POOL = ADAPT", "Answer": "419 + 9774 = 10193"}
{"Question": "TOP + POET = AHEAD", "Answer": "579 + 9735 = 10314"}
{"Question": "RED + DEAR = ASIDE", "Answer": "879 + 9718 = 10597"}
{"Question": "RID + DEER = TASTE", "Answer": "839 + 9778 = 10617"}
{"Question": "HEY + YEAH = BLADE", "Answer": "879 + 9768 = 10647"}
{"Question": "TEN + ONTO = NONE", "Answer": "853 + 2382 = 3235"}
{"Question": "EAT + TAKE = AREA", "Answer": "187 + 7831 = 8018"}
{"Question": "DAD + EASE = AREA", "Answer": "181 + 7897 = 8078"}
{"Question": "MRS + SEEM = IRISH", "Answer": "309 + 9883 = 10192"}
{"Question": "NET + TONE = ERROR", "Answer": "419 + 9641 = 10060"}
{"Question": "CAT + TALL = PIECE", "Answer": "849 + 9433 = 10282"}
{"Question": "SET + TELL = ELSE", "Answer": "654 + 4511 = 5165"}
{"Question": "FEW + WELL = LIFE", "Answer": "457 + 7588 = 8045"}
{"Question": "HIM + MISS = DRAMA", "Answer": "759 + 9533 = 10292"}
{"Question": "ALL + DEAD = RIVER", "Answer": "522 + 9859 = 10381"}
{"Question": "HOT + TOSS = WASTE", "Answer": "859 + 9533 = 10392"}
{"Question": "ALL + DEAD = COLOR", "Answer": "544 + 9859 = 10403"}
{"Question": "LAP + PASS = SELL", "Answer": "567 + 7688 = 8255"}
{"Question": "FAT + TALL = FLEE", "Answer": "867 + 7655 = 8522"}
{"Question": "BET + TELL = BITE", "Answer": "372 + 2755 = 3127"}
{"Question": "BET + TELL = BLUE", "Answer": "574 + 4733 = 5307"}
{"Question": "CEO + ONCE = ERROR", "Answer": "719 + 9371 = 10090"}
{"Question": "LAP + PASS = BIBLE", "Answer": "379 + 9755 = 10134"}
{"Question": "EGG + AREA = BIBLE", "Answer": "788 + 9379 = 10167"}
{"Question": "EGG + AREA = SCORE", "Answer": "788 + 9679 = 10467"}
{"Question": "GET + TEAM = GAME", "Answer": "928 + 8214 = 9142"}
{"Question": "AID + DISH = ODDS", "Answer": "742 + 2486 = 3228"}
{"Question": "LEG + GEAR = APPLE", "Answer": "649 + 9415 = 10064"}
{"Question": "TEN + NEAR = ADAPT", "Answer": "749 + 9418 = 10167"}
{"Question": "HIS + SITE = TREAT", "Answer": "849 + 9412 = 10261"}
{"Question": "AID + DISH = SMELL", "Answer": "849 + 9417 = 10266"}
{"Question": "TEN + NEAR = DATA", "Answer": "951 + 1543 = 2494"}
{"Question": "EAR + RANK = KNEE", "Answer": "753 + 3524 = 4277"}
{"Question": "FOR + ROLE = AREA", "Answer": "753 + 3561 = 4314"}
{"Question": "BAD + DATE = BEER", "Answer": "756 + 6583 = 7339"}
{"Question": "TEN + NEAR = APART", "Answer": "659 + 9517 = 10176"}
{"Question": "TIP + PICK = ADAPT", "Answer": "659 + 9537 = 10196"}
{"Question": "FOR + ROSE = STAFF", "Answer": "759 + 9518 = 10277"}
{"Question": "DIG + GIRL = WORLD", "Answer": "759 + 9528 = 10287"}
{"Question": "VIA + AIDE = TREAT", "Answer": "759 + 9532 = 10291"}
{"Question": "AIM + MINE = CLEAN", "Answer": "859 + 9523 = 10382"}
{"Question": "TIP + ONTO = PRIOR", "Answer": "531 + 9859 = 10390"}
{"Question": "ART + TRIP = ELITE", "Answer": "859 + 9532 = 10391"}
{"Question": "LOT + TALE = PHOTO", "Answer": "539 + 9854 = 10393"}
{"Question": "BED + DEAL = GRADE", "Answer": "859 + 9536 = 10395"}
{"Question": "ART + TRIP = QUITE", "Answer": "859 + 9537 = 10396"}
{"Question": "BIG + GIFT = REFER", "Answer": "859 + 9542 = 10401"}
{"Question": "CEO + DEAD = CODE", "Answer": "562 + 4684 = 5246"}
{"Question": "FAR + RATE = STUFF", "Answer": "769 + 9608 = 10377"}
{"Question": "AID + DIET = ENJOY", "Answer": "769 + 9615 = 10384"}
{"Question": "EAT + TASK = SMOKE", "Answer": "769 + 9618 = 10387"}
{"Question": "HIS + SITE = GUEST", "Answer": "769 + 9623 = 10392"}
{"Question": "AIM + MILK = TERMS", "Answer": "769 + 9625 = 10394"}
{"Question": "TOP + POEM = ELITE", "Answer": "869 + 9612 = 10481"}
{"Question": "AIR + RICE = CHEAP", "Answer": "869 + 9614 = 10483"}
{"Question": "ART + TRIP = DEPTH", "Answer": "869 + 9624 = 10493"}
{"Question": "BOY + YOUR = BURY", "Answer": "574 + 4730 = 5304"}
{"Question": "BED + DEAR = RARE", "Answer": "478 + 8719 = 9197"}
{"Question": "YES + SELF = LOOSE", "Answer": "379 + 9718 = 10097"}
{"Question": "TAP + PEER = ADAPT", "Answer": "419 + 9775 = 10194"}
{"Question": "HER + READ = AWARE", "Answer": "479 + 9718 = 10197"}
{"Question": "LAW + WAVE = CIVIL", "Answer": "479 + 9725 = 10204"}
{"Question": "FAN + NAME = STUFF", "Answer": "479 + 9765 = 10244"}
{"Question": "HAT + TANK = NORTH", "Answer": "579 + 9716 = 10295"}
{"Question": "BED + DESK = TASTE", "Answer": "579 + 9738 = 10317"}
{"Question": "YES + SOON = NONE", "Answer": "952 + 2883 = 3835"}
{"Question": "BAD + DARE = AREA", "Answer": "487 + 7831 = 8318"}
{"Question": "HAT + TAIL = FIFTH", "Answer": "389 + 9804 = 10193"}
{"Question": "OFF + ROOF = EVER", "Answer": "544 + 8554 = 9098"}
{"Question": "ODD + GOOD = HIGH", "Answer": "577 + 3557 = 4134"}
{"Question": "OFF + ROOF = HERE", "Answer": "611 + 7661 = 8272"}
{"Question": "ODD + FOOD = DRAMA", "Answer": "611 + 9661 = 10272"}
{"Question": "ODD + FOOD = ONTO", "Answer": "633 + 5663 = 6296"}
{"Question": "ODD + FOOD = DAILY", "Answer": "711 + 9771 = 10482"}
{"Question": "ODD + FOOD = DATA", "Answer": "722 + 1772 = 2494"}
{"Question": "ODD + MOOD = THEME", "Answer": "722 + 9772 = 10494"}
{"Question": "OFF + ROOF = AREA", "Answer": "733 + 5773 = 6506"}
{"Question": "ODD + FOOD = DRAFT", "Answer": "811 + 9881 = 10692"}
{"Question": "OFF + ROOF = HERO", "Answer": "844 + 2884 = 3728"}
{"Question": "EGG + FEEL = GOLF", "Answer": "533 + 2559 = 3092"}
{"Question": "EGG + WEEK = ALLOW", "Answer": "533 + 9556 = 10089"}
{"Question": "OFF + GOOD = ODDS", "Answer": "566 + 4551 = 5117"}
{"Question": "EGG + SEED = ODDS", "Answer": "566 + 7551 = 8117"}
{"Question": "ODD + ROOF = FIFTH", "Answer": "577 + 9551 = 10128"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEER = AWARD", "Answer": "577 + 9552 = 10129"}
{"Question": "EGG + KEEP = ADAPT", "Answer": "588 + 9554 = 10142"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEER = GUARD", "Answer": "611 + 9667 = 10278"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEEP = GRAND", "Answer": "611 + 9668 = 10279"}
{"Question": "ONE + MOON = ONTO", "Answer": "624 + 5662 = 6286"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEER = ANGLE", "Answer": "622 + 9664 = 10286"}
{"Question": "OFF + BOOK = REFER", "Answer": "633 + 9668 = 10301"}
{"Question": "EGG + MEET = TASTE", "Answer": "655 + 9661 = 10316"}
{"Question": "EGG + MEET = CATCH", "Answer": "655 + 9663 = 10318"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEEP = PROOF", "Answer": "677 + 9661 = 10338"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEEP = BLOOD", "Answer": "677 + 9662 = 10339"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEEP = POUND", "Answer": "688 + 9661 = 10349"}
{"Question": "EGG + SEEM = DRAMA", "Answer": "688 + 9665 = 10353"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOOK = DRAMA", "Answer": "711 + 9773 = 10484"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEER = GUARD", "Answer": "711 + 9778 = 10489"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEER = MAYBE", "Answer": "722 + 9775 = 10497"}
{"Question": "ODD + ROOT = ENTER", "Answer": "744 + 9775 = 10519"}
{"Question": "EGG + FEEL = ANGLE", "Answer": "755 + 9772 = 10527"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEER = RAISE", "Answer": "766 + 9771 = 10537"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEER = BOARD", "Answer": "766 + 9773 = 10539"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEER = START", "Answer": "766 + 9774 = 10540"}
{"Question": "ODD + MOON = DRAMA", "Answer": "811 + 9885 = 10696"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEEP = GRADE", "Answer": "811 + 9887 = 10698"}
{"Question": "ODD + ROOT = METER", "Answer": "822 + 9887 = 10709"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOOT = TASTE", "Answer": "833 + 9881 = 10714"}
{"Question": "EGG + TEEN = NINE", "Answer": "855 + 2883 = 3738"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEER = SCORE", "Answer": "855 + 9883 = 10738"}
{"Question": "EGG + FEED = DRAMA", "Answer": "866 + 9881 = 10747"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEER = ALIVE", "Answer": "866 + 9882 = 10748"}
{"Question": "ERA + BEER = GRAB", "Answer": "876 + 3887 = 4763"}
{"Question": "ODD + POOR = RADIO", "Answer": "877 + 9881 = 10758"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEER = ANGRY", "Answer": "877 + 9886 = 10763"}
{"Question": "END + NEED = ODDS", "Answer": "561 + 6551 = 7112"}
{"Question": "END + NEED = APART", "Answer": "593 + 9553 = 10146"}
{"Question": "LAY + ALLY = DATA", "Answer": "621 + 2661 = 3282"}
{"Question": "END + NEED = EDGE", "Answer": "653 + 5663 = 6316"}
{"Question": "END + NEED = JUDGE", "Answer": "693 + 9663 = 10356"}
{"Question": "END + NEED = EASE", "Answer": "658 + 5668 = 6326"}
{"Question": "END + NEED = AGREE", "Answer": "698 + 9668 = 10366"}
{"Question": "END + NEED = DATA", "Answer": "712 + 1772 = 2484"}
{"Question": "END + NEED = CLASS", "Answer": "793 + 9773 = 10566"}
{"Question": "END + NEED = ORDER", "Answer": "795 + 9775 = 10570"}
{"Question": "LAY + ALLY = YARD", "Answer": "756 + 5776 = 6532"}
{"Question": "LAY + ALLY = LADY", "Answer": "870 + 7880 = 8750"}
{"Question": "LAY + ALLY = STEEL", "Answer": "894 + 9884 = 10778"}
{"Question": "END + NEED = MODEL", "Answer": "897 + 9887 = 10784"}
{"Question": "OWE + WOOD = DEEP", "Answer": "561 + 6557 = 7118"}
{"Question": "LAB + ALLY = BUYER", "Answer": "691 + 9663 = 10354"}
{"Question": "ETC + TEEN = CLASS", "Answer": "691 + 9664 = 10355"}
{"Question": "OWE + WOOD = GUESS", "Answer": "693 + 9662 = 10355"}
{"Question": "LAP + ALLY = PASS", "Answer": "623 + 2665 = 3288"}
{"Question": "ETC + TEEN = BUNCH", "Answer": "695 + 9663 = 10358"}
{"Question": "DOG + ODDS = GOLD", "Answer": "756 + 5771 = 6527"}
{"Question": "OWE + WOOD = DRESS", "Answer": "795 + 9771 = 10566"}
{"Question": "OWN + WOOD = ONTO", "Answer": "765 + 6772 = 7537"}
{"Question": "ETC + TEEN = RANGE", "Answer": "792 + 9775 = 10567"}
{"Question": "ETC + TEEN = ONCE", "Answer": "831 + 3887 = 4718"}
{"Question": "END + SEED = ODDS", "Answer": "561 + 2551 = 3112"}
{"Question": "OLD + FOOD = ODDS", "Answer": "561 + 4551 = 5112"}
{"Question": "OUT + BOOT = TITLE", "Answer": "581 + 9551 = 10132"}
{"Question": "OIL + COOL = APPLE", "Answer": "528 + 9558 = 10086"}
{"Question": "OLD + MOOD = DRAMA", "Answer": "631 + 9661 = 10292"}
{"Question": "EAT + MEET = ACTOR", "Answer": "612 + 9662 = 10274"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEER = ALIVE", "Answer": "613 + 9663 = 10276"}
{"Question": "OIL + COOL = HELLO", "Answer": "673 + 9663 = 10336"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEER = FORCE", "Answer": "683 + 9663 = 10346"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEER = CLASS", "Answer": "624 + 9664 = 10288"}
{"Question": "OLD + FOOD = LEAVE", "Answer": "615 + 9665 = 10280"}
{"Question": "OIL + COOL = WHICH", "Answer": "625 + 9665 = 10290"}
{"Question": "OIL + COOL = BRICK", "Answer": "627 + 9667 = 10294"}
{"Question": "OWN + MOON = FEWER", "Answer": "637 + 9667 = 10304"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEER = ABLE", "Answer": "648 + 3668 = 4316"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEER = CAUSE", "Answer": "608 + 9668 = 10276"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEER = BLADE", "Answer": "628 + 9668 = 10296"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEER = STATE", "Answer": "638 + 9668 = 10306"}
{"Question": "OIL + TOOL = DATA", "Answer": "712 + 8772 = 9484"}
{"Question": "OWN + MOON = WHERE", "Answer": "712 + 9772 = 10484"}
{"Question": "OLD + FOOD = STEEL", "Answer": "784 + 9774 = 10558"}
{"Question": "OWN + MOON = SENSE", "Answer": "735 + 9775 = 10510"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEER = DAILY", "Answer": "706 + 9776 = 10482"}
{"Question": "OLD + FOOD = DRESS", "Answer": "841 + 9881 = 10722"}
{"Question": "EAT + MEET = THANK", "Answer": "871 + 9881 = 10752"}
{"Question": "END + FEED = DATA", "Answer": "813 + 2883 = 3696"}
{"Question": "OIL + COOL = KICK", "Answer": "873 + 5883 = 6756"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEER = ASIDE", "Answer": "814 + 9884 = 10698"}
{"Question": "END + FEED = STATE", "Answer": "824 + 9884 = 10708"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEER = SCORE", "Answer": "864 + 9884 = 10748"}
{"Question": "OIL + COOL = SEIZE", "Answer": "875 + 9885 = 10760"}
{"Question": "OLD + FOOD = LIMIT", "Answer": "816 + 9886 = 10702"}
{"Question": "OIL + COOL = PITCH", "Answer": "807 + 9887 = 10694"}
{"Question": "OUT + BOOT = CATCH", "Answer": "827 + 9887 = 10714"}
{"Question": "OUR + DOOR = AGREE", "Answer": "857 + 9887 = 10744"}
{"Question": "ERA + FEEL = APPLY", "Answer": "521 + 9557 = 10078"}
{"Question": "ERA + WEEK = ALLOW", "Answer": "521 + 9558 = 10079"}
{"Question": "ERA + TEEN = ADAPT", "Answer": "571 + 9558 = 10129"}
{"Question": "OUR + TOOL = APART", "Answer": "583 + 9556 = 10139"}
{"Question": "END + FEEL = APPLY", "Answer": "526 + 9558 = 10084"}
{"Question": "EAR + FEEL = APPLE", "Answer": "518 + 9557 = 10075"}
{"Question": "END + FEEL = APPLE", "Answer": "527 + 9558 = 10085"}
{"Question": "OUT + DOOR = THREE", "Answer": "681 + 9663 = 10344"}
{"Question": "DAY + ODDS = YIELD", "Answer": "681 + 9665 = 10346"}
{"Question": "OWE + ROOT = WATER", "Answer": "617 + 9662 = 10279"}
{"Question": "EAR + KEEP = WORKS", "Answer": "632 + 9665 = 10297"}
{"Question": "OWN + DOOR = WHERE", "Answer": "614 + 9668 = 10282"}
{"Question": "END + MEET = DRAMA", "Answer": "721 + 9773 = 10494"}
{"Question": "ONE + ROOT = EXTRA", "Answer": "721 + 9774 = 10495"}
{"Question": "ETC + FEEL = LIMIT", "Answer": "732 + 9771 = 10503"}
{"Question": "ETC + FEEL = COLOR", "Answer": "731 + 9775 = 10506"}
{"Question": "DNA + ODDS = AHEAD", "Answer": "741 + 9776 = 10517"}
{"Question": "EAT + KEEP = THANK", "Answer": "751 + 9778 = 10529"}
{"Question": "ERA + MEET = ACTOR", "Answer": "761 + 9775 = 10536"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEEP = ROUND", "Answer": "761 + 9778 = 10539"}
{"Question": "ERA + SEED = EASE", "Answer": "795 + 6772 = 7567"}
{"Question": "ERA + DEEP = STATE", "Answer": "735 + 9772 = 10507"}
{"Question": "DIE + ODDS = AHEAD", "Answer": "745 + 9772 = 10517"}
{"Question": "EAR + FEED = JUDGE", "Answer": "762 + 9775 = 10537"}
{"Question": "OUR + COOL = HELLO", "Answer": "782 + 9775 = 10557"}
{"Question": "DUE + ODDS = GUEST", "Answer": "704 + 9778 = 10482"}
{"Question": "LET + ALLY = EXTRA", "Answer": "714 + 9775 = 10489"}
{"Question": "OIL + ROOT = METER", "Answer": "734 + 9775 = 10509"}
{"Question": "ONE + DOOR = SPEED", "Answer": "785 + 9774 = 10559"}
{"Question": "LIE + ALLY = IDEAL", "Answer": "816 + 9882 = 10698"}
{"Question": "OIL + ROOT = ENTER", "Answer": "832 + 9887 = 10719"}
{"Question": "ONE + DOOR = TIRED", "Answer": "842 + 9887 = 10729"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEEP = SHAPE", "Answer": "873 + 9885 = 10758"}
{"Question": "EAR + TEEN = GIANT", "Answer": "874 + 9885 = 10759"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEEP = START", "Answer": "876 + 9884 = 10760"}
{"Question": "DAY + ODDS = MAYOR", "Answer": "806 + 9887 = 10693"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOOM = APPLE", "Answer": "828 + 9228 = 10056"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOOM = ARAB", "Answer": "838 + 6338 = 7176"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOOM = TRIBE", "Answer": "848 + 9448 = 10296"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOOM = MEET", "Answer": "454 + 3554 = 4008"}
{"Question": "MOM + ROOM = BEER", "Answer": "454 + 8554 = 9008"}
{"Question": "MOM + ROOM = AREA", "Answer": "757 + 3557 = 4314"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOOM = MALL", "Answer": "272 + 1772 = 2044"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOOM = AGREE", "Answer": "383 + 9883 = 10266"}
{"Question": "LEG + FEEL = APPLE", "Answer": "736 + 9337 = 10073"}
{"Question": "TOP + ROOT = PAPER", "Answer": "831 + 9338 = 10169"}
{"Question": "KEY + SEEK = AWARE", "Answer": "835 + 9338 = 10173"}
{"Question": "MOM + DOOR = APART", "Answer": "838 + 9337 = 10175"}
{"Question": "MOM + LOOK = APPLE", "Answer": "646 + 9447 = 10093"}
{"Question": "KEY + SEEK = LOOSE", "Answer": "648 + 9446 = 10094"}
{"Question": "MOM + SOON = TRUST", "Answer": "848 + 9443 = 10291"}
{"Question": "KEY + SEEK = ABUSE", "Answer": "846 + 9448 = 10294"}
{"Question": "NEW + TEEN = NINE", "Answer": "945 + 8449 = 9394"}
{"Question": "KEY + SEEK = TOOTH", "Answer": "458 + 9554 = 10012"}
{"Question": "MOM + COOL = SALAD", "Answer": "656 + 9552 = 10208"}
{"Question": "MOM + ROOF = FREE", "Answer": "757 + 3554 = 4311"}
{"Question": "POP + MOON = SENSE", "Answer": "757 + 9553 = 10310"}
{"Question": "MOM + ROOF = FEWER", "Answer": "858 + 9551 = 10409"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOOT = CATCH", "Answer": "858 + 9554 = 10412"}
{"Question": "TEN + MEET = TENT", "Answer": "950 + 8559 = 9509"}
{"Question": "TOE + BOOT = TEEN", "Answer": "562 + 4665 = 5227"}
{"Question": "TOE + ROOT = BEER", "Answer": "562 + 7665 = 8227"}
{"Question": "MOM + COOL = FULLY", "Answer": "565 + 9662 = 10227"}
{"Question": "MOM + DOOR = AGREE", "Answer": "868 + 9665 = 10533"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOOK = DRAMA", "Answer": "575 + 9778 = 10353"}
{"Question": "MOM + SOON = FENCE", "Answer": "676 + 9774 = 10450"}
{"Question": "LEG + FEEL = LOOSE", "Answer": "187 + 9881 = 10068"}
{"Question": "TEN + MEET = NINE", "Answer": "286 + 5882 = 6168"}
{"Question": "MOM + COOK = BASIC", "Answer": "484 + 9885 = 10369"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOOT = THREE", "Answer": "585 + 9881 = 10466"}
{"Question": "MOM + DOOR = TIRED", "Answer": "585 + 9884 = 10469"}
{"Question": "RED + BEER = START", "Answer": "783 + 9887 = 10670"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOOK = CRIME", "Answer": "787 + 9885 = 10672"}
{"Question": "SEA + EAST = TOOTH", "Answer": "297 + 9721 = 10018"}
{"Question": "DNA + NEED = DEAD", "Answer": "980 + 8229 = 9209"}
{"Question": "DNA + NEED = AIDE", "Answer": "845 + 4338 = 5183"}
{"Question": "MOM + ODDS = SOME", "Answer": "616 + 1552 = 2168"}
{"Question": "SEA + EAST = TELL", "Answer": "615 + 1562 = 2177"}
{"Question": "AGE + GEAR = TIRED", "Answer": "695 + 9562 = 10257"}
{"Question": "DNA + NEED = ISSUE", "Answer": "295 + 9772 = 10067"}
{"Question": "AGO + GOAL = ALLY", "Answer": "765 + 6573 = 7338"}
{"Question": "MOM + NONE = OPEN", "Answer": "282 + 7875 = 8157"}
{"Question": "MOM + ODDS = SEED", "Answer": "343 + 4885 = 5228"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALLY = BEGIN", "Answer": "494 + 9882 = 10376"}
{"Question": "POP + NONE = OPEN", "Answer": "191 + 8987 = 9178"}
{"Question": "DAD + NEED = GANG", "Answer": "818 + 5338 = 6156"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAND = ENEMY", "Answer": "838 + 9308 = 10146"}
{"Question": "MOM + FORM = ENEMY", "Answer": "838 + 9348 = 10186"}
{"Question": "TEA + DATA = ESSAY", "Answer": "416 + 9646 = 10062"}
{"Question": "DAD + FEED = AWARE", "Answer": "717 + 9447 = 10164"}
{"Question": "DAD + FEED = BIBLE", "Answer": "737 + 9447 = 10184"}
{"Question": "DAD + FOOD = AGREE", "Answer": "818 + 9448 = 10266"}
{"Question": "MOM + POEM = AWARE", "Answer": "656 + 9526 = 10182"}
{"Question": "DAD + YARD = ARMY", "Answer": "757 + 4527 = 5284"}
{"Question": "EYE + TYPE = PANEL", "Answer": "757 + 9517 = 10274"}
{"Question": "DAD + CARD = PRESS", "Answer": "858 + 9508 = 10366"}
{"Question": "DAD + CARD = FORCE", "Answer": "858 + 9538 = 10396"}
{"Question": "DAD + FEED = ISSUE", "Answer": "383 + 9663 = 10046"}
{"Question": "DAD + FEED = DARE", "Answer": "858 + 7668 = 8526"}
{"Question": "DAD + FEED = CABLE", "Answer": "808 + 9668 = 10476"}
{"Question": "DAD + FEED = ASIDE", "Answer": "818 + 9668 = 10486"}
{"Question": "EYE + TYPE = DIRTY", "Answer": "868 + 9628 = 10496"}
{"Question": "EYE + TYPE = IMPLY", "Answer": "868 + 9658 = 10526"}
{"Question": "DAD + YARD = ALLY", "Answer": "373 + 6743 = 7116"}
{"Question": "DAD + CARD = PRIOR", "Answer": "575 + 9705 = 10280"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAND = SENSE", "Answer": "575 + 9735 = 10310"}
{"Question": "DAD + CARD = THREE", "Answer": "676 + 9746 = 10422"}
{"Question": "MOM + POEM = SCENE", "Answer": "878 + 9768 = 10646"}
{"Question": "DAD + FEED = AIDE", "Answer": "464 + 5884 = 6348"}
{"Question": "EYE + TYPE = PARTY", "Answer": "484 + 9814 = 10298"}
{"Question": "EYE + TYPE = CARRY", "Answer": "484 + 9854 = 10338"}
{"Question": "EYE + TYPE = HONEY", "Answer": "484 + 9864 = 10348"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAND = FENCE", "Answer": "585 + 9845 = 10430"}
{"Question": "SKI + RISK = STIR", "Answer": "348 + 2834 = 3182"}
{"Question": "EYE + ALLY = RURAL", "Answer": "858 + 9335 = 10193"}
{"Question": "TEA + DATE = DEAD", "Answer": "483 + 1348 = 1831"}
{"Question": "EAT + HATE = THEM", "Answer": "843 + 2438 = 3281"}
{"Question": "TOO + DATA = LOAD", "Answer": "511 + 7656 = 8167"}
{"Question": "SEE + ODDS = TEST", "Answer": "722 + 8557 = 9279"}
{"Question": "TOO + DATA = BROAD", "Answer": "522 + 9757 = 10279"}
{"Question": "MOM + ROLL = MERE", "Answer": "565 + 4677 = 5242"}
{"Question": "FEE + ROOF = HERO", "Answer": "511 + 7665 = 8176"}
{"Question": "TEA + BEAT = AWARE", "Answer": "561 + 9615 = 10176"}
{"Question": "OUT + AUTO = TALL", "Answer": "765 + 4657 = 5422"}
{"Question": "TOO + DATA = TOSS", "Answer": "644 + 5767 = 6411"}
{"Question": "DAD + MASS = SLIDE", "Answer": "767 + 9611 = 10378"}
{"Question": "TOO + MEET = BOMB", "Answer": "855 + 2668 = 3523"}
{"Question": "SEE + ODDS = FOOD", "Answer": "344 + 1773 = 2117"}
{"Question": "POP + TOSS = ADAPT", "Answer": "373 + 9766 = 10139"}
{"Question": "TEA + BEAT = ABLE", "Answer": "473 + 2734 = 3207"}
{"Question": "SEE + ODDS = DEAD", "Answer": "522 + 6775 = 7297"}
{"Question": "TOO + MEET = NONE", "Answer": "522 + 8775 = 9297"}
{"Question": "TEA + MEAT = BLAME", "Answer": "572 + 9725 = 10297"}
{"Question": "TOO + DATA = OUGHT", "Answer": "711 + 9676 = 10387"}
{"Question": "DAD + BALL = TRIBE", "Answer": "676 + 9722 = 10398"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOSS = DRAMA", "Answer": "676 + 9788 = 10464"}
{"Question": "EAT + DATE = TIRED", "Answer": "871 + 9718 = 10589"}
{"Question": "TOO + DATA = CROSS", "Answer": "766 + 9878 = 10644"}
{"Question": "TEA + BEAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "183 + 9831 = 10014"}
{"Question": "TOO + DATA = ASSET", "Answer": "877 + 9181 = 10058"}
{"Question": "OWN + SNOW = ODDS", "Answer": "843 + 7384 = 8227"}
{"Question": "FEE + ROOF = EVERY", "Answer": "311 + 9883 = 10194"}
{"Question": "DAD + BALL = CHEEK", "Answer": "383 + 9844 = 10227"}
{"Question": "EYE + ALLY = HOTEL", "Answer": "353 + 9885 = 10238"}
{"Question": "TEA + HEAT = EACH", "Answer": "483 + 7834 = 8317"}
{"Question": "MOM + BOSS = TASTE", "Answer": "484 + 9833 = 10317"}
{"Question": "DAD + TALL = PILOT", "Answer": "585 + 9844 = 10429"}
{"Question": "MOM + POLL = SALES", "Answer": "686 + 9855 = 10541"}
{"Question": "TEA + SEAT = ABUSE", "Answer": "781 + 9817 = 10598"}
{"Question": "DAD + FEEL = APPLE", "Answer": "818 + 9224 = 10042"}
{"Question": "ERA + TRUE = INNER", "Answer": "824 + 9258 = 10082"}
{"Question": "ERA + TRUE = ASSET", "Answer": "821 + 9268 = 10089"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEER = RARE", "Answer": "818 + 4335 = 5153"}
{"Question": "SET + NEWS = AWARE", "Answer": "835 + 9308 = 10143"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEER = AWARE", "Answer": "818 + 9335 = 10153"}
{"Question": "SEA + LAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "358 + 9831 = 10189"}
{"Question": "LEG + DEAL = APPLY", "Answer": "647 + 9416 = 10063"}
{"Question": "ERA + TRUE = UPPER", "Answer": "648 + 9416 = 10064"}
{"Question": "WIN + VIEW = FENCE", "Answer": "842 + 9408 = 10250"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAKE = SKILL", "Answer": "848 + 9407 = 10255"}
{"Question": "DAD + FAIR = RIDE", "Answer": "656 + 2513 = 3169"}
{"Question": "MOM + POET = ENEMY", "Answer": "656 + 9512 = 10168"}
{"Question": "RED + TEAR = APART", "Answer": "653 + 9516 = 10169"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEER = ASIDE", "Answer": "717 + 9558 = 10275"}
{"Question": "EYE + MYTH = HOTEL", "Answer": "757 + 9521 = 10278"}
{"Question": "MOM + CODE = VIDEO", "Answer": "757 + 9528 = 10285"}
{"Question": "DAD + CAMP = TOPIC", "Answer": "757 + 9532 = 10289"}
{"Question": "DAD + RAIL = EXTRA", "Answer": "757 + 9538 = 10295"}
{"Question": "DAD + CAMP = PITCH", "Answer": "757 + 9541 = 10298"}
{"Question": "TWO + LOTS = SLOW", "Answer": "528 + 3854 = 4382"}
{"Question": "MOM + COAL = SALES", "Answer": "858 + 9503 = 10361"}
{"Question": "DAD + BANK = NERVE", "Answer": "858 + 9512 = 10370"}
{"Question": "MOM + NOTE = TREAT", "Answer": "858 + 9513 = 10371"}
{"Question": "MOM + SORT = TERMS", "Answer": "858 + 9531 = 10389"}
{"Question": "DAD + VARY = NERVE", "Answer": "858 + 9532 = 10390"}
{"Question": "DAD + KEEP = SHAKE", "Answer": "838 + 9557 = 10395"}
{"Question": "MOM + SOFT = REFER", "Answer": "858 + 9543 = 10401"}
{"Question": "END + IDEA = AIDE", "Answer": "684 + 1462 = 2146"}
{"Question": "MOM + COAL = ALSO", "Answer": "565 + 2631 = 3196"}
{"Question": "DAD + MEET = TITLE", "Answer": "525 + 9661 = 10186"}
{"Question": "TEA + REST = AWARE", "Answer": "561 + 9635 = 10196"}
{"Question": "DAD + EAST = SLIDE", "Answer": "767 + 9612 = 10379"}
{"Question": "DAD + BASE = SUPER", "Answer": "767 + 9618 = 10385"}
{"Question": "MOM + CORN = FENCE", "Answer": "767 + 9623 = 10390"}
{"Question": "DAD + CAMP = EMPTY", "Answer": "868 + 9604 = 10472"}
{"Question": "EAR + FATE = TIRED", "Answer": "864 + 9618 = 10482"}
{"Question": "MOM + SOFT = TERMS", "Answer": "868 + 9621 = 10489"}
{"Question": "DAD + EARN = OWNER", "Answer": "868 + 9624 = 10492"}
{"Question": "DAD + EARN = HONOR", "Answer": "868 + 9635 = 10503"}
{"Question": "DAD + RATE = ENTER", "Answer": "868 + 9651 = 10519"}
{"Question": "DAD + FAIR = SKILL", "Answer": "868 + 9654 = 10522"}
{"Question": "END + ONCE = CODE", "Answer": "470 + 2734 = 3204"}
{"Question": "DAD + FEEL = AWARE", "Answer": "414 + 9773 = 10187"}
{"Question": "MOM + ALLY = RURAL", "Answer": "424 + 9773 = 10197"}
{"Question": "EYE + ODDS = FOOD", "Answer": "565 + 3772 = 4337"}
{"Question": "TEN + BOOT = TENT", "Answer": "530 + 4775 = 5305"}
{"Question": "MOM + PORT = RATIO", "Answer": "575 + 9712 = 10287"}
{"Question": "DAD + BACK = CLIMB", "Answer": "575 + 9714 = 10289"}
{"Question": "DAD + RACE = EXTRA", "Answer": "676 + 9721 = 10397"}
{"Question": "SEA + ODDS = AHEAD", "Answer": "641 + 9776 = 10417"}
{"Question": "EAT + CARE = ORDER", "Answer": "872 + 9708 = 10580"}
{"Question": "EYE + MYTH = OTHER", "Answer": "878 + 9705 = 10583"}
{"Question": "THE + SHIT = TOOTH", "Answer": "187 + 9831 = 10018"}
{"Question": "YES + ALLY = ESSAY", "Answer": "210 + 9882 = 10092"}
{"Question": "FEW + LEAF = APPLE", "Answer": "286 + 9812 = 10098"}
{"Question": "TAP + ROOT = APART", "Answer": "310 + 9883 = 10193"}
{"Question": "LEG + REAL = AWARE", "Answer": "385 + 9813 = 10198"}
{"Question": "DAD + HAVE = CIVIL", "Answer": "383 + 9824 = 10207"}
{"Question": "DAD + CARE = BREAK", "Answer": "484 + 9802 = 10286"}
{"Question": "DAD + FATE = ENTER", "Answer": "484 + 9831 = 10315"}
{"Question": "MOM + FOUR = TERMS", "Answer": "484 + 9863 = 10347"}
{"Question": "TEA + DEBT = BLADE", "Answer": "583 + 9815 = 10398"}
{"Question": "MOM + HOST = CATCH", "Answer": "585 + 9834 = 10419"}
{"Question": "EYE + DOOR = TIRED", "Answer": "575 + 9884 = 10459"}
{"Question": "DAD + SEEK = ABUSE", "Answer": "616 + 9882 = 10498"}
{"Question": "DAD + GAIN = BEING", "Answer": "686 + 9853 = 10539"}
{"Question": "MOM + NOTE = TENT", "Answer": "787 + 2836 = 3623"}
{"Question": "DAD + SALE = FLESH", "Answer": "787 + 9805 = 10592"}
{"Question": "DAD + PALM = LIMIT", "Answer": "787 + 9816 = 10603"}
{"Question": "POP + MEET = TASTE", "Answer": "737 + 9881 = 10618"}
{"Question": "DAD + FATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "787 + 9861 = 10648"}
{"Question": "DAD + CASE = MUSIC", "Answer": "787 + 9862 = 10649"}
{"Question": "PER + PEER = ERROR", "Answer": "910 + 9110 = 10020"}
{"Question": "TEN + TEEN = ERROR", "Answer": "915 + 9115 = 10030"}
{"Question": "PER + PEER = AWARD", "Answer": "924 + 9224 = 10148"}
{"Question": "TEN + TEEN = AWARE", "Answer": "926 + 9226 = 10152"}
{"Question": "GOD + GOOD = DRAMA", "Answer": "931 + 9331 = 10262"}
{"Question": "GOD + GOOD = FENCE", "Answer": "935 + 9335 = 10270"}
{"Question": "GOD + GOOD = BASIS", "Answer": "936 + 9336 = 10272"}
{"Question": "GOD + GOOD = ASIDE", "Answer": "937 + 9337 = 10274"}
{"Question": "GOD + GOOD = DAILY", "Answer": "941 + 9441 = 10382"}
{"Question": "GOD + GOOD = PIANO", "Answer": "942 + 9442 = 10384"}
{"Question": "PER + PEER = SCOPE", "Answer": "947 + 9447 = 10394"}
{"Question": "PER + PEER = EASE", "Answer": "568 + 5668 = 6236"}
{"Question": "PER + PEER = PASS", "Answer": "172 + 1772 = 1944"}
{"Question": "PER + PEER = EARN", "Answer": "675 + 6775 = 7450"}
{"Question": "PER + PEER = ROLL", "Answer": "283 + 2883 = 3166"}
{"Question": "SON + SOON = KISS", "Answer": "683 + 6883 = 7566"}
{"Question": "POT + POOL = TITLE", "Answer": "921 + 9224 = 10145"}
{"Question": "TEA + TEEN = ADAPT", "Answer": "921 + 9228 = 10149"}
{"Question": "TOP + TOOL = ADAPT", "Answer": "924 + 9225 = 10149"}
{"Question": "HER + HEEL = AWARE", "Answer": "925 + 9227 = 10152"}
{"Question": "BET + BEER = THIRD", "Answer": "931 + 9336 = 10267"}
{"Question": "HER + HEEL = ROUGH", "Answer": "931 + 9338 = 10269"}
{"Question": "ROW + ROOM = MERE", "Answer": "732 + 7338 = 8070"}
{"Question": "COP + COOL = IMPLY", "Answer": "932 + 9336 = 10268"}
{"Question": "FOR + FOOD = NERVE", "Answer": "932 + 9338 = 10270"}
{"Question": "BOX + BOOT = ELITE", "Answer": "934 + 9337 = 10271"}
{"Question": "BOX + BOOM = DRAMA", "Answer": "935 + 9337 = 10272"}
{"Question": "BED + BEER = SCORE", "Answer": "936 + 9337 = 10273"}
{"Question": "BED + BEER = STUDY", "Answer": "937 + 9338 = 10275"}
{"Question": "TOP + TOOL = PIECE", "Answer": "941 + 9442 = 10383"}
{"Question": "DOG + DOOR = GUARD", "Answer": "941 + 9448 = 10389"}
{"Question": "SEA + SEED = BASE", "Answer": "685 + 6883 = 7568"}
{"Question": "RID + RIDE = INNER", "Answer": "914 + 9145 = 10059"}
{"Question": "CEO + CELL = ERROR", "Answer": "916 + 9144 = 10060"}
{"Question": "SEE + SOON = EVENT", "Answer": "911 + 9223 = 10134"}
{"Question": "TEA + TEAM = ADAPT", "Answer": "921 + 9218 = 10139"}
{"Question": "CAR + CARE = ELECT", "Answer": "927 + 9271 = 10198"}
{"Question": "SEE + SOON = AGENT", "Answer": "922 + 9335 = 10257"}
{"Question": "ARM + ARMY = YEAR", "Answer": "834 + 8349 = 9183"}
{"Question": "OFF + ODDS = ELITE", "Answer": "944 + 9337 = 10281"}
{"Question": "OFF + ODDS = THESE", "Answer": "944 + 9338 = 10282"}
{"Question": "FEE + FOOD = STUDY", "Answer": "922 + 9446 = 10368"}
{"Question": "TEN + TEND = DATA", "Answer": "843 + 8439 = 9282"}
{"Question": "SEA + SEAT = TASK", "Answer": "651 + 6517 = 7168"}
{"Question": "TOO + TEEN = GIANT", "Answer": "922 + 9557 = 10479"}
{"Question": "BIT + BITE = ORDER", "Answer": "952 + 9528 = 10480"}
{"Question": "FEE + FOOD = BASIS", "Answer": "922 + 9663 = 10585"}
{"Question": "TAP + TAPE = PHOTO", "Answer": "981 + 9816 = 10797"}
{"Question": "TOO + TEEN = NOSE", "Answer": "433 + 4885 = 5318"}
{"Question": "TOO + TEEN = NINE", "Answer": "255 + 2883 = 3138"}
{"Question": "USE + USER = SURE", "Answer": "891 + 8910 = 9801"}
{"Question": "SUE + SURE = UPPER", "Answer": "918 + 9168 = 10086"}
{"Question": "LET + LEFT = TITLE", "Answer": "921 + 9271 = 10192"}
{"Question": "HER + HEAR = APART", "Answer": "923 + 9213 = 10136"}
{"Question": "BED + BEND = AGAIN", "Answer": "923 + 9263 = 10186"}
{"Question": "BET + BEAT = AWARE", "Answer": "926 + 9216 = 10142"}
{"Question": "SUE + SURE = PAPER", "Answer": "927 + 9247 = 10174"}
{"Question": "FOR + FOUR = APART", "Answer": "928 + 9258 = 10186"}
{"Question": "POT + POET = THEME", "Answer": "931 + 9321 = 10252"}
{"Question": "CAP + CAMP = PIECE", "Answer": "931 + 9361 = 10292"}
{"Question": "BET + BELT = UNTIL", "Answer": "932 + 9342 = 10274"}
{"Question": "SHE + SHOE = ORDER", "Answer": "935 + 9315 = 10250"}
{"Question": "PER + POOR = THERE", "Answer": "926 + 9336 = 10262"}
{"Question": "BET + BEAT = CLASS", "Answer": "938 + 9328 = 10266"}
{"Question": "BET + BEAT = THANK", "Answer": "941 + 9431 = 10372"}
{"Question": "SUE + SURE = ORDER", "Answer": "945 + 9405 = 10350"}
{"Question": "GOD + GOLD = LEAVE", "Answer": "945 + 9415 = 10360"}
{"Question": "BED + BEND = ASIDE", "Answer": "947 + 9427 = 10374"}
{"Question": "FAR + FAIR = SHIRT", "Answer": "948 + 9438 = 10386"}
{"Question": "BAD + BAND = DEPTH", "Answer": "951 + 9531 = 10482"}
{"Question": "TIE + TIRE = EARTH", "Answer": "951 + 9541 = 10492"}
{"Question": "MAN + MOON = DRAMA", "Answer": "942 + 9552 = 10494"}
{"Question": "FAR + FAIR = KNIFE", "Answer": "953 + 9543 = 10496"}
{"Question": "BUY + BURY = ARAB", "Answer": "658 + 6518 = 7176"}
{"Question": "BAD + BAND = EXTRA", "Answer": "963 + 9623 = 10586"}
{"Question": "RED + READ = DATA", "Answer": "465 + 4605 = 5070"}
{"Question": "BET + BEAT = AUTO", "Answer": "765 + 7685 = 8450"}
{"Question": "PER + POOR = NERVE", "Answer": "905 + 9665 = 10570"}
{"Question": "RED + READ = ASIDE", "Answer": "968 + 9618 = 10586"}
{"Question": "LAY + LADY = YIELD", "Answer": "971 + 9721 = 10692"}
{"Question": "BAD + BAND = INDEX", "Answer": "976 + 9706 = 10682"}
{"Question": "SET + SEAT = ABUSE", "Answer": "984 + 9814 = 10798"}
{"Question": "EAT + EAST = STEP", "Answer": "685 + 6875 = 7560"}
{"Question": "BUY + BURY = TRIBE", "Answer": "986 + 9806 = 10792"}
{"Question": "SUE + SURE = FRESH", "Answer": "987 + 9807 = 10794"}
{"Question": "SUE + SURE = USER", "Answer": "891 + 8921 = 9812"}
{"Question": "HEY + HERO = ERROR", "Answer": "918 + 9102 = 10020"}
{"Question": "THE + THAN = EVENT", "Answer": "921 + 9268 = 10189"}
{"Question": "NOD + NOTE = EVENT", "Answer": "926 + 9271 = 10197"}
{"Question": "TEN + TEAR = APART", "Answer": "926 + 9213 = 10139"}
{"Question": "HER + HEAD = AWARE", "Answer": "924 + 9218 = 10142"}
{"Question": "SUN + SUIT = ELITE", "Answer": "935 + 9326 = 10261"}
{"Question": "RUB + RUSH = BASIS", "Answer": "941 + 9432 = 10373"}
{"Question": "DUE + DUTY = TREAT", "Answer": "943 + 9418 = 10361"}
{"Question": "TEN + TEAM = DRAMA", "Answer": "945 + 9438 = 10383"}
{"Question": "TIE + TOOL = ELITE", "Answer": "941 + 9550 = 10491"}
{"Question": "MAD + MEET = DRAMA", "Answer": "941 + 9553 = 10494"}
{"Question": "EAT + EARN = THREE", "Answer": "951 + 9548 = 10499"}
{"Question": "BOX + BOAT = ELITE", "Answer": "953 + 9528 = 10481"}
{"Question": "RUB + RULE = LABEL", "Answer": "954 + 9517 = 10471"}
{"Question": "MAN + MAIL = FENCE", "Answer": "954 + 9526 = 10480"}
{"Question": "CAN + CARE = OWNER", "Answer": "954 + 9528 = 10482"}
{"Question": "AIM + AIDE = TREAT", "Answer": "957 + 9534 = 10491"}
{"Question": "ART + ARMY = METAL", "Answer": "976 + 9718 = 10694"}
{"Question": "LOT + LOSE = SHELL", "Answer": "982 + 9817 = 10799"}
{"Question": "VIA + VIEW = LEAVE", "Answer": "987 + 9803 = 10790"}
{"Question": "HER + DEER = HARD", "Answer": "924 + 8224 = 9148"}
{"Question": "BET + MEET = DRAMA", "Answer": "846 + 9446 = 10292"}
{"Question": "BED + SEED = LOOSE", "Answer": "647 + 9447 = 10094"}
{"Question": "BED + FEED = KNIFE", "Answer": "847 + 9447 = 10294"}
{"Question": "POT + ROOT = TRIP", "Answer": "653 + 2553 = 3206"}
{"Question": "LET + MEET = CIVIL", "Answer": "653 + 9553 = 10206"}
{"Question": "HER + BEER = TOOTH", "Answer": "457 + 9557 = 10014"}
{"Question": "NET + MEET = ASIAN", "Answer": "658 + 9558 = 10216"}
{"Question": "FOR + DOOR = FREE", "Answer": "461 + 3661 = 4122"}
{"Question": "FLY + ALLY = MASS", "Answer": "761 + 4661 = 5422"}
{"Question": "BED + FEED = BALL", "Answer": "861 + 7661 = 8522"}
{"Question": "HOT + BOOT = FIFTH", "Answer": "462 + 9662 = 10124"}
{"Question": "FLY + ALLY = FEEL", "Answer": "563 + 4663 = 5226"}
{"Question": "GET + MEET = GENE", "Answer": "963 + 8663 = 9626"}
{"Question": "LET + MEET = APPLE", "Answer": "368 + 9668 = 10036"}
{"Question": "HOT + ROOT = TREE", "Answer": "372 + 1772 = 2144"}
{"Question": "FLY + ALLY = PROOF", "Answer": "673 + 9773 = 10446"}
{"Question": "BED + SEED = ODDS", "Answer": "674 + 8774 = 9448"}
{"Question": "NOT + ROOT = TURN", "Answer": "276 + 5776 = 6052"}
{"Question": "BED + NEED = DENY", "Answer": "976 + 5776 = 6752"}
{"Question": "LET + MEET = TOTAL", "Answer": "281 + 9881 = 10162"}
{"Question": "BED + FEED = DRAMA", "Answer": "381 + 9881 = 10262"}
{"Question": "BED + FEED = DOUBT", "Answer": "681 + 9881 = 10562"}
{"Question": "LET + MEET = BALL", "Answer": "683 + 1883 = 2566"}
{"Question": "LET + MEET = TALL", "Answer": "683 + 2883 = 3566"}
{"Question": "FOR + DOOR = AGREE", "Answer": "483 + 9883 = 10366"}
{"Question": "FLY + ALLY = STUFF", "Answer": "683 + 9883 = 10566"}
{"Question": "BED + FEED = EDGE", "Answer": "584 + 7884 = 8468"}
{"Question": "LET + MEET = LOOSE", "Answer": "184 + 9884 = 10068"}
{"Question": "BED + FEED = JUDGE", "Answer": "584 + 9884 = 10468"}
{"Question": "BED + FEED = MAYBE", "Answer": "684 + 9884 = 10568"}
{"Question": "RED + FEED = START", "Answer": "785 + 9885 = 10670"}
{"Question": "GOD + FOOD = EDGE", "Answer": "786 + 1886 = 2672"}
{"Question": "FLY + ALLY = LEAF", "Answer": "286 + 7886 = 8172"}
{"Question": "GOD + FOOD = JUDGE", "Answer": "786 + 9886 = 10672"}
{"Question": "BED + PEER = AWARE", "Answer": "836 + 9337 = 10173"}
{"Question": "CEO + NEED = ONCE", "Answer": "843 + 2441 = 3284"}
{"Question": "CEO + DEEP = CODE", "Answer": "943 + 8441 = 9384"}
{"Question": "SEA + DEER = AWARD", "Answer": "741 + 9448 = 10189"}
{"Question": "DOG + LOOK = GLAD", "Answer": "742 + 1445 = 2187"}
{"Question": "SEA + DEEP = PASS", "Answer": "842 + 5446 = 6288"}
{"Question": "SEA + BEER = CLASS", "Answer": "842 + 9446 = 10288"}
{"Question": "BET + SEED = ODDS", "Answer": "561 + 3662 = 4223"}
{"Question": "BED + PEER = DIRTY", "Answer": "761 + 9664 = 10425"}
{"Question": "DOG + BOOK = GRAND", "Answer": "861 + 9667 = 10528"}
{"Question": "CEO + KEEP = COOK", "Answer": "674 + 5771 = 6445"}
{"Question": "BED + TEEN = DOUBT", "Answer": "471 + 9778 = 10249"}
{"Question": "LOT + DOOR = THREE", "Answer": "571 + 9773 = 10344"}
{"Question": "DOG + MOON = GRAND", "Answer": "571 + 9774 = 10345"}
{"Question": "YOU + ROOT = TRUE", "Answer": "374 + 1772 = 2146"}
{"Question": "TOE + BOOM = MEET", "Answer": "674 + 1772 = 2446"}
{"Question": "CEO + PEER = ROPE", "Answer": "281 + 6887 = 7168"}
{"Question": "COP + BOOK = PIECE", "Answer": "681 + 9884 = 10565"}
{"Question": "YES + BEER = SORRY", "Answer": "781 + 9886 = 10667"}
{"Question": "KEY + SEED = DESK", "Answer": "982 + 6887 = 7869"}
{"Question": "CEO + TEEN = ONCE", "Answer": "683 + 2885 = 3568"}
{"Question": "CEO + FEED = ODDS", "Answer": "783 + 2886 = 3669"}
{"Question": "DOG + COOL = GOLD", "Answer": "983 + 2886 = 3869"}
{"Question": "BED + FEEL = JUDGE", "Answer": "483 + 9885 = 10368"}
{"Question": "CEO + TEEN = FRONT", "Answer": "483 + 9886 = 10369"}
{"Question": "COP + MOON = FENCE", "Answer": "784 + 9886 = 10670"}
{"Question": "ALL + FEEL = LOOSE", "Answer": "811 + 9221 = 10032"}
{"Question": "ADD + LOAD = ERROR", "Answer": "255 + 9825 = 10080"}
{"Question": "ALL + TOOL = AUTO", "Answer": "722 + 6442 = 7164"}
{"Question": "SEE + BASE = ARAB", "Answer": "433 + 6743 = 7176"}
{"Question": "FEE + LIFE = AGAIN", "Answer": "433 + 9743 = 10176"}
{"Question": "SEE + POSE = ADAPT", "Answer": "544 + 9654 = 10198"}
{"Question": "ADD + LEAD = RIFLE", "Answer": "544 + 9854 = 10398"}
{"Question": "YES + LESS = BIBLE", "Answer": "563 + 9633 = 10196"}
{"Question": "FEE + LIFE = SHELF", "Answer": "633 + 9763 = 10396"}
{"Question": "ADD + ROAD = EXTRA", "Answer": "633 + 9863 = 10496"}
{"Question": "ALL + DEAL = IDEA", "Answer": "688 + 2568 = 3256"}
{"Question": "TOO + INTO = AGENT", "Answer": "688 + 9568 = 10256"}
{"Question": "FEE + LIFE = APPLY", "Answer": "722 + 9372 = 10094"}
{"Question": "TOO + INTO = AGAIN", "Answer": "722 + 9472 = 10194"}
{"Question": "ADD + GLAD = JUDGE", "Answer": "722 + 9572 = 10294"}
{"Question": "ALL + DEAL = ODDS", "Answer": "744 + 1374 = 2118"}
{"Question": "ADD + GLAD = SHELL", "Answer": "788 + 9678 = 10466"}
{"Question": "SEE + CASE = ELECT", "Answer": "811 + 9381 = 10192"}
{"Question": "ADD + FEED = APPLE", "Answer": "144 + 9884 = 10028"}
{"Question": "TOO + INTO = EVENT", "Answer": "844 + 9284 = 10128"}
{"Question": "FEE + LIFE = PROOF", "Answer": "844 + 9384 = 10228"}
{"Question": "ADD + HEAD = ERROR", "Answer": "855 + 9185 = 10040"}
{"Question": "ALL + MEAL = ORDER", "Answer": "855 + 9485 = 10340"}
{"Question": "SEE + NOSE = SOON", "Answer": "944 + 8394 = 9338"}
{"Question": "ADD + HEAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "388 + 9631 = 10019"}
{"Question": "AIR + FIRE = AREA", "Answer": "842 + 7426 = 8268"}
{"Question": "ALL + GRAB = BELOW", "Answer": "422 + 9841 = 10263"}
{"Question": "EGG + COOL = ANGLE", "Answer": "822 + 9446 = 10268"}
{"Question": "ADD + NEAR = EARN", "Answer": "477 + 8941 = 9418"}
{"Question": "CRY + TREE = ELECT", "Answer": "658 + 9511 = 10169"}
{"Question": "ADD + TEAM = DOUBT", "Answer": "511 + 9758 = 10269"}
{"Question": "ILL + TRIP = ADAPT", "Answer": "522 + 9657 = 10179"}
{"Question": "ADD + THAN = ELITE", "Answer": "533 + 9758 = 10291"}
{"Question": "ADD + LEAF = MODEL", "Answer": "533 + 9856 = 10389"}
{"Question": "BAR + VARY = NERVE", "Answer": "853 + 9537 = 10390"}
{"Question": "TOO + CITE = ELECT", "Answer": "544 + 9651 = 10195"}
{"Question": "OFF + BLOW = REFER", "Answer": "544 + 9857 = 10401"}
{"Question": "ADD + NEAR = DOZEN", "Answer": "611 + 9768 = 10379"}
{"Question": "ADD + BEAR = AREA", "Answer": "622 + 5864 = 6486"}
{"Question": "ADD + COAL = FENCE", "Answer": "622 + 9768 = 10390"}
{"Question": "EGG + FUEL = VALUE", "Answer": "622 + 9864 = 10486"}
{"Question": "EGG + OPEN = PINE", "Answer": "655 + 2361 = 3016"}
{"Question": "SEA + DEAL = SALE", "Answer": "865 + 7651 = 8516"}
{"Question": "EGG + DIET = TASTE", "Answer": "655 + 9761 = 10416"}
{"Question": "YES + BEST = TASTE", "Answer": "865 + 9651 = 10516"}
{"Question": "SEE + LAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "688 + 9461 = 10149"}
{"Question": "EGG + DIET = BASIS", "Answer": "688 + 9564 = 10252"}
{"Question": "EGG + IDEA = AIDE", "Answer": "711 + 5876 = 6587"}
{"Question": "TOO + RATE = OFFER", "Answer": "711 + 9378 = 10089"}
{"Question": "SEA + TEAR = APART", "Answer": "471 + 9718 = 10189"}
{"Question": "TOO + CITY = ELECT", "Answer": "722 + 9475 = 10197"}
{"Question": "ALL + ROAD = EXTRA", "Answer": "722 + 9675 = 10397"}
{"Question": "EGG + ITEM = BASIS", "Answer": "722 + 9873 = 10595"}
{"Question": "TOO + SITE = CHEST", "Answer": "722 + 9875 = 10597"}
{"Question": "EAT + IDEA = DATA", "Answer": "730 + 4573 = 5303"}
{"Question": "BIT + CITE = ENTER", "Answer": "674 + 9741 = 10415"}
{"Question": "EGG + OPEN = NONE", "Answer": "755 + 1372 = 2127"}
{"Question": "CAT + RATE = AREA", "Answer": "875 + 6752 = 7627"}
{"Question": "SEE + DISH = ODDS", "Answer": "766 + 3571 = 4337"}
{"Question": "EGG + IDEA = ANGLE", "Answer": "766 + 9871 = 10637"}
{"Question": "ADD + BEAN = JUDGE", "Answer": "766 + 9872 = 10638"}
{"Question": "AID + RIDE = UNDER", "Answer": "876 + 9763 = 10639"}
{"Question": "ADD + LEAN = NOVEL", "Answer": "788 + 9571 = 10359"}
{"Question": "ALL + SEED = LOOSE", "Answer": "211 + 9887 = 10098"}
{"Question": "TEA + PEAK = ADAPT", "Answer": "381 + 9812 = 10193"}
{"Question": "SEA + READ = AWARE", "Answer": "381 + 9817 = 10198"}
{"Question": "THE + CHEF = TOOTH", "Answer": "183 + 9835 = 10018"}
{"Question": "TEA + HEAD = TOOTH", "Answer": "183 + 9836 = 10019"}
{"Question": "DNA + KNEE = AHEAD", "Answer": "481 + 9833 = 10314"}
{"Question": "TOO + BITE = AHEAD", "Answer": "833 + 9584 = 10417"}
{"Question": "ADD + BEAN = FUNNY", "Answer": "844 + 9382 = 10226"}
{"Question": "ADD + FLAG = JUDGE", "Answer": "844 + 9582 = 10426"}
{"Question": "SEA + BEAR = RARE", "Answer": "685 + 2853 = 3538"}
{"Question": "BAR + CARE = AREA", "Answer": "685 + 7853 = 8538"}
{"Question": "TOO + DATE = ASSET", "Answer": "855 + 9183 = 10038"}
{"Question": "EGG + FUEL = ANGLE", "Answer": "855 + 9683 = 10538"}
{"Question": "EGG + DIET = ISSUE", "Answer": "866 + 9182 = 10048"}
{"Question": "ADD + GRAB = EXTRA", "Answer": "866 + 9482 = 10348"}
{"Question": "ALL + DEAR = TIRED", "Answer": "866 + 9483 = 10349"}
{"Question": "FEE + GIFT = PROOF", "Answer": "866 + 9582 = 10448"}
{"Question": "ADD + BOAT = MEDIA", "Answer": "866 + 9782 = 10648"}
{"Question": "RUB + TUBE = LABEL", "Answer": "786 + 9865 = 10651"}
{"Question": "EGG + STEP = PLATE", "Answer": "877 + 9581 = 10458"}
{"Question": "ACT + COAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "392 + 9732 = 10124"}
{"Question": "THE + HATE = TENT", "Answer": "432 + 3842 = 4274"}
{"Question": "AND + NEED = ISSUE", "Answer": "592 + 9442 = 10034"}
{"Question": "LAY + BABY = YELL", "Answer": "643 + 2423 = 3066"}
{"Question": "SAY + ALLY = LESS", "Answer": "839 + 3449 = 4288"}
{"Question": "SET + EAST = SEAT", "Answer": "540 + 4950 = 5490"}
{"Question": "THE + HATE = ESSAY", "Answer": "591 + 9451 = 10042"}
{"Question": "SET + EAST = DEAD", "Answer": "532 + 3852 = 4384"}
{"Question": "SAY + ALLY = MASS", "Answer": "613 + 1553 = 2166"}
{"Question": "ARM + ROOM = ESSAY", "Answer": "493 + 9553 = 10046"}
{"Question": "DIE + NINE = SPEED", "Answer": "854 + 9594 = 10448"}
{"Question": "THE + HATE = TEEN", "Answer": "651 + 5461 = 6112"}
{"Question": "TIE + NINE = ADAPT", "Answer": "462 + 9692 = 10154"}
{"Question": "AND + NEED = AIDE", "Answer": "873 + 7663 = 8536"}
{"Question": "DAY + ALLY = YARD", "Answer": "412 + 1772 = 2184"}
{"Question": "MAY + ARMY = BUYER", "Answer": "792 + 9472 = 10264"}
{"Question": "SAY + ALLY = CROSS", "Answer": "693 + 9773 = 10466"}
{"Question": "TIE + NINE = ELECT", "Answer": "281 + 9891 = 10172"}
{"Question": "ITS + THIS = LIST", "Answer": "842 + 4982 = 5824"}
{"Question": "ARM + ROOM = BOMB", "Answer": "953 + 5883 = 6836"}
{"Question": "THE + HATE = YEAH", "Answer": "863 + 6483 = 7346"}
{"Question": "AND + NEED = APPLE", "Answer": "194 + 9884 = 10078"}
{"Question": "LAY + BABY = ALLY", "Answer": "790 + 8980 = 9770"}
{"Question": "USE + SHUT = TOOTH", "Answer": "296 + 9721 = 10017"}
{"Question": "ARM + REAL = BIBLE", "Answer": "395 + 9732 = 10127"}
{"Question": "ACT + COAL = ONTO", "Answer": "572 + 7856 = 8428"}
{"Question": "AND + NEAR = SCORE", "Answer": "692 + 9765 = 10457"}
{"Question": "SIT + PIPE = STEP", "Answer": "573 + 4741 = 5314"}
{"Question": "DRY + RIDE = DEER", "Answer": "872 + 7685 = 8557"}
{"Question": "CRY + RICE = INNER", "Answer": "892 + 9187 = 10079"}
{"Question": "OUT + UPON = ONTO", "Answer": "875 + 7483 = 8358"}
{"Question": "BET + DEBT = BITE", "Answer": "842 + 7482 = 8324"}
{"Question": "DIE + RIDE = AHEAD", "Answer": "472 + 9742 = 10214"}
{"Question": "SET + BEST = ABLE", "Answer": "463 + 1643 = 2106"}
{"Question": "SAY + EASY = ABLE", "Answer": "473 + 6743 = 7216"}
{"Question": "TOE + NOTE = THEN", "Answer": "572 + 4752 = 5324"}
{"Question": "TOE + VOTE = OVEN", "Answer": "853 + 4583 = 5436"}
{"Question": "DIE + AIDE = IDEA", "Answer": "594 + 8954 = 9548"}
{"Question": "CAT + FACT = EXTRA", "Answer": "584 + 9854 = 10438"}
{"Question": "DIE + SIDE = USED", "Answer": "673 + 4763 = 5436"}
{"Question": "BET + DEBT = EDGE", "Answer": "863 + 5683 = 6546"}
{"Question": "NOD + BOND = ODDS", "Answer": "685 + 7865 = 8550"}
{"Question": "WET + NEWS = TASTE", "Answer": "831 + 9382 = 10213"}
{"Question": "LEG + BELT = EDGE", "Answer": "482 + 7846 = 8328"}
{"Question": "TAX + DATE = TEXT", "Answer": "572 + 4753 = 5325"}
{"Question": "LET + BEST = APPLE", "Answer": "826 + 9256 = 10082"}
{"Question": "ANY + ONLY = COOL", "Answer": "734 + 1384 = 2118"}
{"Question": "HOT + SOFT = FIFTH", "Answer": "834 + 9314 = 10148"}
{"Question": "HER + DOOR = HERE", "Answer": "926 + 8336 = 9262"}
{"Question": "DIE + FIRE = PAPER", "Answer": "836 + 9326 = 10162"}
{"Question": "BED + HEAD = DRAMA", "Answer": "841 + 9421 = 10262"}
{"Question": "GOD + WORD = RADIO", "Answer": "842 + 9412 = 10254"}
{"Question": "THE + SHOE = FLESH", "Answer": "842 + 9452 = 10294"}
{"Question": "DAY + EASY = FEED", "Answer": "643 + 1473 = 2116"}
{"Question": "SET + COST = ERROR", "Answer": "415 + 9645 = 10060"}
{"Question": "LIE + FIRE = ORDER", "Answer": "845 + 9405 = 10250"}
{"Question": "LAY + RELY = AREA", "Answer": "426 + 1746 = 2172"}
{"Question": "TIE + AIDE = DATA", "Answer": "846 + 2436 = 3282"}
{"Question": "ITS + ODDS = THESE", "Answer": "816 + 9446 = 10262"}
{"Question": "ANY + ONLY = LOAN", "Answer": "847 + 2437 = 3284"}
{"Question": "LET + BEAT = APPLE", "Answer": "647 + 9417 = 10064"}
{"Question": "ARM + FROM = COVER", "Answer": "847 + 9407 = 10254"}
{"Question": "BED + LEAD = BALL", "Answer": "748 + 6418 = 7166"}
{"Question": "EAT + CAST = ISSUE", "Answer": "648 + 9408 = 10056"}
{"Question": "LAY + EASY = SELL", "Answer": "849 + 2439 = 3288"}
{"Question": "SIT + DIET = THESE", "Answer": "751 + 9521 = 10272"}
{"Question": "AID + WILD = DELAY", "Answer": "851 + 9531 = 10382"}
{"Question": "LIE + RIDE = AWARD", "Answer": "652 + 9542 = 10194"}
{"Question": "BAN + EARN = OWNER", "Answer": "752 + 9542 = 10294"}
{"Question": "AID + WIND = BROWN", "Answer": "852 + 9542 = 10394"}
{"Question": "EAT + PART = TREE", "Answer": "653 + 2513 = 3166"}
{"Question": "AID + BIRD = ARAB", "Answer": "753 + 6523 = 7276"}
{"Question": "DIE + BIKE = ARMED", "Answer": "653 + 9583 = 10236"}
{"Question": "DIE + RISE = SHELL", "Answer": "853 + 9513 = 10366"}
{"Question": "BAG + HANG = EIGHT", "Answer": "853 + 9543 = 10396"}
{"Question": "CRY + ARMY = MUSIC", "Answer": "854 + 9514 = 10368"}
{"Question": "FLY + PLAY = STAFF", "Answer": "854 + 9534 = 10388"}
{"Question": "DIE + BIKE = AHEAD", "Answer": "854 + 9564 = 10418"}
{"Question": "PIE + HIDE = ADAPT", "Answer": "657 + 9507 = 10164"}
{"Question": "AID + BIND = ENJOY", "Answer": "857 + 9507 = 10364"}
{"Question": "BAN + EARN = ROUND", "Answer": "857 + 9517 = 10374"}
{"Question": "TIE + DATE = IDEA", "Answer": "528 + 1658 = 2186"}
{"Question": "HER + DEAR = HARD", "Answer": "758 + 6528 = 7286"}
{"Question": "AID + BIRD = CROSS", "Answer": "758 + 9508 = 10266"}
{"Question": "AIM + FIRM = TERMS", "Answer": "758 + 9528 = 10286"}
{"Question": "BAN + LAWN = NEWLY", "Answer": "761 + 9631 = 10392"}
{"Question": "AIM + FILM = METAL", "Answer": "861 + 9621 = 10482"}
{"Question": "LAY + EASY = YELL", "Answer": "462 + 1682 = 2144"}
{"Question": "DUE + TUBE = BASIS", "Answer": "862 + 9612 = 10474"}
{"Question": "EAR + FAIR = AREA", "Answer": "763 + 5613 = 6376"}
{"Question": "HER + BEAR = HERE", "Answer": "963 + 8673 = 9636"}
{"Question": "LIE + MALE = IDEAL", "Answer": "613 + 9763 = 10376"}
{"Question": "EAR + FAIR = THREE", "Answer": "864 + 9624 = 10488"}
{"Question": "TWO + AUTO = ERROR", "Answer": "685 + 9365 = 10050"}
{"Question": "EAT + PART = ORDER", "Answer": "765 + 9605 = 10370"}
{"Question": "CAN + LAWN = WHICH", "Answer": "865 + 9615 = 10480"}
{"Question": "TIE + RISE = ASSET", "Answer": "467 + 9607 = 10074"}
{"Question": "YES + NEWS = AWARE", "Answer": "568 + 9608 = 10176"}
{"Question": "HER + BEAR = AWARE", "Answer": "568 + 9618 = 10186"}
{"Question": "ANY + ONLY = CLEAN", "Answer": "768 + 9608 = 10376"}
{"Question": "BED + HEAD = ASIDE", "Answer": "768 + 9618 = 10386"}
{"Question": "BAN + RAIN = EXTRA", "Answer": "768 + 9628 = 10396"}
{"Question": "DIE + LIFE = FLEE", "Answer": "470 + 2730 = 3200"}
{"Question": "TIE + FIRE = TREE", "Answer": "570 + 4730 = 5300"}
{"Question": "HAT + CAST = TOOTH", "Answer": "271 + 9741 = 10012"}
{"Question": "DIE + CITE = ELECT", "Answer": "471 + 9721 = 10192"}
{"Question": "SET + MOST = THEME", "Answer": "721 + 9571 = 10292"}
{"Question": "RUN + TEEN = HONOR", "Answer": "432 + 9772 = 10204"}
{"Question": "DIE + BIKE = SPEED", "Answer": "472 + 9752 = 10224"}
{"Question": "DIE + WIPE = DEEP", "Answer": "573 + 4763 = 5336"}
{"Question": "BIT + DIET = BITE", "Answer": "973 + 8763 = 9736"}
{"Question": "AID + BIRD = UNDER", "Answer": "674 + 9784 = 10458"}
{"Question": "LAY + EASY = SKILL", "Answer": "874 + 9714 = 10588"}
{"Question": "BET + MEAT = CLIMB", "Answer": "874 + 9724 = 10598"}
{"Question": "OLD + GLAD = ERROR", "Answer": "275 + 9745 = 10020"}
{"Question": "YES + ODDS = ERROR", "Answer": "315 + 9775 = 10090"}
{"Question": "BOY + COPY = PEACE", "Answer": "675 + 9715 = 10390"}
{"Question": "AID + BIRD = CREAM", "Answer": "876 + 9706 = 10582"}
{"Question": "DIE + LIFE = OFFER", "Answer": "378 + 9708 = 10086"}
{"Question": "DIE + FIRE = ARMED", "Answer": "678 + 9708 = 10386"}
{"Question": "TAP + CAMP = PHOTO", "Answer": "381 + 9851 = 10232"}
{"Question": "BIT + DIRT = THREE", "Answer": "581 + 9841 = 10422"}
{"Question": "YET + ROOT = ENTRY", "Answer": "412 + 9882 = 10294"}
{"Question": "LIP + HELP = PIPE", "Answer": "853 + 2683 = 3536"}
{"Question": "BAN + EARN = BEER", "Answer": "583 + 4863 = 5446"}
{"Question": "EAR + DOOR = AREA", "Answer": "463 + 5883 = 6346"}
{"Question": "EAT + PANT = OFTEN", "Answer": "483 + 9863 = 10346"}
{"Question": "BAG + HANG = NIGHT", "Answer": "583 + 9813 = 10396"}
{"Question": "DIE + BIKE = NAKED", "Answer": "683 + 9853 = 10536"}
{"Question": "THE + DATE = ASSET", "Answer": "864 + 9184 = 10048"}
{"Question": "BED + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "284 + 9814 = 10098"}
{"Question": "BED + READ = AWARE", "Answer": "384 + 9814 = 10198"}
{"Question": "YES + NEWS = TASTE", "Answer": "584 + 9834 = 10418"}
{"Question": "DIE + FADE = BREAD", "Answer": "874 + 9584 = 10458"}
{"Question": "LIE + ABLE = IDEAL", "Answer": "814 + 9684 = 10498"}
{"Question": "BED + HEAD = FLAME", "Answer": "684 + 9854 = 10538"}
{"Question": "MRS + ODDS = ERROR", "Answer": "205 + 9885 = 10090"}
{"Question": "CAN + GAIN = FENCE", "Answer": "685 + 9875 = 10560"}
{"Question": "LIE + AIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "785 + 9865 = 10650"}
{"Question": "THE + RATE = AREA", "Answer": "876 + 1286 = 2162"}
{"Question": "LIE + AIDE = DEAD", "Answer": "786 + 1826 = 2612"}
{"Question": "TOE + SOME = MESS", "Answer": "786 + 2836 = 3622"}
{"Question": "NOD + SEND = LOOSE", "Answer": "806 + 9286 = 10092"}
{"Question": "NOD + SAND = LOOSE", "Answer": "807 + 9287 = 10094"}
{"Question": "DIE + WIRE = CROWD", "Answer": "487 + 9807 = 10294"}
{"Question": "TOE + HOLE = LIMIT", "Answer": "487 + 9817 = 10304"}
{"Question": "TOE + COAL = ASSET", "Answer": "823 + 9215 = 10038"}
{"Question": "YES + BELT = LOOSE", "Answer": "735 + 9318 = 10053"}
{"Question": "DNA + KNOW = AVOID", "Answer": "841 + 9427 = 10268"}
{"Question": "BAG + HATE = FIGHT", "Answer": "842 + 9453 = 10295"}
{"Question": "NOT + HOLE = THEN", "Answer": "843 + 2415 = 3258"}
{"Question": "TEN + HEAD = DATA", "Answer": "951 + 2543 = 3494"}
{"Question": "CAP + HARD = PORCH", "Answer": "751 + 9528 = 10279"}
{"Question": "VIA + BIKE = AHEAD", "Answer": "751 + 9563 = 10314"}
{"Question": "CUP + FUEL = PIECE", "Answer": "851 + 9532 = 10383"}
{"Question": "BIG + SITE = GUEST", "Answer": "851 + 9543 = 10394"}
{"Question": "DNA + INTO = AHEAD", "Answer": "851 + 9567 = 10418"}
{"Question": "VIA + FILM = LEAVE", "Answer": "752 + 9518 = 10270"}
{"Question": "BAN + CAMP = FENCE", "Answer": "752 + 9538 = 10290"}
{"Question": "BAR + DATE = TIRED", "Answer": "853 + 9516 = 10369"}
{"Question": "GOD + HUGE = ORDER", "Answer": "513 + 9857 = 10370"}
{"Question": "BED + MEAL = DRAMA", "Answer": "761 + 9632 = 10393"}
{"Question": "WHY + SHOE = ORDER", "Answer": "762 + 9618 = 10380"}
{"Question": "JOB + HOLE = LABEL", "Answer": "763 + 9618 = 10381"}
{"Question": "AID + BITE = TREAT", "Answer": "867 + 9614 = 10481"}
{"Question": "AIM + DIRT = METER", "Answer": "471 + 9732 = 10203"}
{"Question": "ETC + STAR = CHASE", "Answer": "571 + 9724 = 10295"}
{"Question": "WAR + NEWS = STATE", "Answer": "734 + 9571 = 10305"}
{"Question": "VIA + DIET = AHEAD", "Answer": "671 + 9748 = 10419"}
{"Question": "AID + FIRE = ORDER", "Answer": "572 + 9708 = 10280"}
{"Question": "BAR + VAST = SERVE", "Answer": "572 + 9718 = 10290"}
{"Question": "ETC + STIR = AGREE", "Answer": "572 + 9783 = 10355"}
{"Question": "AND + ONCE = CLEAN", "Answer": "872 + 9715 = 10587"}
{"Question": "AID + NICE = CLEAN", "Answer": "874 + 9715 = 10589"}
{"Question": "RAW + SAFE = OFFER", "Answer": "375 + 9708 = 10083"}
{"Question": "DNA + UNIT = ASIAN", "Answer": "481 + 9837 = 10318"}
{"Question": "AIR + VIEW = NERVE", "Answer": "583 + 9807 = 10390"}
{"Question": "AID + BIKE = SPEAK", "Answer": "583 + 9874 = 10457"}
{"Question": "CEO + BEAR = KNOCK", "Answer": "584 + 9867 = 10451"}
{"Question": "TIP + BIKE = ADAPT", "Answer": "285 + 9867 = 10152"}
{"Question": "COW + SOFT = FEWER", "Answer": "685 + 9817 = 10502"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = BABY", "Answer": "323 + 3923 = 4246"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = NINE", "Answer": "373 + 3673 = 4046"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = FADE", "Answer": "424 + 4824 = 5248"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = ABLE", "Answer": "454 + 4854 = 5308"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = DATA", "Answer": "484 + 4384 = 4868"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = AIDE", "Answer": "787 + 7487 = 8274"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = RARE", "Answer": "848 + 8648 = 9496"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = TASTE", "Answer": "909 + 9809 = 10718"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = AGAIN", "Answer": "919 + 9219 = 10138"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = AFTER", "Answer": "919 + 9319 = 10238"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = ABOVE", "Answer": "919 + 9819 = 10738"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = FLOOR", "Answer": "929 + 9629 = 10558"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = CLOSE", "Answer": "929 + 9829 = 10758"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = FIFTH", "Answer": "939 + 9239 = 10178"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAD = GUIDE", "Answer": "949 + 9849 = 10798"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = AREA", "Answer": "211 + 2812 = 3023"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = DATA", "Answer": "466 + 4564 = 5030"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = DIET", "Answer": "733 + 7837 = 8570"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = DOOR", "Answer": "833 + 8938 = 9771"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = TIGHT", "Answer": "922 + 9329 = 10251"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = AWARD", "Answer": "933 + 9239 = 10172"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = ANGRY", "Answer": "933 + 9439 = 10372"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = STUDY", "Answer": "933 + 9739 = 10672"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = CARRY", "Answer": "933 + 9839 = 10772"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = PAPER", "Answer": "944 + 9249 = 10193"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = ARMED", "Answer": "944 + 9349 = 10293"}
{"Question": "EGG + EDGE = ANGER", "Answer": "944 + 9549 = 10493"}
{"Question": "POP + PLOT = TOOL", "Answer": "303 + 3704 = 4007"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAL = RARE", "Answer": "323 + 3926 = 4249"}
{"Question": "POP + PLOT = LOSS", "Answer": "515 + 5618 = 6133"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAL = FLEE", "Answer": "545 + 5843 = 6388"}
{"Question": "TAP + THAT = HATE", "Answer": "632 + 6736 = 7368"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAL = ALLY", "Answer": "676 + 6875 = 7551"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAL = EASE", "Answer": "767 + 7861 = 8628"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAL = AREA", "Answer": "787 + 7681 = 8468"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAL = MALE", "Answer": "838 + 8537 = 9375"}
{"Question": "POP + PLOT = TALL", "Answer": "838 + 8739 = 9577"}
{"Question": "DAD + DRAW = AWARD", "Answer": "919 + 9210 = 10129"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAR = AWARE", "Answer": "919 + 9213 = 10132"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAL = AGREE", "Answer": "919 + 9314 = 10233"}
{"Question": "DAD + DRAG = FLOOR", "Answer": "929 + 9627 = 10556"}
{"Question": "POP + PLOT = FIFTH", "Answer": "939 + 9237 = 10176"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAL = IRAQI", "Answer": "939 + 9432 = 10371"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAL = RIVER", "Answer": "939 + 9732 = 10671"}
{"Question": "TAP + THAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "943 + 9249 = 10192"}
{"Question": "DAD + DEAL = GRADE", "Answer": "949 + 9546 = 10495"}
{"Question": "EYE + EDGE = GOOD", "Answer": "737 + 7487 = 8224"}
{"Question": "EYE + ELSE = SHALL", "Answer": "969 + 9819 = 10788"}
{"Question": "TOO + TENT = DATA", "Answer": "377 + 3653 = 4030"}
{"Question": "TEA + THAT = HALL", "Answer": "654 + 6746 = 7400"}
{"Question": "TOO + TEST = SITE", "Answer": "688 + 6476 = 7164"}
{"Question": "MOM + MALL = ALSO", "Answer": "737 + 7866 = 8603"}
{"Question": "ADD + AREA = DEER", "Answer": "899 + 8768 = 9667"}
{"Question": "TOO + TEST = SALES", "Answer": "922 + 9419 = 10341"}
{"Question": "EGG + ELSE = USUAL", "Answer": "933 + 9209 = 10142"}
{"Question": "TAX + TEXT = AWARE", "Answer": "913 + 9239 = 10152"}
{"Question": "MOM + MESS = AWARE", "Answer": "949 + 9233 = 10182"}
{"Question": "TOO + THAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "933 + 9259 = 10192"}
{"Question": "MOM + MASS = HELLO", "Answer": "929 + 9733 = 10662"}
{"Question": "OFF + ONTO = ADAPT", "Answer": "944 + 9239 = 10183"}
{"Question": "MOM + MESS = ABOVE", "Answer": "929 + 9344 = 10273"}
{"Question": "EYE + EASY = BLOOD", "Answer": "949 + 9824 = 10773"}
{"Question": "MOM + MALL = ENEMY", "Answer": "939 + 9255 = 10194"}
{"Question": "MOM + MALL = EXTRA", "Answer": "929 + 9455 = 10384"}
{"Question": "ADD + AREA = CLEAR", "Answer": "955 + 9439 = 10394"}
{"Question": "MOM + MESS = BLAME", "Answer": "929 + 9566 = 10495"}
{"Question": "EYE + EASY = ASSET", "Answer": "989 + 9108 = 10097"}
{"Question": "TOO + THAT = EARTH", "Answer": "988 + 9709 = 10697"}
{"Question": "MOM + MERE = EVER", "Answer": "464 + 4595 = 5059"}
{"Question": "AIR + AREA = RICE", "Answer": "768 + 7857 = 8625"}
{"Question": "DIE + DEAD = AREA", "Answer": "821 + 8198 = 9019"}
{"Question": "EYE + EARN = AREA", "Answer": "727 + 7851 = 8578"}
{"Question": "TIE + THAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "903 + 9289 = 10192"}
{"Question": "ERA + EDGE = GRASS", "Answer": "903 + 9419 = 10322"}
{"Question": "DAD + DIET = CYCLE", "Answer": "939 + 9245 = 10184"}
{"Question": "DAD + DROP = KNOCK", "Answer": "939 + 9542 = 10481"}
{"Question": "ADD + DATA = TELL", "Answer": "644 + 4656 = 5300"}
{"Question": "ADD + DATA = TALL", "Answer": "977 + 7989 = 8966"}
{"Question": "EYE + YELL = ADAPT", "Answer": "595 + 9533 = 10128"}
{"Question": "EYE + YELL = FIFTY", "Answer": "595 + 9544 = 10139"}
{"Question": "EYE + YELL = ASIAN", "Answer": "696 + 9622 = 10318"}
{"Question": "EYE + YELL = LOOK", "Answer": "828 + 2833 = 3661"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAR = BOARD", "Answer": "696 + 9632 = 10328"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAH = BLOOD", "Answer": "696 + 9642 = 10338"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAR = SORRY", "Answer": "696 + 9643 = 10339"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAH = BLIND", "Answer": "696 + 9652 = 10348"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAH = BRIEF", "Answer": "696 + 9672 = 10368"}
{"Question": "POP + OPEN = ABUSE", "Answer": "696 + 9682 = 10378"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAR = STORY", "Answer": "797 + 9732 = 10529"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAH = DIRTY", "Answer": "797 + 9742 = 10539"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAH = CRAZY", "Answer": "797 + 9752 = 10549"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAH = FULLY", "Answer": "797 + 9762 = 10559"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAH = MONEY", "Answer": "797 + 9782 = 10579"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAH = ALLY", "Answer": "828 + 2834 = 3662"}
{"Question": "EYE + YEAR = AREA", "Answer": "838 + 3846 = 4684"}
{"Question": "POP + OPEN = COPE", "Answer": "868 + 6813 = 7681"}
{"Question": "ERA + RARE = THAT", "Answer": "386 + 8683 = 9069"}
{"Question": "ERA + RARE = EASE", "Answer": "980 + 8089 = 9069"}
{"Question": "EAR + ARAB = RARE", "Answer": "912 + 1217 = 2129"}
{"Question": "DAD + ARAB = INNER", "Answer": "292 + 9795 = 10087"}
{"Question": "END + NINE = AGAIN", "Answer": "297 + 9892 = 10189"}
{"Question": "LAW + AWAY = YELL", "Answer": "843 + 4345 = 5188"}
{"Question": "LAW + AWAY = WELL", "Answer": "634 + 3432 = 4066"}
{"Question": "NET + EVEN = ONTO", "Answer": "562 + 6965 = 7527"}
{"Question": "DAD + ARAB = BEER", "Answer": "757 + 5356 = 6113"}
{"Question": "BAD + ARAB = MEDIA", "Answer": "792 + 9497 = 10289"}
{"Question": "EYE + NINE = TEEN", "Answer": "282 + 4942 = 5224"}
{"Question": "EYE + NINE = ASSET", "Answer": "232 + 9792 = 10024"}
{"Question": "THE + HERE = ASSET", "Answer": "693 + 9343 = 10036"}
{"Question": "EYE + NINE = BADLY", "Answer": "363 + 9893 = 10256"}
{"Question": "DAD + ACID = GUESS", "Answer": "393 + 9873 = 10266"}
{"Question": "DAD + ACID = TOOTH", "Answer": "494 + 9524 = 10018"}
{"Question": "DAD + ACID = FLOOR", "Answer": "494 + 9734 = 10228"}
{"Question": "EYE + RARE = TODAY", "Answer": "484 + 9794 = 10278"}
{"Question": "SHE + HERE = VIRUS", "Answer": "894 + 9434 = 10328"}
{"Question": "EYE + NONE = VIDEO", "Answer": "454 + 9894 = 10348"}
{"Question": "THE + HERE = DATA", "Answer": "475 + 7565 = 8040"}
{"Question": "EYE + NONE = OPEN", "Answer": "818 + 6768 = 7586"}
{"Question": "EYE + RARE = AREA", "Answer": "919 + 7879 = 8798"}
{"Question": "MOM + ONTO = TENT", "Answer": "141 + 4954 = 5095"}
{"Question": "ODD + DATA = THAT", "Answer": "855 + 5161 = 6016"}
{"Question": "EGG + GAME = AREA", "Answer": "177 + 7841 = 8018"}
{"Question": "TEA + EASE = SEAT", "Answer": "725 + 2532 = 3257"}
{"Question": "MOM + ONTO = MOON", "Answer": "545 + 4904 = 5449"}
{"Question": "MOM + ONTO = TOSS", "Answer": "646 + 4754 = 5400"}
{"Question": "DAD + AREA = BALL", "Answer": "737 + 3563 = 4300"}
{"Question": "DAD + AREA = RARE", "Answer": "919 + 1201 = 2120"}
{"Question": "THE + HEAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "198 + 9821 = 10019"}
{"Question": "THE + HEAT = AREA", "Answer": "287 + 8792 = 9079"}
{"Question": "EGG + NONE = OPEN", "Answer": "255 + 7872 = 8127"}
{"Question": "EGG + NINE = PAPER", "Answer": "233 + 9892 = 10125"}
{"Question": "THE + HELL = ADAPT", "Answer": "892 + 9266 = 10158"}
{"Question": "EYE + AWAY = BRIEF", "Answer": "343 + 9894 = 10237"}
{"Question": "SAD + AIDS = IDEA", "Answer": "473 + 7834 = 8307"}
{"Question": "TEA + RARE = SHOOT", "Answer": "734 + 9493 = 10227"}
{"Question": "TEA + RARE = TENT", "Answer": "725 + 6562 = 7287"}
{"Question": "EYE + AWAY = BLOOD", "Answer": "535 + 9693 = 10228"}
{"Question": "SEA + RARE = THEIR", "Answer": "845 + 9594 = 10439"}
{"Question": "EYE + BABY = AREA", "Answer": "858 + 2325 = 3183"}
{"Question": "SKI + KILL = SLIP", "Answer": "548 + 4833 = 5381"}
{"Question": "EGG + RARE = AREA", "Answer": "955 + 3439 = 4394"}
{"Question": "HIT + ITEM = TOOTH", "Answer": "891 + 9127 = 10018"}
{"Question": "EYE + ARAB = INNER", "Answer": "232 + 9795 = 10027"}
{"Question": "DAD + ARMY = INNER", "Answer": "292 + 9745 = 10037"}
{"Question": "WIN + INTO = ALLOW", "Answer": "792 + 9265 = 10057"}
{"Question": "DAD + ABLE = COUNT", "Answer": "393 + 9864 = 10257"}
{"Question": "RID + IDEA = READ", "Answer": "874 + 7430 = 8304"}
{"Question": "TWO + NONE = TEEN", "Answer": "864 + 7473 = 8337"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALSO = WHOLE", "Answer": "494 + 9782 = 10276"}
{"Question": "DAD + ABLE = CLEAN", "Answer": "494 + 9802 = 10296"}
{"Question": "MOM + OPEN = AGENT", "Answer": "494 + 9832 = 10326"}
{"Question": "DAD + ABLE = CROSS", "Answer": "494 + 9872 = 10366"}
{"Question": "THE + HERO = ROOT", "Answer": "815 + 1523 = 2338"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALSO = COOL", "Answer": "515 + 1934 = 2449"}
{"Question": "SIN + INTO = TOSS", "Answer": "735 + 3542 = 4277"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALSO = IMPLY", "Answer": "595 + 9673 = 10268"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALSO = WHEEL", "Answer": "595 + 9742 = 10337"}
{"Question": "DAD + ARMY = ENTER", "Answer": "595 + 9823 = 10418"}
{"Question": "WHO + HOST = CATCH", "Answer": "895 + 9524 = 10419"}
{"Question": "SON + ONLY = LOSS", "Answer": "736 + 3641 = 4377"}
{"Question": "EAR + AIDE = DATA", "Answer": "648 + 4756 = 5404"}
{"Question": "DAD + ABLE = FUNNY", "Answer": "696 + 9752 = 10448"}
{"Question": "DAD + ARMY = STORM", "Answer": "696 + 9782 = 10478"}
{"Question": "MOM + ARAB = SOLAR", "Answer": "606 + 9892 = 10498"}
{"Question": "DAD + ARMY = HUMOR", "Answer": "696 + 9852 = 10548"}
{"Question": "ONE + NEAR = AREA", "Answer": "487 + 8792 = 9279"}
{"Question": "EYE + YOUR = CARRY", "Answer": "797 + 9432 = 10229"}
{"Question": "EYE + YARD = TODAY", "Answer": "797 + 9452 = 10249"}
{"Question": "WHO + NONE = WHEN", "Answer": "318 + 2824 = 3142"}
{"Question": "TOP + OPEN = TONE", "Answer": "328 + 2891 = 3219"}
{"Question": "KID + IDEA = DEAD", "Answer": "478 + 7830 = 8308"}
{"Question": "ERA + NINE = AGAIN", "Answer": "831 + 9298 = 10129"}
{"Question": "END + GENE = EDGE", "Answer": "520 + 4525 = 5045"}
{"Question": "ERA + HERE = INNER", "Answer": "527 + 9525 = 10052"}
{"Question": "END + GENE = ASSET", "Answer": "528 + 9525 = 10053"}
{"Question": "ERA + HERE = OCCUR", "Answer": "538 + 9535 = 10073"}
{"Question": "POP + SPOT = TITLE", "Answer": "575 + 9571 = 10146"}
{"Question": "POP + UPON = ADAPT", "Answer": "575 + 9578 = 10153"}
{"Question": "POP + UPON = HONOR", "Answer": "606 + 9602 = 10208"}
{"Question": "ERA + HERE = CLASS", "Answer": "642 + 9646 = 10288"}
{"Question": "POP + UPON = NEVER", "Answer": "656 + 9651 = 10307"}
{"Question": "POP + SPOT = CIVIL", "Answer": "656 + 9652 = 10308"}
{"Question": "ERA + MERE = CLAIM", "Answer": "673 + 9676 = 10349"}
{"Question": "POP + UPON = SCENE", "Answer": "686 + 9687 = 10373"}
{"Question": "ERA + MERE = BOOM", "Answer": "721 + 8727 = 9448"}
{"Question": "POP + SPOT = CLOCK", "Answer": "757 + 9756 = 10513"}
{"Question": "POP + UPON = BASIS", "Answer": "767 + 9768 = 10535"}
{"Question": "END + GENE = LABEL", "Answer": "784 + 9787 = 10571"}
{"Question": "ERA + HERE = CRACK", "Answer": "806 + 9808 = 10614"}
{"Question": "POP + SPOT = OFTEN", "Answer": "818 + 9816 = 10634"}
{"Question": "POP + UPON = ODDS", "Answer": "838 + 2831 = 3669"}
{"Question": "POP + SPOT = LOTS", "Answer": "878 + 3875 = 4753"}
{"Question": "ERA + MERE = ARMY", "Answer": "876 + 5878 = 6754"}
{"Question": "POP + SPOT = KNOCK", "Answer": "878 + 9873 = 10751"}
{"Question": "POP + SPOT = QUOTE", "Answer": "878 + 9875 = 10753"}
{"Question": "EYE + GENE = HONOR", "Answer": "828 + 9878 = 10706"}
{"Question": "EYE + MERE = ARMY", "Answer": "868 + 4878 = 5746"}
{"Question": "EYE + HERE = DIRTY", "Answer": "868 + 9878 = 10746"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = APPLE", "Answer": "515 + 9561 = 10076"}
{"Question": "EYE + LESS = APPLY", "Answer": "575 + 9522 = 10097"}
{"Question": "EYE + DENY = AWARD", "Answer": "545 + 9584 = 10129"}
{"Question": "EYE + RELY = LOSS", "Answer": "575 + 3547 = 4122"}
{"Question": "EYE + RELY = ALLOW", "Answer": "575 + 9507 = 10082"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = BILL", "Answer": "585 + 1548 = 2133"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = CYCLE", "Answer": "585 + 9538 = 10123"}
{"Question": "EYE + DENY = PAPER", "Answer": "585 + 9568 = 10153"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = ABOVE", "Answer": "616 + 9671 = 10287"}
{"Question": "EYE + RELY = YOURS", "Answer": "616 + 9681 = 10297"}
{"Question": "EAR + HERE = CARRY", "Answer": "602 + 9626 = 10228"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = EXACT", "Answer": "626 + 9612 = 10238"}
{"Question": "EYE + DENY = BUYER", "Answer": "626 + 9642 = 10268"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = DARE", "Answer": "636 + 5693 = 6329"}
{"Question": "EAR + HERE = LABEL", "Answer": "605 + 9656 = 10261"}
{"Question": "EYE + RELY = AREA", "Answer": "686 + 3678 = 4364"}
{"Question": "EYE + RELY = LIMIT", "Answer": "686 + 9618 = 10304"}
{"Question": "EYE + VERY = FLOOR", "Answer": "686 + 9648 = 10334"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = CROSS", "Answer": "686 + 9658 = 10344"}
{"Question": "EYE + LESS = SHOOT", "Answer": "737 + 9711 = 10448"}
{"Question": "EYE + DENY = ARMED", "Answer": "727 + 9752 = 10479"}
{"Question": "EYE + RELY = HONOR", "Answer": "727 + 9782 = 10509"}
{"Question": "EYE + RELY = START", "Answer": "737 + 9753 = 10490"}
{"Question": "EYE + BELL = SALES", "Answer": "727 + 9744 = 10471"}
{"Question": "EGG + MERE = TIGHT", "Answer": "744 + 9737 = 10481"}
{"Question": "EYE + DENY = NOVEL", "Answer": "757 + 9715 = 10472"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = CLASS", "Answer": "757 + 9765 = 10522"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = FLOOR", "Answer": "767 + 9786 = 10553"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = SCENE", "Answer": "787 + 9758 = 10545"}
{"Question": "ART + DATA = TIRED", "Answer": "861 + 9818 = 10679"}
{"Question": "EYE + BELL = ORDER", "Answer": "858 + 9822 = 10680"}
{"Question": "EYE + VERY = IRAQI", "Answer": "838 + 9803 = 10641"}
{"Question": "EYE + DENY = LABEL", "Answer": "838 + 9843 = 10681"}
{"Question": "ART + DATA = READ", "Answer": "834 + 2848 = 3682"}
{"Question": "ALL + DATA = TROOP", "Answer": "844 + 9818 = 10662"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = HELLO", "Answer": "858 + 9805 = 10663"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = MOVIE", "Answer": "858 + 9835 = 10693"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = BEACH", "Answer": "868 + 9806 = 10674"}
{"Question": "EYE + DENY = ASIAN", "Answer": "868 + 9846 = 10714"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = COACH", "Answer": "878 + 9837 = 10715"}
{"Question": "DAD + IDEA = BLAME", "Answer": "878 + 9857 = 10735"}
{"Question": "EYE + DEAD = ASSET", "Answer": "535 + 9519 = 10054"}
{"Question": "EYE + DEAD = APPLY", "Answer": "545 + 9519 = 10064"}
{"Question": "DAD + EDGE = ALLOW", "Answer": "515 + 9569 = 10084"}
{"Question": "DAD + EDGE = ASSET", "Answer": "515 + 9579 = 10094"}
{"Question": "DAD + EDGE = ANGRY", "Answer": "616 + 9629 = 10245"}
{"Question": "DAD + EDGE = AFTER", "Answer": "616 + 9679 = 10295"}
{"Question": "DAD + EDGE = COACH", "Answer": "636 + 9679 = 10315"}
{"Question": "EYE + DEAD = IMPLY", "Answer": "656 + 9689 = 10345"}
{"Question": "DAD + EDGE = GLASS", "Answer": "747 + 9719 = 10466"}
{"Question": "EYE + TENT = HONOR", "Answer": "747 + 9759 = 10506"}
{"Question": "EYE + TENT = ASIAN", "Answer": "747 + 9769 = 10516"}
{"Question": "EYE + TEST = STEP", "Answer": "808 + 6876 = 7684"}
{"Question": "AID + DATA = STILL", "Answer": "869 + 9808 = 10677"}
{"Question": "AID + DATA = TRIAL", "Answer": "869 + 9818 = 10687"}
{"Question": "EYE + TENT = MONTH", "Answer": "828 + 9869 = 10697"}
{"Question": "POP + SPIN = LOOSE", "Answer": "505 + 9587 = 10092"}
{"Question": "EYE + LEAD = APPLY", "Answer": "585 + 9513 = 10098"}
{"Question": "EYE + HERO = OCCUR", "Answer": "525 + 9561 = 10086"}
{"Question": "EYE + LEFT = APPLY", "Answer": "525 + 9567 = 10092"}
{"Question": "AIR + DATA = THIRD", "Answer": "623 + 9616 = 10239"}
{"Question": "AGE + DATA = TIGHT", "Answer": "625 + 9616 = 10241"}
{"Question": "ARM + DATA = THREE", "Answer": "628 + 9616 = 10244"}
{"Question": "EYE + HELP = LABEL", "Answer": "646 + 9615 = 10261"}
{"Question": "EYE + BEAT = AFTER", "Answer": "656 + 9612 = 10268"}
{"Question": "EYE + DEBT = LABEL", "Answer": "636 + 9625 = 10261"}
{"Question": "ARM + DATA = METER", "Answer": "671 + 9636 = 10307"}
{"Question": "EYE + DEAL = SALES", "Answer": "767 + 9704 = 10471"}
{"Question": "EYE + BEST = SORRY", "Answer": "727 + 9715 = 10442"}
{"Question": "EYE + DEBT = BLOOD", "Answer": "737 + 9712 = 10449"}
{"Question": "END + HERE = NORTH", "Answer": "712 + 9747 = 10459"}
{"Question": "ARM + DATA = TERMS", "Answer": "746 + 9717 = 10463"}
{"Question": "AGE + DATA = TREAT", "Answer": "754 + 9717 = 10471"}
{"Question": "EYE + DECK = CIVIL", "Answer": "787 + 9716 = 10503"}
{"Question": "ETC + HERE = COLOR", "Answer": "721 + 9787 = 10508"}
{"Question": "EYE + HEAD = COACH", "Answer": "767 + 9752 = 10519"}
{"Question": "EYE + TERM = MAYOR", "Answer": "757 + 9781 = 10538"}
{"Question": "AIM + DATA = TIGHT", "Answer": "803 + 9818 = 10621"}
{"Question": "EAT + HERE = RATIO", "Answer": "806 + 9818 = 10624"}
{"Question": "POP + SPIN = HONEY", "Answer": "808 + 9826 = 10634"}
{"Question": "EYE + HERO = CROSS", "Answer": "838 + 9806 = 10644"}
{"Question": "EYE + BEAR = PARTY", "Answer": "848 + 9806 = 10654"}
{"Question": "EYE + HERO = PROOF", "Answer": "858 + 9806 = 10664"}
{"Question": "EYE + DEAR = LABEL", "Answer": "878 + 9803 = 10681"}
{"Question": "EYE + BEAN = PANEL", "Answer": "878 + 9806 = 10684"}
{"Question": "EYE + TERM = DIRTY", "Answer": "828 + 9864 = 10692"}
{"Question": "ERA + GENE = HONOR", "Answer": "824 + 9878 = 10702"}
{"Question": "EYE + BELT = HOTEL", "Answer": "838 + 9846 = 10684"}
{"Question": "ARM + DATA = LIMIT", "Answer": "847 + 9858 = 10705"}
{"Question": "ETC + HERE = CATCH", "Answer": "871 + 9848 = 10719"}
{"Question": "EYE + BEAR = START", "Answer": "848 + 9872 = 10720"}
{"Question": "SIT + STIR = AWARD", "Answer": "932 + 9236 = 10168"}
{"Question": "SIT + STIR = RURAL", "Answer": "942 + 9241 = 10183"}
{"Question": "SET + STEP = ELITE", "Answer": "913 + 9318 = 10231"}
{"Question": "SON + SNOW = CROWD", "Answer": "923 + 9324 = 10247"}
{"Question": "FOR + FROM = KNOCK", "Answer": "923 + 9328 = 10251"}
{"Question": "SET + STEP = PHONE", "Answer": "943 + 9341 = 10284"}
{"Question": "ERA + EARN = FINAL", "Answer": "924 + 9423 = 10347"}
{"Question": "TWO + TOWN = PILOT", "Answer": "924 + 9425 = 10349"}
{"Question": "ERA + EARN = SOLAR", "Answer": "925 + 9527 = 10452"}
{"Question": "ERA + EARN = SINCE", "Answer": "935 + 9534 = 10469"}
{"Question": "TWO + TOWN = ONTO", "Answer": "475 + 4570 = 5045"}
{"Question": "ERA + EARN = AREA", "Answer": "637 + 6730 = 7367"}
{"Question": "TWO + TOWN = SHEET", "Answer": "937 + 9732 = 10669"}
{"Question": "SIT + STIR = AGREE", "Answer": "928 + 9827 = 10755"}
{"Question": "ERA + EARN = FLOOR", "Answer": "938 + 9835 = 10773"}
{"Question": "ERA + EARN = FUNNY", "Answer": "938 + 9837 = 10775"}
{"Question": "DNA + DATA = ELECT", "Answer": "932 + 9242 = 10174"}
{"Question": "DNA + DATA = NERVE", "Answer": "915 + 9565 = 10480"}
{"Question": "DNA + DATA = NEED", "Answer": "457 + 4767 = 5224"}
{"Question": "CEO + CODE = ELECT", "Answer": "912 + 9281 = 10193"}
{"Question": "CEO + CODE = AWARD", "Answer": "932 + 9253 = 10185"}
{"Question": "TEA + TALL = EVENT", "Answer": "912 + 9277 = 10189"}
{"Question": "CEO + CODE = BREAD", "Answer": "923 + 9352 = 10275"}
{"Question": "TEA + TALE = LEFT", "Answer": "615 + 6571 = 7186"}
{"Question": "CEO + CODE = FULLY", "Answer": "926 + 9632 = 10558"}
{"Question": "CEO + COPE = PRIOR", "Answer": "946 + 9614 = 10560"}
{"Question": "CEO + CODE = TREAT", "Answer": "956 + 9625 = 10581"}
{"Question": "TEA + TAKE = FLOAT", "Answer": "927 + 9752 = 10679"}
{"Question": "CEO + CODE = DREAM", "Answer": "967 + 9716 = 10683"}
{"Question": "TWO + TOSS = SHEET", "Answer": "968 + 9811 = 10779"}
{"Question": "CEO + CODE = PRIOR", "Answer": "928 + 9852 = 10780"}
{"Question": "SEA + SAFE = PROOF", "Answer": "948 + 9824 = 10772"}
{"Question": "SEA + SAFE = FLESH", "Answer": "978 + 9817 = 10795"}
{"Question": "THE + TEAR = APART", "Answer": "962 + 9217 = 10179"}
{"Question": "VIA + VAST = ELITE", "Answer": "923 + 9358 = 10281"}
{"Question": "CEO + COAL = FRAME", "Answer": "924 + 9438 = 10362"}
{"Question": "SKI + SIDE = DRESS", "Answer": "985 + 9514 = 10499"}
{"Question": "DIG + DATA = TIGHT", "Answer": "905 + 9616 = 10521"}
{"Question": "SKI + SITE = TREAT", "Answer": "926 + 9615 = 10541"}
{"Question": "DNA + DATE = TREAT", "Answer": "946 + 9615 = 10561"}
{"Question": "DIE + DEAR = CHART", "Answer": "926 + 9658 = 10584"}
{"Question": "CEO + CORN = BENCH", "Answer": "907 + 9786 = 10693"}
{"Question": "DNA + DATE = SHEET", "Answer": "927 + 9736 = 10663"}
{"Question": "CEO + COLD = JUDGE", "Answer": "937 + 9746 = 10683"}
{"Question": "CEO + CORN = MINOR", "Answer": "928 + 9857 = 10785"}
{"Question": "SIT + STEP = PRESS", "Answer": "928 + 9871 = 10799"}
{"Question": "ONE + GENE = ESSAY", "Answer": "871 + 9171 = 10042"}
{"Question": "MOM + FROM = ROOF", "Answer": "303 + 6703 = 7006"}
{"Question": "DAD + HEAD = ISSUE", "Answer": "373 + 9673 = 10046"}
{"Question": "DAD + LEAD = ABLE", "Answer": "393 + 8693 = 9086"}
{"Question": "MOM + FROM = COLOR", "Answer": "404 + 9804 = 10208"}
{"Question": "DAD + HEAD = BLADE", "Answer": "424 + 9824 = 10248"}
{"Question": "DAD + HEAD = EACH", "Answer": "434 + 8934 = 9368"}
{"Question": "DAD + HEAD = INNER", "Answer": "434 + 9634 = 10068"}
{"Question": "DAD + GLAD = CIVIL", "Answer": "454 + 9854 = 10308"}
{"Question": "MOM + WHOM = ORDER", "Answer": "515 + 9715 = 10230"}
{"Question": "DAD + ROAD = LEAVE", "Answer": "535 + 9835 = 10370"}
{"Question": "DAD + READ = AREA", "Answer": "626 + 1526 = 2152"}
{"Question": "DAD + GLAD = IMAGE", "Answer": "646 + 9846 = 10492"}
{"Question": "DAD + GLAD = COACH", "Answer": "656 + 9856 = 10512"}
{"Question": "MOM + FROM = THERE", "Answer": "676 + 9576 = 10252"}
{"Question": "DAD + GLAD = PHOTO", "Answer": "686 + 9586 = 10272"}
{"Question": "DAD + HEAD = RARE", "Answer": "717 + 2417 = 3134"}
{"Question": "DAD + GLAD = APPLE", "Answer": "717 + 9317 = 10034"}
{"Question": "DAD + HEAD = AWARE", "Answer": "717 + 9417 = 10134"}
{"Question": "DAD + HEAD = BIBLE", "Answer": "727 + 9427 = 10154"}
{"Question": "POP + STOP = ADAPT", "Answer": "737 + 9437 = 10174"}
{"Question": "DAD + GLAD = READY", "Answer": "737 + 9637 = 10374"}
{"Question": "DAD + ROAD = AREA", "Answer": "747 + 3647 = 4394"}
{"Question": "MOM + WHOM = CATCH", "Answer": "757 + 9457 = 10214"}
{"Question": "MOM + WHOM = DRAMA", "Answer": "787 + 9687 = 10474"}
{"Question": "DAD + HEAD = TASTE", "Answer": "808 + 9608 = 10416"}
{"Question": "POP + DROP = WORD", "Answer": "818 + 6318 = 7136"}
{"Question": "DAD + GLAD = AWFUL", "Answer": "818 + 9618 = 10436"}
{"Question": "DAD + READ = EVER", "Answer": "838 + 6738 = 7576"}
{"Question": "POP + SHOP = PUSH", "Answer": "838 + 7638 = 8476"}
{"Question": "DAD + HEAD = EASE", "Answer": "848 + 5648 = 6496"}
{"Question": "DAD + LEAD = SCALE", "Answer": "848 + 9648 = 10496"}
{"Question": "DAD + LEAD = MALE", "Answer": "858 + 1658 = 2516"}
{"Question": "MOM + FROM = PHOTO", "Answer": "868 + 9768 = 10636"}
{"Question": "DAD + GLAD = LOOSE", "Answer": "878 + 9178 = 10056"}
{"Question": "DAD + GLAD = STEEL", "Answer": "878 + 9678 = 10556"}
{"Question": "EGG + HUGE = ESSAY", "Answer": "166 + 9861 = 10027"}
{"Question": "TOO + SHOT = FIFTH", "Answer": "266 + 9862 = 10128"}
{"Question": "TOO + PLOT = CIVIL", "Answer": "355 + 9853 = 10208"}
{"Question": "EGG + PAGE = TROOP", "Answer": "366 + 9863 = 10229"}
{"Question": "EGG + URGE = INNER", "Answer": "422 + 9624 = 10046"}
{"Question": "EGG + HUGE = ANGER", "Answer": "422 + 9824 = 10246"}
{"Question": "TEN + KNEE = ELECT", "Answer": "615 + 9511 = 10126"}
{"Question": "HER + TREE = FIGHT", "Answer": "845 + 9544 = 10389"}
{"Question": "HER + TREE = APART", "Answer": "536 + 9633 = 10169"}
{"Question": "HER + TREE = COURT", "Answer": "836 + 9633 = 10469"}
{"Question": "FEE + CHEF = HELL", "Answer": "655 + 7856 = 8511"}
{"Question": "EGG + HUGE = BLOOD", "Answer": "677 + 9876 = 10553"}
{"Question": "FEE + CHEF = EACH", "Answer": "688 + 7486 = 8174"}
{"Question": "PER + TREE = ADAPT", "Answer": "427 + 9722 = 10149"}
{"Question": "TOO + PLOT = GROUP", "Answer": "722 + 9527 = 10249"}
{"Question": "TOO + SHOT = HERE", "Answer": "755 + 3457 = 4212"}
{"Question": "FEE + CHEF = TOOTH", "Answer": "755 + 9257 = 10012"}
{"Question": "TOO + SPOT = PASS", "Answer": "766 + 3467 = 4233"}
{"Question": "FEE + CHEF = DRESS", "Answer": "766 + 9867 = 10633"}
{"Question": "EGG + URGE = AFTER", "Answer": "788 + 9587 = 10375"}
{"Question": "HER + TREE = ELECT", "Answer": "318 + 9811 = 10129"}
{"Question": "EGG + URGE = START", "Answer": "822 + 9528 = 10350"}
{"Question": "TOO + PLOT = KNOCK", "Answer": "833 + 9538 = 10371"}
{"Question": "EGG + PAGE = LOCAL", "Answer": "833 + 9738 = 10571"}
{"Question": "EGG + URGE = OCCUR", "Answer": "844 + 9248 = 10092"}
{"Question": "TOO + SPOT = IRISH", "Answer": "844 + 9348 = 10192"}
{"Question": "EGG + HUGE = FIGHT", "Answer": "844 + 9648 = 10492"}
{"Question": "HER + TREE = DATA", "Answer": "458 + 1855 = 2313"}
{"Question": "TEN + KNEE = TOOTH", "Answer": "158 + 9855 = 10013"}
{"Question": "FEE + CHEF = TRUTH", "Answer": "855 + 9358 = 10213"}
{"Question": "TOO + SHOT = CLOCK", "Answer": "855 + 9658 = 10513"}
{"Question": "EGG + PAGE = ALLOW", "Answer": "866 + 9168 = 10034"}
{"Question": "EGG + HUGE = BASIS", "Answer": "866 + 9568 = 10434"}
{"Question": "EGG + HUGE = ANGRY", "Answer": "866 + 9768 = 10634"}
{"Question": "TOO + PLOT = SHALL", "Answer": "877 + 9578 = 10455"}
{"Question": "RAW + WEAR = APART", "Answer": "319 + 9813 = 10132"}
{"Question": "ETC + CITE = AGAIN", "Answer": "389 + 9783 = 10172"}
{"Question": "DAD + THAT = AGREE", "Answer": "414 + 9819 = 10233"}
{"Question": "HER + AREA = EARN", "Answer": "724 + 1421 = 2145"}
{"Question": "ONE + TENT = ALLOW", "Answer": "574 + 9479 = 10053"}
{"Question": "DAD + THAT = BLADE", "Answer": "525 + 9729 = 10254"}
{"Question": "DAD + THAT = IRISH", "Answer": "636 + 9539 = 10175"}
{"Question": "DAD + THAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "646 + 9549 = 10195"}
{"Question": "DRY + YARD = ENTER", "Answer": "659 + 9756 = 10415"}
{"Question": "HER + AREA = CARE", "Answer": "586 + 2682 = 3268"}
{"Question": "RAW + WEAR = ASSET", "Answer": "719 + 9317 = 10036"}
{"Question": "RAW + WEAR = SHARE", "Answer": "739 + 9637 = 10376"}
{"Question": "NET + THEN = PIECE", "Answer": "769 + 9867 = 10636"}
{"Question": "ETC + CITE = OFFER", "Answer": "789 + 9287 = 10076"}
{"Question": "RAW + WEAR = SCORE", "Answer": "789 + 9687 = 10476"}
{"Question": "BAG + GRAB = APART", "Answer": "819 + 9318 = 10137"}
{"Question": "BAG + GRAB = ACTOR", "Answer": "819 + 9718 = 10537"}
{"Question": "BAG + GRAB = FLOOR", "Answer": "829 + 9728 = 10557"}
{"Question": "DAD + THAT = CLASS", "Answer": "838 + 9539 = 10377"}
{"Question": "DRY + YARD = DEAR", "Answer": "857 + 7158 = 8015"}
{"Question": "DAD + THAT = CRACK", "Answer": "858 + 9659 = 10517"}
{"Question": "DRY + YARD = ALLOW", "Answer": "869 + 9168 = 10037"}
{"Question": "DAD + THAT = BEACH", "Answer": "868 + 9769 = 10637"}
{"Question": "BAG + GRAB = EXTRA", "Answer": "879 + 9578 = 10457"}
{"Question": "DAD + THAT = MATH", "Answer": "919 + 3213 = 4132"}
{"Question": "ERA + CARE = EVER", "Answer": "891 + 7198 = 8089"}
{"Question": "BAR + GRAB = RACE", "Answer": "658 + 7856 = 8514"}
{"Question": "ERA + CARD = APPLE", "Answer": "861 + 9167 = 10028"}
{"Question": "LAB + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "216 + 9812 = 10028"}
{"Question": "ERA + PART = TAPE", "Answer": "982 + 6287 = 7269"}
{"Question": "DAD + REAL = DARE", "Answer": "313 + 2815 = 3128"}
{"Question": "ERA + WARN = HONOR", "Answer": "853 + 9352 = 10205"}
{"Question": "MOM + UPON = HONOR", "Answer": "404 + 9802 = 10206"}
{"Question": "DAD + MEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "414 + 9612 = 10026"}
{"Question": "ONE + TEND = ASSET", "Answer": "624 + 9425 = 10049"}
{"Question": "DAD + BOAT = TRADE", "Answer": "424 + 9821 = 10245"}
{"Question": "AIR + TRIP = SHIRT", "Answer": "824 + 9425 = 10249"}
{"Question": "DAD + FLAG = CIVIL", "Answer": "454 + 9753 = 10207"}
{"Question": "DAD + BOAT = ERROR", "Answer": "474 + 9576 = 10050"}
{"Question": "DAD + LEAF = FLEE", "Answer": "484 + 1682 = 2166"}
{"Question": "SKI + LIKE = SELL", "Answer": "784 + 6482 = 7266"}
{"Question": "PIE + TRIP = PEER", "Answer": "512 + 4715 = 5227"}
{"Question": "MOM + IRON = OWNER", "Answer": "515 + 9813 = 10328"}
{"Question": "DAD + REAL = AREA", "Answer": "535 + 2738 = 3273"}
{"Question": "EAT + STAR = TREE", "Answer": "635 + 4531 = 5166"}
{"Question": "DNA + SEND = EASE", "Answer": "532 + 6735 = 7267"}
{"Question": "DAD + FLAG = GRASS", "Answer": "535 + 9831 = 10366"}
{"Question": "DAD + HEAT = CRASH", "Answer": "535 + 9834 = 10369"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAN = NOVEL", "Answer": "545 + 9841 = 10386"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAR = THREE", "Answer": "545 + 9843 = 10388"}
{"Question": "MOM + DROP = COLOR", "Answer": "606 + 9802 = 10408"}
{"Question": "DAD + LEAF = AWFUL", "Answer": "616 + 9713 = 10329"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAN = ALONE", "Answer": "616 + 9812 = 10428"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAT = TRADE", "Answer": "636 + 9731 = 10367"}
{"Question": "DAD + PLAN = LAND", "Answer": "656 + 7850 = 8506"}
{"Question": "GET + ITEM = GENE", "Answer": "856 + 7659 = 8515"}
{"Question": "HER + CREW = TOOTH", "Answer": "356 + 9657 = 10013"}
{"Question": "GAS + DRAG = STATE", "Answer": "651 + 9856 = 10507"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAN = STATE", "Answer": "656 + 9852 = 10508"}
{"Question": "DNA + RANK = HONOR", "Answer": "856 + 9653 = 10509"}
{"Question": "MRS + HERE = SEEM", "Answer": "983 + 2686 = 3669"}
{"Question": "EAT + STAR = ROUTE", "Answer": "786 + 9681 = 10467"}
{"Question": "LIE + RAIL = INNER", "Answer": "712 + 9317 = 10029"}
{"Question": "DAD + TEAR = APART", "Answer": "717 + 9412 = 10129"}
{"Question": "BIT + STIR = EARTH", "Answer": "837 + 9735 = 10572"}
{"Question": "DAD + SEAT = LOOSE", "Answer": "747 + 9346 = 10093"}
{"Question": "DAD + REAL = COLOR", "Answer": "757 + 9452 = 10209"}
{"Question": "SKI + BIKE = ORDER", "Answer": "467 + 9763 = 10230"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAT = TRACE", "Answer": "767 + 9861 = 10628"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAR = START", "Answer": "767 + 9863 = 10630"}
{"Question": "TWO + BOWL = ERROR", "Answer": "287 + 9783 = 10070"}
{"Question": "BED + IDEA = AWARE", "Answer": "387 + 9781 = 10168"}
{"Question": "END + FINE = ORDER", "Answer": "783 + 9587 = 10370"}
{"Question": "BET + ITEM = MAYBE", "Answer": "687 + 9781 = 10468"}
{"Question": "DNA + HANG = LEGAL", "Answer": "687 + 9784 = 10471"}
{"Question": "DAD + SEAT = EASE", "Answer": "808 + 1204 = 2012"}
{"Question": "SKI + BIKE = SEEK", "Answer": "518 + 4813 = 5331"}
{"Question": "DAD + STAR = AGREE", "Answer": "818 + 9715 = 10533"}
{"Question": "DAD + MEAL = BIBLE", "Answer": "828 + 9325 = 10153"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAN = CHASE", "Answer": "828 + 9426 = 10254"}
{"Question": "ETC + DATE = LOCAL", "Answer": "823 + 9528 = 10351"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAR = AREA", "Answer": "838 + 2735 = 3573"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAR = RARE", "Answer": "838 + 6537 = 7375"}
{"Question": "DNA + WIND = ALLOW", "Answer": "831 + 9238 = 10069"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAN = PLANE", "Answer": "838 + 9537 = 10375"}
{"Question": "ERA + CARD = UNDER", "Answer": "738 + 9835 = 10573"}
{"Question": "ERA + TIRE = ASSET", "Answer": "841 + 9248 = 10089"}
{"Question": "BET + STEP = LOOSE", "Answer": "248 + 9846 = 10094"}
{"Question": "DAD + LEAF = BIBLE", "Answer": "848 + 9345 = 10193"}
{"Question": "DNA + HANG = TIGHT", "Answer": "548 + 9843 = 10391"}
{"Question": "BAR + DRAG = GUARD", "Answer": "648 + 9841 = 10489"}
{"Question": "DAD + COAL = PEACE", "Answer": "848 + 9642 = 10490"}
{"Question": "BED + IDEA = DEAD", "Answer": "658 + 7850 = 8508"}
{"Question": "DAD + OKAY = CHECK", "Answer": "858 + 9456 = 10314"}
{"Question": "SIN + UNIT = ELITE", "Answer": "768 + 9863 = 10631"}
{"Question": "ONE + MENU = OCCUR", "Answer": "178 + 9875 = 10053"}
{"Question": "DAD + FLAG = TIGHT", "Answer": "878 + 9473 = 10351"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEAR = DARE", "Answer": "919 + 8213 = 9132"}
{"Question": "EYE + LIFE = APPLY", "Answer": "242 + 9852 = 10094"}
{"Question": "THE + GENE = TEEN", "Answer": "973 + 8363 = 9336"}
{"Question": "MOM + TEAM = ABOVE", "Answer": "424 + 9814 = 10238"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEND = ASIDE", "Answer": "414 + 9834 = 10248"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEND = AGREE", "Answer": "414 + 9874 = 10288"}
{"Question": "ERA + DATA = TREE", "Answer": "824 + 5464 = 6288"}
{"Question": "DAD + USED = CLASS", "Answer": "424 + 9864 = 10288"}
{"Question": "DAD + SEND = CHASE", "Answer": "424 + 9874 = 10298"}
{"Question": "DAD + USED = LOOSE", "Answer": "474 + 9584 = 10058"}
{"Question": "EYE + HATE = THEY", "Answer": "505 + 3845 = 4350"}
{"Question": "MOM + FARM = ORDER", "Answer": "515 + 9805 = 10320"}
{"Question": "DAD + COLD = LEAVE", "Answer": "525 + 9715 = 10240"}
{"Question": "EYE + SHOE = ORDER", "Answer": "535 + 9715 = 10250"}
{"Question": "MOM + TEAM = ORDER", "Answer": "515 + 9865 = 10380"}
{"Question": "EYE + RISE = START", "Answer": "575 + 9815 = 10390"}
{"Question": "DAD + COLD = PEACE", "Answer": "525 + 9765 = 10290"}
{"Question": "DAD + COLD = ELECT", "Answer": "686 + 9506 = 10192"}
{"Question": "EYE + BASE = SORRY", "Answer": "626 + 9816 = 10442"}
{"Question": "EYE + CORE = PAPER", "Answer": "636 + 9526 = 10162"}
{"Question": "EYE + AIDE = DATA", "Answer": "676 + 2536 = 3212"}
{"Question": "MOM + FILM = LOOSE", "Answer": "707 + 9317 = 10024"}
{"Question": "DAD + BIRD = AGREE", "Answer": "717 + 9527 = 10244"}
{"Question": "DAD + USED = ARISE", "Answer": "717 + 9647 = 10364"}
{"Question": "TOE + HERE = ROOT", "Answer": "427 + 8797 = 9224"}
{"Question": "DAD + COLD = ALLOW", "Answer": "818 + 9208 = 10026"}
{"Question": "VIA + DATA = TITLE", "Answer": "308 + 9818 = 10126"}
{"Question": "DAD + WORD = RATIO", "Answer": "808 + 9618 = 10426"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEND = CAUSE", "Answer": "808 + 9628 = 10436"}
{"Question": "THE + GENE = SHOOT", "Answer": "608 + 9838 = 10446"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEND = RANGE", "Answer": "808 + 9648 = 10456"}
{"Question": "SUE + HERE = CROSS", "Answer": "658 + 9808 = 10466"}
{"Question": "EYE + TRUE = SUPER", "Answer": "878 + 9608 = 10486"}
{"Question": "DIE + HERE = INNER", "Answer": "218 + 9868 = 10086"}
{"Question": "ERA + DATA = THREE", "Answer": "648 + 9818 = 10466"}
{"Question": "DAD + SEND = ABUSE", "Answer": "818 + 9678 = 10496"}
{"Question": "EYE + RIDE = AWARD", "Answer": "828 + 9368 = 10196"}
{"Question": "MOM + THEM = QUOTE", "Answer": "828 + 9468 = 10296"}
{"Question": "DAD + BEND = COACH", "Answer": "838 + 9478 = 10316"}
{"Question": "EYE + CODE = VIDEO", "Answer": "838 + 9648 = 10486"}
{"Question": "THE + GENE = TOOTH", "Answer": "168 + 9848 = 10016"}
{"Question": "THE + DIET = TOOTH", "Answer": "165 + 9851 = 10016"}
{"Question": "EGG + BIKE = ESSAY", "Answer": "155 + 9871 = 10026"}
{"Question": "EYE + BILL = ESSAY", "Answer": "171 + 9866 = 10037"}
{"Question": "CEO + LOSE = COOL", "Answer": "971 + 8147 = 9118"}
{"Question": "TEA + WHAT = TOOTH", "Answer": "147 + 9871 = 10018"}
{"Question": "HER + URGE = TOOTH", "Answer": "752 + 9265 = 10017"}
{"Question": "EYE + BURY = INNER", "Answer": "353 + 9685 = 10038"}
{"Question": "TOO + LIST = SOIL", "Answer": "411 + 5764 = 6175"}
{"Question": "MOM + HERO = OFFER", "Answer": "414 + 9651 = 10065"}
{"Question": "MOM + HERO = PROOF", "Answer": "424 + 9802 = 10226"}
{"Question": "MOM + ALSO = SCOPE", "Answer": "424 + 9812 = 10236"}
{"Question": "SEE + THIS = IRISH", "Answer": "433 + 9714 = 10147"}
{"Question": "MOM + AUTO = TREAT", "Answer": "474 + 9817 = 10291"}
{"Question": "TEN + ONCE = EVENT", "Answer": "615 + 9541 = 10156"}
{"Question": "TEA + CAKE = ELECT", "Answer": "615 + 9581 = 10196"}
{"Question": "EYE + TINY = YOUTH", "Answer": "515 + 9781 = 10296"}
{"Question": "EYE + TALL = FIFTY", "Answer": "575 + 9622 = 10197"}
{"Question": "MOM + SELL = FALSE", "Answer": "565 + 9833 = 10398"}
{"Question": "EGG + ROPE = PAPER", "Answer": "544 + 9615 = 10159"}
{"Question": "DAD + KNEE = CHECK", "Answer": "575 + 9844 = 10419"}
{"Question": "DAD + LESS = SMILE", "Answer": "686 + 9711 = 10397"}
{"Question": "DAD + CELL = TABLE", "Answer": "606 + 9822 = 10428"}
{"Question": "EYE + ARMY = MINOR", "Answer": "626 + 9812 = 10438"}
{"Question": "EYE + BODY = VIDEO", "Answer": "626 + 9842 = 10468"}
{"Question": "EYE + ARMY = SOLAR", "Answer": "626 + 9872 = 10498"}
{"Question": "EGG + SHOE = ORDER", "Answer": "644 + 9716 = 10360"}
{"Question": "CEO + NOTE = EVENT", "Answer": "417 + 9781 = 10198"}
{"Question": "EYE + TINY = ASSET", "Answer": "727 + 9352 = 10079"}
{"Question": "EYE + LADY = MODEL", "Answer": "727 + 9852 = 10579"}
{"Question": "DAD + FLEE = LESS", "Answer": "767 + 4533 = 5300"}
{"Question": "EYE + HOLY = LAYER", "Answer": "757 + 9815 = 10572"}
{"Question": "EYE + BUSY = SHOUT", "Answer": "767 + 9816 = 10583"}
{"Question": "DAD + BELL = MAYBE", "Answer": "707 + 9588 = 10295"}
{"Question": "EYE + ARMY = MOTOR", "Answer": "787 + 9518 = 10305"}
{"Question": "CEO + TONE = ELECT", "Answer": "318 + 9821 = 10139"}
{"Question": "ADD + GENE = ORDER", "Answer": "422 + 9858 = 10280"}
{"Question": "EYE + LADY = ORDER", "Answer": "828 + 9752 = 10580"}
{"Question": "DAD + BILL = SALES", "Answer": "808 + 9533 = 10341"}
{"Question": "EYE + BILL = SALES", "Answer": "848 + 9533 = 10381"}
{"Question": "TOO + SALT = LOTS", "Answer": "844 + 2638 = 3482"}
{"Question": "EGG + TYPE = APPLY", "Answer": "844 + 9208 = 10052"}
{"Question": "EYE + BURY = MAYOR", "Answer": "848 + 9624 = 10472"}
{"Question": "EYE + BURY = PROOF", "Answer": "848 + 9704 = 10552"}
{"Question": "EYE + LOSS = APPLY", "Answer": "838 + 9255 = 10093"}
{"Question": "MOM + FLEE = TOTAL", "Answer": "808 + 9355 = 10163"}
{"Question": "MOM + AUTO = FLOAT", "Answer": "858 + 9735 = 10593"}
{"Question": "THE + BELL = TOOTH", "Answer": "148 + 9866 = 10014"}
{"Question": "EYE + GRAY = FAVOR", "Answer": "868 + 9406 = 10274"}
{"Question": "EYE + GRAY = AFTER", "Answer": "868 + 9416 = 10284"}
{"Question": "EYE + STAY = COAST", "Answer": "868 + 9426 = 10294"}
{"Question": "DAD + BELL = STATE", "Answer": "838 + 9466 = 10304"}
{"Question": "EYE + MASS = APPLY", "Answer": "858 + 9177 = 10035"}
{"Question": "EYE + BUSY = ASSET", "Answer": "878 + 9207 = 10085"}
{"Question": "EYE + GRAY = LATER", "Answer": "878 + 9507 = 10385"}
{"Question": "MOM + ALSO = STEAL", "Answer": "878 + 9517 = 10395"}
{"Question": "PAN + ONTO = ADAPT", "Answer": "615 + 9549 = 10164"}
{"Question": "HIM + MERE = IRISH", "Answer": "519 + 9606 = 10125"}
{"Question": "SIT + THUS = FIFTH", "Answer": "609 + 9586 = 10195"}
{"Question": "DAD + ONTO = AGAIN", "Answer": "616 + 9529 = 10145"}
{"Question": "SIT + THUS = IRISH", "Answer": "619 + 9546 = 10165"}
{"Question": "MOM + AREA = ROLL", "Answer": "626 + 4574 = 5200"}
{"Question": "DAD + ELSE = PANEL", "Answer": "707 + 9689 = 10396"}
{"Question": "DAD + HIGH = ANGER", "Answer": "717 + 9529 = 10246"}
{"Question": "DAD + ONTO = TRAIN", "Answer": "737 + 9619 = 10356"}
{"Question": "DAD + TENT = AGREE", "Answer": "717 + 9649 = 10366"}
{"Question": "DIG + GLAD = SHALL", "Answer": "729 + 9637 = 10366"}
{"Question": "EAR + ROLE = ALLOW", "Answer": "819 + 9208 = 10027"}
{"Question": "EAR + RIDE = AWARD", "Answer": "819 + 9378 = 10197"}
{"Question": "DAD + ELSE = SHALL", "Answer": "858 + 9719 = 10577"}
{"Question": "MOM + DEAD = BLAME", "Answer": "828 + 9759 = 10587"}
{"Question": "THE + DEAD = TOOTH", "Answer": "178 + 9839 = 10017"}
{"Question": "HER + RUSH = TASTE", "Answer": "879 + 9438 = 10317"}
{"Question": "DAD + GENE = EARN", "Answer": "656 + 7848 = 8504"}
{"Question": "DAD + TOWN = ALLOW", "Answer": "212 + 9875 = 10087"}
{"Question": "DAD + LOTS = TASTE", "Answer": "404 + 9812 = 10216"}
{"Question": "WHO + POLE = SHELL", "Answer": "804 + 9462 = 10266"}
{"Question": "DAD + FOUR = AGREE", "Answer": "414 + 9852 = 10266"}
{"Question": "MOM + USED = ODDS", "Answer": "535 + 2914 = 3449"}
{"Question": "TEA + HANG = EIGHT", "Answer": "715 + 9582 = 10297"}
{"Question": "DNA + BASE = SPEED", "Answer": "825 + 9513 = 10338"}
{"Question": "DAD + THEN = AGENT", "Answer": "515 + 9834 = 10349"}
{"Question": "DAD + CITE = EXACT", "Answer": "535 + 9861 = 10396"}
{"Question": "DAD + BIKE = CRACK", "Answer": "545 + 9872 = 10417"}
{"Question": "DAD + CREW = EAGER", "Answer": "606 + 9812 = 10418"}
{"Question": "DAD + TYPE = HAPPY", "Answer": "606 + 9842 = 10448"}
{"Question": "DAD + LOSE = STEEL", "Answer": "626 + 9713 = 10339"}
{"Question": "MOM + ABLE = ORDER", "Answer": "616 + 9724 = 10340"}
{"Question": "DNA + CASH = SPEED", "Answer": "836 + 9612 = 10448"}
{"Question": "MOM + SEAT = LOOSE", "Answer": "707 + 9386 = 10093"}
{"Question": "DAD + BELT = CAUSE", "Answer": "707 + 9538 = 10245"}
{"Question": "TEN + CAST = FENCE", "Answer": "703 + 9687 = 10390"}
{"Question": "DAD + BELT = MATCH", "Answer": "707 + 9835 = 10542"}
{"Question": "DAD + REST = AFTER", "Answer": "717 + 9542 = 10259"}
{"Question": "DAD + MENU = ARGUE", "Answer": "717 + 9568 = 10285"}
{"Question": "DAD + BORN = AGREE", "Answer": "717 + 9638 = 10355"}
{"Question": "MOM + BEND = ORDER", "Answer": "717 + 9643 = 10360"}
{"Question": "DAD + HUGE = GREEN", "Answer": "737 + 9815 = 10552"}
{"Question": "EYE + BUCK = CARRY", "Answer": "737 + 9816 = 10553"}
{"Question": "EYE + INTO = OFTEN", "Answer": "727 + 9851 = 10578"}
{"Question": "CEO + HOST = TASTE", "Answer": "587 + 9731 = 10318"}
{"Question": "DAD + THUS = SOUTH", "Answer": "747 + 9851 = 10598"}
{"Question": "DAD + SHUT = TRUTH", "Answer": "757 + 9861 = 10618"}
{"Question": "DAD + NEWS = AWARE", "Answer": "818 + 9305 = 10123"}
{"Question": "DAD + TRUE = PAPER", "Answer": "808 + 9345 = 10153"}
{"Question": "DAD + FROM = PAPER", "Answer": "808 + 9365 = 10173"}
{"Question": "EYE + DRAG = PAPER", "Answer": "878 + 9305 = 10183"}
{"Question": "BIG + DATA = TIGHT", "Answer": "503 + 9818 = 10321"}
{"Question": "DAD + BELT = LARGE", "Answer": "808 + 9517 = 10325"}
{"Question": "DAD + MYTH = CARRY", "Answer": "808 + 9527 = 10335"}
{"Question": "MOM + DEAL = SALES", "Answer": "848 + 9503 = 10351"}
{"Question": "DAD + BOWL = SALES", "Answer": "808 + 9563 = 10371"}
{"Question": "EYE + GRAB = LABEL", "Answer": "878 + 9503 = 10381"}
{"Question": "DAD + BELT = LATIN", "Answer": "808 + 9715 = 10523"}
{"Question": "DAD + BLUE = GUESS", "Answer": "828 + 9705 = 10533"}
{"Question": "DAD + LEFT = ANGLE", "Answer": "818 + 9476 = 10294"}
{"Question": "DNA + FATE = TREAT", "Answer": "568 + 9813 = 10381"}
{"Question": "TEA + QUIT = IRAQI", "Answer": "873 + 9518 = 10391"}
{"Question": "DAD + NICE = AGENT", "Answer": "818 + 9674 = 10492"}
{"Question": "THE + BEAN = TOOTH", "Answer": "138 + 9875 = 10013"}
{"Question": "FEE + FLEE = GIFT", "Answer": "366 + 3766 = 4132"}
{"Question": "FEE + FLEE = LESS", "Answer": "511 + 5611 = 6122"}
{"Question": "FEE + FLEE = LIFT", "Answer": "577 + 5677 = 6254"}
{"Question": "FEE + FREE = EARN", "Answer": "677 + 6577 = 7254"}
{"Question": "FEE + FLEE = LEAD", "Answer": "766 + 7866 = 8632"}
{"Question": "SEE + STEP = PAST", "Answer": "422 + 4725 = 5147"}
{"Question": "TEA + TREE = RATE", "Answer": "470 + 4577 = 5047"}
{"Question": "TEA + TREE = READ", "Answer": "512 + 5611 = 6123"}
{"Question": "SEE + STEP = TOSS", "Answer": "577 + 5678 = 6255"}
{"Question": "SEE + STEP = TEST", "Answer": "633 + 6734 = 7367"}
{"Question": "FLY + FALL = LEAF", "Answer": "679 + 6577 = 7256"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDE = DEEP", "Answer": "677 + 6875 = 7552"}
{"Question": "ALL + ABLE = BEER", "Answer": "833 + 8937 = 9770"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDE = BELL", "Answer": "855 + 8756 = 9611"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDE = DEAD", "Answer": "899 + 8190 = 9089"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDE = INNER", "Answer": "922 + 9124 = 10046"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDE = MODEL", "Answer": "922 + 9324 = 10246"}
{"Question": "FEW + FREE = SHELF", "Answer": "927 + 9322 = 10249"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDS = ORDER", "Answer": "922 + 9328 = 10250"}
{"Question": "SEE + STEP = PHOTO", "Answer": "922 + 9421 = 10343"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDE = CHEEK", "Answer": "922 + 9524 = 10446"}
{"Question": "FEE + FUEL = PROOF", "Answer": "922 + 9527 = 10449"}
{"Question": "FEW + FREE = START", "Answer": "928 + 9522 = 10450"}
{"Question": "SEE + STEP = ADOPT", "Answer": "922 + 9624 = 10546"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDS = THESE", "Answer": "922 + 9724 = 10646"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDE = BUYER", "Answer": "922 + 9824 = 10746"}
{"Question": "FEE + FUEL = SHELF", "Answer": "933 + 9436 = 10369"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "933 + 9437 = 10370"}
{"Question": "FEE + FUEL = TREAT", "Answer": "933 + 9438 = 10371"}
{"Question": "FLY + FALL = TREAT", "Answer": "938 + 9733 = 10671"}
{"Question": "TEN + TREE = ADAPT", "Answer": "945 + 9244 = 10189"}
{"Question": "TEA + TREE = PHOTO", "Answer": "948 + 9344 = 10292"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDE = TODAY", "Answer": "944 + 9548 = 10492"}
{"Question": "ADD + AIDE = TREAT", "Answer": "944 + 9847 = 10791"}
{"Question": "FEE + FACE = DEAD", "Answer": "322 + 3972 = 4294"}
{"Question": "TOE + TREE = ROLL", "Answer": "645 + 6755 = 7400"}
{"Question": "ADD + ACID = BILL", "Answer": "755 + 7645 = 8400"}
{"Question": "SEE + SHOE = HELL", "Answer": "766 + 7856 = 8622"}
{"Question": "MRS + MISS = INNER", "Answer": "942 + 9122 = 10064"}
{"Question": "FEE + FADE = SPEND", "Answer": "922 + 9342 = 10264"}
{"Question": "ADD + ACID = TODAY", "Answer": "922 + 9372 = 10294"}
{"Question": "TIE + TREE = PHOTO", "Answer": "972 + 9522 = 10494"}
{"Question": "FEE + FADE = BROAD", "Answer": "922 + 9642 = 10564"}
{"Question": "FEE + FADE = BLOOD", "Answer": "922 + 9742 = 10664"}
{"Question": "FEE + FACE = MUSIC", "Answer": "922 + 9842 = 10764"}
{"Question": "THE + TREE = FIFTH", "Answer": "963 + 9233 = 10196"}
{"Question": "SEE + SAFE = IRISH", "Answer": "944 + 9254 = 10198"}
{"Question": "MRS + MESS = ERROR", "Answer": "905 + 9155 = 10060"}
{"Question": "ADD + ACID = PRIOR", "Answer": "955 + 9325 = 10280"}
{"Question": "ADD + ACID = ORDER", "Answer": "955 + 9625 = 10580"}
{"Question": "BUS + BOSS = UNION", "Answer": "915 + 9755 = 10670"}
{"Question": "ADD + ACID = FENCE", "Answer": "955 + 9825 = 10780"}
{"Question": "ADD + ACID = INDEX", "Answer": "966 + 9716 = 10682"}
{"Question": "FEE + FILE = BLOOD", "Answer": "966 + 9806 = 10772"}
{"Question": "FEE + FATE = TODAY", "Answer": "966 + 9816 = 10782"}
{"Question": "SEE + SIDE = ADAPT", "Answer": "977 + 9207 = 10184"}
{"Question": "SEE + SHOE = FORTH", "Answer": "977 + 9407 = 10384"}
{"Question": "SEE + SAFE = FLESH", "Answer": "977 + 9817 = 10794"}
{"Question": "SEE + SURE = IRISH", "Answer": "988 + 9208 = 10196"}
{"Question": "MRS + MESS = CRIME", "Answer": "908 + 9688 = 10596"}
{"Question": "MRS + MESS = DRAMA", "Answer": "908 + 9788 = 10696"}
{"Question": "SEE + SLIP = LOSS", "Answer": "466 + 4578 = 5044"}
{"Question": "RED + ROSE = ODDS", "Answer": "654 + 6795 = 7449"}
{"Question": "FEE + FLAT = DATA", "Answer": "855 + 8761 = 9616"}
{"Question": "DNA + DEAR = AWARD", "Answer": "971 + 9218 = 10189"}
{"Question": "LET + LOTS = TITLE", "Answer": "981 + 9217 = 10198"}
{"Question": "TOO + TAKE = ASSET", "Answer": "922 + 9157 = 10079"}
{"Question": "TWO + TELL = ERROR", "Answer": "958 + 9122 = 10080"}
{"Question": "FEE + FAIL = SHELF", "Answer": "922 + 9357 = 10279"}
{"Question": "ADD + ABLE = ORDER", "Answer": "922 + 9358 = 10280"}
{"Question": "EGG + EARN = PHONE", "Answer": "922 + 9457 = 10379"}
{"Question": "TOO + TEAR = CHART", "Answer": "922 + 9657 = 10579"}
{"Question": "ALL + AIDE = ORDER", "Answer": "922 + 9658 = 10580"}
{"Question": "ADD + ABLE = STEAL", "Answer": "922 + 9675 = 10597"}
{"Question": "ADD + AUTO = SHEET", "Answer": "922 + 9853 = 10775"}
{"Question": "TOO + TAKE = SHEET", "Answer": "922 + 9857 = 10779"}
{"Question": "ILL + IDEA = AWARE", "Answer": "933 + 9241 = 10174"}
{"Question": "TOO + TEAR = APART", "Answer": "944 + 9215 = 10159"}
{"Question": "SEE + STAR = ADAPT", "Answer": "944 + 9218 = 10162"}
{"Question": "SEE + STOP = ADAPT", "Answer": "944 + 9238 = 10182"}
{"Question": "LET + LOSS = TITLE", "Answer": "951 + 9244 = 10195"}
{"Question": "EGG + EACH = TIGHT", "Answer": "944 + 9527 = 10471"}
{"Question": "MAN + MIND = DRAMA", "Answer": "954 + 9641 = 10595"}
{"Question": "LEG + LATE = TIGHT", "Answer": "947 + 9814 = 10761"}
{"Question": "BUS + BASE = TREAT", "Answer": "934 + 9847 = 10781"}
{"Question": "SEE + STAR = APART", "Answer": "955 + 9217 = 10172"}
{"Question": "ILL + INTO = AGAIN", "Answer": "955 + 9237 = 10192"}
{"Question": "ADD + ABLE = RURAL", "Answer": "955 + 9238 = 10193"}
{"Question": "FEE + FLAG = IRAQI", "Answer": "955 + 9326 = 10281"}
{"Question": "ILL + IDEA = BREAD", "Answer": "955 + 9328 = 10283"}
{"Question": "ADD + ALSO = KNOCK", "Answer": "955 + 9726 = 10681"}
{"Question": "ADD + ABLE = TREAT", "Answer": "955 + 9736 = 10691"}
{"Question": "ADD + AUTO = SHOUT", "Answer": "955 + 9827 = 10782"}
{"Question": "ADD + ABLE = SLEEP", "Answer": "966 + 9807 = 10773"}
{"Question": "SEE + SLIP = IMPLY", "Answer": "966 + 9817 = 10783"}
{"Question": "SEE + SHIP = IRISH", "Answer": "977 + 9215 = 10192"}
{"Question": "CEO + CAKE = KNOCK", "Answer": "974 + 9517 = 10491"}
{"Question": "ALL + AIDE = DREAM", "Answer": "977 + 9615 = 10592"}
{"Question": "HIS + HOST = TOOTH", "Answer": "938 + 9081 = 10019"}
{"Question": "TOO + THIN = FIFTH", "Answer": "988 + 9204 = 10192"}
{"Question": "ALL + AUTO = TOTAL", "Answer": "988 + 9210 = 10198"}
{"Question": "END + EARN = ORDER", "Answer": "982 + 9308 = 10290"}
{"Question": "NOT + ONTO = THAN", "Answer": "578 + 7587 = 8165"}
{"Question": "NOT + ONTO = BEAN", "Answer": "587 + 8578 = 9165"}
{"Question": "NOT + ONTO = TANK", "Answer": "678 + 7687 = 8365"}
{"Question": "NOT + ONTO = TOUR", "Answer": "756 + 5765 = 6521"}
{"Question": "ADD + DARE = DEER", "Answer": "155 + 5183 = 5338"}
{"Question": "RAW + AREA = WEAR", "Answer": "523 + 2502 = 3025"}
{"Question": "ADD + DARE = READ", "Answer": "522 + 2530 = 3052"}
{"Question": "EGG + GEAR = RARE", "Answer": "577 + 7508 = 8085"}
{"Question": "EGG + GEAR = AREA", "Answer": "577 + 7581 = 8158"}
{"Question": "ETC + TENT = NOTE", "Answer": "587 + 8598 = 9185"}
{"Question": "ADD + DARK = AREA", "Answer": "655 + 5621 = 6276"}
{"Question": "EGG + GEAR = EARN", "Answer": "655 + 5628 = 6283"}
{"Question": "ADD + DARE = REAL", "Answer": "677 + 7683 = 8360"}
{"Question": "NOR + ONTO = TURN", "Answer": "725 + 2732 = 3457"}
{"Question": "ADD + DARE = AREA", "Answer": "766 + 6751 = 7517"}
{"Question": "EGG + GEAR = RACE", "Answer": "788 + 8759 = 9547"}
{"Question": "EGG + GEAR = CARE", "Answer": "811 + 1867 = 2678"}
{"Question": "ADD + DATE = TELL", "Answer": "855 + 5867 = 6722"}
{"Question": "ADD + DARE = OVER", "Answer": "855 + 5894 = 6749"}
{"Question": "ETC + TENT = EVEN", "Answer": "873 + 7807 = 8680"}
{"Question": "AIR + RARE = AREA", "Answer": "847 + 7871 = 8718"}
{"Question": "ADD + DATE = TEEN", "Answer": "933 + 3948 = 4881"}
{"Question": "ALL + LAST = DATA", "Answer": "977 + 7952 = 8929"}
{"Question": "RAW + AREA = RARE", "Answer": "982 + 8908 = 9890"}
{"Question": "SEE + EVEN = NEWS", "Answer": "522 + 2723 = 3245"}
{"Question": "FEE + EVEN = LEAF", "Answer": "533 + 3832 = 4365"}
{"Question": "EGG + GANG = AREA", "Answer": "811 + 1271 = 2082"}
{"Question": "ODD + DEAD = AREA", "Answer": "711 + 1321 = 2032"}
{"Question": "FEE + EASE = SEAT", "Answer": "722 + 2532 = 3254"}
{"Question": "FEE + ELSE = SELF", "Answer": "633 + 3743 = 4376"}
{"Question": "YES + EASE = STAY", "Answer": "578 + 7687 = 8265"}
{"Question": "TEN + EASE = SEAT", "Answer": "817 + 1321 = 2138"}
{"Question": "DAY + AREA = YARD", "Answer": "312 + 1871 = 2183"}
{"Question": "EGG + GOLF = FEEL", "Answer": "377 + 7958 = 8335"}
{"Question": "TEA + ELSE = SEAT", "Answer": "413 + 1721 = 2134"}
{"Question": "LIE + EVEN = LINE", "Answer": "837 + 7470 = 8307"}
{"Question": "ADD + DROP = ROLL", "Answer": "566 + 6734 = 7300"}
{"Question": "ODD + DARE = AREA", "Answer": "577 + 7841 = 8418"}
{"Question": "ALL + TALL = THAT", "Answer": "366 + 2366 = 2732"}
{"Question": "ALL + HALL = THAN", "Answer": "577 + 1577 = 2154"}
{"Question": "ALL + BALL = DEAD", "Answer": "577 + 3577 = 4154"}
{"Question": "ALL + BALL = LEAD", "Answer": "577 + 6577 = 7154"}
{"Question": "ILL + BILL = AGAIN", "Answer": "577 + 9577 = 10154"}
{"Question": "ALL + CALL = LOCK", "Answer": "588 + 7588 = 8176"}
{"Question": "ALL + MALL = ARMY", "Answer": "677 + 5677 = 6354"}
{"Question": "ALL + BALL = AREA", "Answer": "688 + 5688 = 6376"}
{"Question": "ALL + BALL = EXTRA", "Answer": "688 + 9688 = 10376"}
{"Question": "ALL + BALL = ALSO", "Answer": "755 + 6755 = 7510"}
{"Question": "ALL + HALL = THAT", "Answer": "788 + 5788 = 6576"}
{"Question": "ALL + BALL = CHEAP", "Answer": "788 + 9788 = 10576"}
{"Question": "ALL + BALL = ELSE", "Answer": "877 + 3877 = 4754"}
{"Question": "ALL + BALL = PILOT", "Answer": "877 + 9877 = 10754"}
{"Question": "ALL + CALL = LACK", "Answer": "988 + 7988 = 8976"}
{"Question": "ADD + FADE = INNER", "Answer": "522 + 9524 = 10046"}
{"Question": "OLD + ROLL = INNER", "Answer": "527 + 9522 = 10049"}
{"Question": "ODD + BODY = ERROR", "Answer": "522 + 9528 = 10050"}
{"Question": "SEE + USED = OCCUR", "Answer": "544 + 9548 = 10092"}
{"Question": "SEE + USER = APART", "Answer": "566 + 9562 = 10128"}
{"Question": "ILL + FILE = AGAIN", "Answer": "577 + 9576 = 10153"}
{"Question": "ADD + FADE = AREA", "Answer": "588 + 4587 = 5175"}
{"Question": "ALL + TALE = EVENT", "Answer": "588 + 9581 = 10169"}
{"Question": "TOO + STOP = ADAPT", "Answer": "588 + 9587 = 10175"}
{"Question": "ALL + PALE = DEEP", "Answer": "611 + 3612 = 4223"}
{"Question": "ASK + PASS = SLEEP", "Answer": "618 + 9611 = 10229"}
{"Question": "ODD + CODE = VIDEO", "Answer": "622 + 9624 = 10246"}
{"Question": "ILL + MILK = DRAMA", "Answer": "644 + 9648 = 10292"}
{"Question": "SEE + USER = PURE", "Answer": "655 + 3650 = 4305"}
{"Question": "ILL + FILE = DEAD", "Answer": "655 + 7653 = 8308"}
{"Question": "ADD + FADE = CIVIL", "Answer": "655 + 9652 = 10307"}
{"Question": "ALL + SALT = METER", "Answer": "655 + 9653 = 10308"}
{"Question": "ILL + FILM = AHEAD", "Answer": "655 + 9657 = 10312"}
{"Question": "ILL + WILD = ORDER", "Answer": "677 + 9673 = 10350"}
{"Question": "ADD + FADE = CROSS", "Answer": "677 + 9678 = 10355"}
{"Question": "ILL + FILE = LEFT", "Answer": "688 + 7683 = 8371"}
{"Question": "NET + KNEE = THANK", "Answer": "681 + 9688 = 10369"}
{"Question": "ODD + CODE = BASIS", "Answer": "688 + 9685 = 10373"}
{"Question": "RED + TREE = DATA", "Answer": "713 + 2711 = 3424"}
{"Question": "ALL + HALF = LUNCH", "Answer": "711 + 9718 = 10429"}
{"Question": "ADD + FADE = CHEEK", "Answer": "722 + 9724 = 10446"}
{"Question": "ADD + FADE = BRIEF", "Answer": "733 + 9736 = 10469"}
{"Question": "NEW + KNEE = NEWS", "Answer": "749 + 6744 = 7493"}
{"Question": "ADD + LADY = MEDIA", "Answer": "744 + 9743 = 10487"}
{"Question": "TOO + STOP = CLOSE", "Answer": "744 + 9748 = 10492"}
{"Question": "TOO + STOP = BOSS", "Answer": "755 + 1756 = 2511"}
{"Question": "ALL + HALF = COLOR", "Answer": "755 + 9753 = 10508"}
{"Question": "SEE + USER = AHEAD", "Answer": "755 + 9758 = 10513"}
{"Question": "ADD + FADE = EXTRA", "Answer": "766 + 9761 = 10527"}
{"Question": "SEE + USED = DUST", "Answer": "788 + 5786 = 6574"}
{"Question": "ALL + HALF = FORTH", "Answer": "788 + 9781 = 10569"}
{"Question": "ODD + BODY = PRIOR", "Answer": "788 + 9782 = 10570"}
{"Question": "ILL + FILM = DRAMA", "Answer": "822 + 9824 = 10646"}
{"Question": "ALL + PALE = SWEEP", "Answer": "833 + 9836 = 10669"}
{"Question": "ALL + HALF = THAT", "Answer": "844 + 6843 = 7687"}
{"Question": "ILL + FILE = BASIS", "Answer": "844 + 9842 = 10686"}
{"Question": "ADD + LADY = EQUAL", "Answer": "844 + 9845 = 10689"}
{"Question": "ALL + SALE = TEST", "Answer": "855 + 1857 = 2712"}
{"Question": "ALL + HALF = LESS", "Answer": "855 + 4856 = 5711"}
{"Question": "SEE + USER = SURE", "Answer": "855 + 7850 = 8705"}
{"Question": "ALL + HALF = FEWER", "Answer": "855 + 9851 = 10706"}
{"Question": "TOO + STOP = LIMIT", "Answer": "855 + 9853 = 10708"}
{"Question": "ILL + FILE = AHEAD", "Answer": "855 + 9857 = 10712"}
{"Question": "ALL + SALE = MESS", "Answer": "866 + 3867 = 4733"}
{"Question": "ALL + MALE = LESS", "Answer": "866 + 5867 = 6733"}
{"Question": "NEW + KNEE = BROWN", "Answer": "862 + 9866 = 10728"}
{"Question": "ADD + FADE = GUESS", "Answer": "866 + 9867 = 10733"}
{"Question": "TOO + STOP = KNOCK", "Answer": "877 + 9874 = 10751"}
{"Question": "ADD + FADE = INDEX", "Answer": "877 + 9875 = 10752"}
{"Question": "ADD + FADE = DEAL", "Answer": "944 + 3948 = 4892"}
{"Question": "ADD + RARE = DEAD", "Answer": "533 + 2520 = 3053"}
{"Question": "ERA + REAL = BIBLE", "Answer": "593 + 9532 = 10125"}
{"Question": "DIE + IDEA = AWARD", "Answer": "594 + 9541 = 10135"}
{"Question": "ILL + NINE = PAPER", "Answer": "544 + 9593 = 10137"}
{"Question": "ADD + BABY = RURAL", "Answer": "566 + 9592 = 10158"}
{"Question": "ILL + NINE = AGAIN", "Answer": "566 + 9593 = 10159"}
{"Question": "ILL + NINE = AHEAD", "Answer": "622 + 9693 = 10315"}
{"Question": "ODD + NONE = ASIAN", "Answer": "622 + 9697 = 10319"}
{"Question": "ADD + RARE = INDEX", "Answer": "633 + 9692 = 10325"}
{"Question": "TIE + ITEM = MARRY", "Answer": "694 + 9641 = 10335"}
{"Question": "DIE + IDEA = BLOOD", "Answer": "694 + 9642 = 10336"}
{"Question": "ILL + NINE = CHEEK", "Answer": "644 + 9693 = 10337"}
{"Question": "ERA + READ = DROP", "Answer": "625 + 2653 = 3278"}
{"Question": "ILL + NINE = OPEN", "Answer": "655 + 7672 = 8327"}
{"Question": "ILL + NINE = TEEN", "Answer": "655 + 8683 = 9338"}
{"Question": "ASK + SAKE = EXTRA", "Answer": "695 + 9651 = 10346"}
{"Question": "ADD + RARE = EQUAL", "Answer": "677 + 9691 = 10368"}
{"Question": "ILL + NINE = BRAIN", "Answer": "677 + 9692 = 10369"}
{"Question": "ACT + CALL = TOPIC", "Answer": "691 + 9688 = 10379"}
{"Question": "ALL + RARE = DEAD", "Answer": "722 + 5754 = 6476"}
{"Question": "ERA + REAL = LACK", "Answer": "714 + 1742 = 2456"}
{"Question": "OFF + NONE = VIDEO", "Answer": "744 + 9793 = 10537"}
{"Question": "ILL + NINE = OCEAN", "Answer": "744 + 9795 = 10539"}
{"Question": "ADD + BABY = MEDIA", "Answer": "755 + 9792 = 10547"}
{"Question": "ADD + RARE = UNDER", "Answer": "755 + 9794 = 10549"}
{"Question": "ADD + BABY = CHEEK", "Answer": "766 + 9792 = 10558"}
{"Question": "ERA + REAL = LOVER", "Answer": "798 + 9781 = 10579"}
{"Question": "SUE + USER = SURE", "Answer": "873 + 7830 = 8703"}
{"Question": "ILL + NINE = AFTER", "Answer": "833 + 9892 = 10725"}
{"Question": "ADD + RARE = IDEA", "Answer": "877 + 4841 = 5718"}
{"Question": "ERA + READ = CHAIR", "Answer": "897 + 9872 = 10769"}
{"Question": "ODD + NONE = DEEP", "Answer": "944 + 3938 = 4882"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAND = ARAB", "Answer": "522 + 4532 = 5054"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARD = INNER", "Answer": "522 + 9542 = 10064"}
{"Question": "ADD + SAND = LOOSE", "Answer": "522 + 9572 = 10094"}
{"Question": "ODD + ROAD = ALLOW", "Answer": "544 + 9514 = 10058"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAND = RURAL", "Answer": "566 + 9586 = 10152"}
{"Question": "ODD + LOAD = APPLE", "Answer": "577 + 9517 = 10094"}
{"Question": "ODD + LOAD = ALLY", "Answer": "588 + 1528 = 2116"}
{"Question": "LIE + FLEE = LOSS", "Answer": "578 + 4588 = 5166"}
{"Question": "ODD + LOAD = DRAMA", "Answer": "611 + 9621 = 10232"}
{"Question": "ODD + WORD = PRIOR", "Answer": "655 + 9605 = 10260"}
{"Question": "ODD + ROAD = AREA", "Answer": "677 + 3647 = 4324"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAND = ENJOY", "Answer": "677 + 9607 = 10284"}
{"Question": "ODD + LOAD = CRACK", "Answer": "677 + 9637 = 10314"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAND = CHEAP", "Answer": "677 + 9687 = 10364"}
{"Question": "LIE + FLEE = COOL", "Answer": "648 + 1688 = 2336"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARD = AREA", "Answer": "688 + 5638 = 6326"}
{"Question": "LIE + FLEE = SHALL", "Answer": "678 + 9688 = 10366"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAND = DOUBT", "Answer": "711 + 9781 = 10492"}
{"Question": "ITS + KISS = TROOP", "Answer": "713 + 9733 = 10446"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAND = TODAY", "Answer": "744 + 9734 = 10478"}
{"Question": "LIE + FLEE = LESS", "Answer": "745 + 6755 = 7500"}
{"Question": "ILL + GIRL = ORDER", "Answer": "755 + 9705 = 10460"}
{"Question": "ODD + LOUD = UNION", "Answer": "755 + 9715 = 10470"}
{"Question": "ODD + LOAD = BALL", "Answer": "766 + 2756 = 3522"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARD = THREE", "Answer": "766 + 9756 = 10522"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARD = BRICK", "Answer": "788 + 9708 = 10496"}
{"Question": "ODD + COLD = LIMIT", "Answer": "788 + 9718 = 10506"}
{"Question": "OIL + ROLL = IRON", "Answer": "871 + 6811 = 7682"}
{"Question": "LIE + FLEE = LIFT", "Answer": "861 + 7811 = 8672"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAND = HONOR", "Answer": "833 + 9873 = 10706"}
{"Question": "ALL + RAIL = EXTRA", "Answer": "844 + 9854 = 10698"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOND = PRIOR", "Answer": "855 + 9825 = 10680"}
{"Question": "ADD + LAND = BELL", "Answer": "866 + 2856 = 3722"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAND = INDEX", "Answer": "866 + 9806 = 10672"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAND = CROSS", "Answer": "866 + 9856 = 10722"}
{"Question": "ALL + FAIL = COLOR", "Answer": "877 + 9827 = 10704"}
{"Question": "LIE + FLEE = AHEAD", "Answer": "837 + 9877 = 10714"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARD = UNDER", "Answer": "877 + 9847 = 10724"}
{"Question": "LIE + FLEE = DRESS", "Answer": "867 + 9877 = 10744"}
{"Question": "EAT + TELL = ELSE", "Answer": "594 + 4511 = 5105"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = ASSET", "Answer": "533 + 9519 = 10052"}
{"Question": "EGG + TENT = INNER", "Answer": "544 + 9509 = 10053"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = ALLOW", "Answer": "544 + 9519 = 10063"}
{"Question": "EGG + TEST = ISSUE", "Answer": "566 + 9509 = 10075"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "566 + 9519 = 10085"}
{"Question": "EGG + TENT = AWARE", "Answer": "566 + 9579 = 10145"}
{"Question": "EAT + TELL = ABLE", "Answer": "598 + 8577 = 9175"}
{"Question": "DIG + EDGE = INNER", "Answer": "517 + 9579 = 10096"}
{"Question": "ILL + KICK = AGAIN", "Answer": "588 + 9569 = 10157"}
{"Question": "ERA + DEAD = IRAQI", "Answer": "602 + 9629 = 10231"}
{"Question": "ETC + CELL = SALES", "Answer": "639 + 9622 = 10261"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOMB = LEVEL", "Answer": "622 + 9679 = 10301"}
{"Question": "NET + ONTO = SCENE", "Answer": "623 + 9639 = 10262"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOMB = MAJOR", "Answer": "644 + 9619 = 10263"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = CABLE", "Answer": "677 + 9609 = 10286"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = ASIDE", "Answer": "677 + 9619 = 10296"}
{"Question": "DIG + EDGE = SALAD", "Answer": "627 + 9679 = 10306"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = THREE", "Answer": "677 + 9689 = 10366"}
{"Question": "ARM + MALL = CRIME", "Answer": "609 + 9688 = 10297"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOMB = METER", "Answer": "688 + 9619 = 10307"}
{"Question": "ADD + EASE = SEAT", "Answer": "722 + 4754 = 5476"}
{"Question": "ADD + EASE = RIVER", "Answer": "722 + 9769 = 10491"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOMB = MEDIA", "Answer": "744 + 9719 = 10463"}
{"Question": "ADD + EASE = TODAY", "Answer": "744 + 9729 = 10473"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOMB = LIMIT", "Answer": "744 + 9759 = 10503"}
{"Question": "ARM + MALL = COLOR", "Answer": "749 + 9755 = 10504"}
{"Question": "NET + ONTO = TOSS", "Answer": "746 + 5765 = 6511"}
{"Question": "EGG + TEST = BASIS", "Answer": "766 + 9759 = 10525"}
{"Question": "EAT + TELL = WASTE", "Answer": "709 + 9788 = 10497"}
{"Question": "NET + ONTO = ASIAN", "Answer": "728 + 9789 = 10517"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = BLAME", "Answer": "788 + 9759 = 10547"}
{"Question": "DOG + EDGE = GOOD", "Answer": "759 + 8798 = 9557"}
{"Question": "OIL + LOSS = IRAQI", "Answer": "819 + 9822 = 10641"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = RIVER", "Answer": "822 + 9859 = 10681"}
{"Question": "ARM + MASS = FLOOR", "Answer": "829 + 9833 = 10662"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = COACH", "Answer": "833 + 9879 = 10712"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOMB = MARRY", "Answer": "844 + 9819 = 10663"}
{"Question": "ADD + GANG = SIGN", "Answer": "855 + 1861 = 2716"}
{"Question": "EAT + TELL = DATA", "Answer": "872 + 2855 = 3727"}
{"Question": "OFF + BOMB = FALL", "Answer": "866 + 5845 = 6711"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = ANGER", "Answer": "866 + 9819 = 10685"}
{"Question": "ADD + EASE = INDEX", "Answer": "866 + 9829 = 10695"}
{"Question": "ADD + EASE = IDEA", "Answer": "877 + 1841 = 2718"}
{"Question": "YET + TYPE = PHOTO", "Answer": "879 + 9817 = 10696"}
{"Question": "ALL + EASE = COLOR", "Answer": "877 + 9829 = 10706"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAD = EDGE", "Answer": "911 + 8908 = 9819"}
{"Question": "NET + ONTO = NONE", "Answer": "935 + 8958 = 9893"}
{"Question": "ADD + BALL = LEAF", "Answer": "566 + 7588 = 8154"}
{"Question": "EGG + MESS = GAME", "Answer": "577 + 6588 = 7165"}
{"Question": "ERA + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "531 + 9514 = 10045"}
{"Question": "ERA + TEAM = ASSET", "Answer": "541 + 9518 = 10059"}
{"Question": "ERA + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "581 + 9514 = 10095"}
{"Question": "EGG + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "522 + 9513 = 10035"}
{"Question": "EGG + HERO = OFFER", "Answer": "522 + 9531 = 10053"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEAN = APPLE", "Answer": "533 + 9512 = 10045"}
{"Question": "ODD + POEM = ERROR", "Answer": "533 + 9517 = 10050"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAKE = ESSAY", "Answer": "533 + 9521 = 10054"}
{"Question": "EGG + HERO = OCCUR", "Answer": "533 + 9541 = 10074"}
{"Question": "ODD + BORN = ERROR", "Answer": "544 + 9506 = 10050"}
{"Question": "ADD + CASH = ESSAY", "Answer": "544 + 9508 = 10052"}
{"Question": "LAP + FLEE = APPLE", "Answer": "510 + 9544 = 10054"}
{"Question": "NET + INTO = ERROR", "Answer": "514 + 9546 = 10060"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEAT = TITLE", "Answer": "544 + 9581 = 10125"}
{"Question": "TEA + STAR = TOSS", "Answer": "576 + 4568 = 5144"}
{"Question": "EGG + LEFT = FREE", "Answer": "566 + 7589 = 8155"}
{"Question": "ADD + SAFE = OFFER", "Answer": "566 + 9507 = 10073"}
{"Question": "ADD + FATE = ELECT", "Answer": "566 + 9571 = 10137"}
{"Question": "ODD + TOUR = APART", "Answer": "566 + 9573 = 10139"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARE = AREA", "Answer": "577 + 4508 = 5085"}
{"Question": "NET + INTO = NONE", "Answer": "587 + 4571 = 5158"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEAT = GATE", "Answer": "577 + 6508 = 7085"}
{"Question": "ADD + SALT = LOOSE", "Answer": "577 + 9516 = 10093"}
{"Question": "EGG + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "577 + 9518 = 10095"}
{"Question": "ADD + SALT = TOTAL", "Answer": "577 + 9581 = 10158"}
{"Question": "ILL + NICE = AGAIN", "Answer": "577 + 9582 = 10159"}
{"Question": "AIR + EARN = INNER", "Answer": "518 + 9580 = 10098"}
{"Question": "ADD + LAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "588 + 9571 = 10159"}
{"Question": "ADD + NAME = DOZEN", "Answer": "611 + 9678 = 10289"}
{"Question": "ALL + EARN = LOVER", "Answer": "611 + 9687 = 10298"}
{"Question": "ADD + GAME = MODEL", "Answer": "622 + 9613 = 10235"}
{"Question": "ADD + PALM = MODEL", "Answer": "622 + 9631 = 10253"}
{"Question": "ADD + FARM = UNDER", "Answer": "622 + 9653 = 10275"}
{"Question": "ILL + VIEW = SOLVE", "Answer": "622 + 9675 = 10297"}
{"Question": "TOO + STIR = ELITE", "Answer": "633 + 9628 = 10261"}
{"Question": "ETC + BELL = COLOR", "Answer": "671 + 9633 = 10304"}
{"Question": "ACT + DATE = ENTER", "Answer": "683 + 9631 = 10314"}
{"Question": "OFF + POEM = DRAMA", "Answer": "644 + 9638 = 10282"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARE = BEER", "Answer": "655 + 1683 = 2338"}
{"Question": "ADD + TAPE = STEP", "Answer": "655 + 3672 = 4327"}
{"Question": "ADD + TAPE = DEEP", "Answer": "655 + 4683 = 5338"}
{"Question": "OUR + BOSS = ARAB", "Answer": "632 + 7655 = 8287"}
{"Question": "ILL + SIGN = GANG", "Answer": "655 + 8694 = 9349"}
{"Question": "ADD + BASE = SPEAK", "Answer": "655 + 9612 = 10267"}
{"Question": "ADD + FATE = EXTRA", "Answer": "655 + 9621 = 10276"}
{"Question": "ADD + CAST = PITCH", "Answer": "655 + 9642 = 10297"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARE = BUYER", "Answer": "655 + 9672 = 10327"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOTH = HELLO", "Answer": "655 + 9681 = 10336"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAKE = CHEEK", "Answer": "655 + 9683 = 10338"}
{"Question": "ADD + EARN = FREE", "Answer": "677 + 1634 = 2311"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARE = BRIEF", "Answer": "677 + 9608 = 10285"}
{"Question": "OFF + MODE = DRAMA", "Answer": "677 + 9615 = 10292"}
{"Question": "ADD + BANK = GREEN", "Answer": "677 + 9658 = 10335"}
{"Question": "AND + EARN = ORDER", "Answer": "682 + 9608 = 10290"}
{"Question": "ADD + RATE = ENTER", "Answer": "688 + 9631 = 10319"}
{"Question": "ADD + PANT = TROOP", "Answer": "688 + 9651 = 10339"}
{"Question": "EGG + HERO = KNOCK", "Answer": "688 + 9653 = 10341"}
{"Question": "ILL + CITE = BASIS", "Answer": "688 + 9675 = 10363"}
{"Question": "AIR + DARE = IDEA", "Answer": "751 + 4716 = 5467"}
{"Question": "EGG + NEAR = EARN", "Answer": "711 + 6745 = 7456"}
{"Question": "ACT + PATH = TROOP", "Answer": "731 + 9718 = 10449"}
{"Question": "ODD + MOST = DRAMA", "Answer": "711 + 9783 = 10494"}
{"Question": "EGG + READ = AREA", "Answer": "722 + 4753 = 5475"}
{"Question": "ADD + EARN = AREA", "Answer": "722 + 6745 = 7467"}
{"Question": "AIR + BALL = ARAB", "Answer": "754 + 6722 = 7476"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAKE = CHEAP", "Answer": "722 + 9754 = 10476"}
{"Question": "RUN + FREE = HONOR", "Answer": "785 + 9722 = 10507"}
{"Question": "TOE + STEP = PHOTO", "Answer": "743 + 9731 = 10474"}
{"Question": "EAR + HERO = AREA", "Answer": "724 + 1748 = 2472"}
{"Question": "USE + FUEL = SELF", "Answer": "734 + 2748 = 3482"}
{"Question": "OUR + BORN = ARAB", "Answer": "724 + 5741 = 6465"}
{"Question": "ADD + BANK = INDEX", "Answer": "744 + 9708 = 10452"}
{"Question": "EGG + YEAR = ANGRY", "Answer": "744 + 9715 = 10459"}
{"Question": "ALL + CARD = SOLAR", "Answer": "744 + 9728 = 10472"}
{"Question": "ADD + RAIL = COLOR", "Answer": "744 + 9765 = 10509"}
{"Question": "ADD + SALT = ELITE", "Answer": "755 + 9706 = 10461"}
{"Question": "ADD + BACK = SCOPE", "Answer": "755 + 9708 = 10463"}
{"Question": "ART + DATE = ENTER", "Answer": "765 + 9751 = 10516"}
{"Question": "END + LESS = TASTE", "Answer": "762 + 9755 = 10517"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARE = UNDER", "Answer": "755 + 9783 = 10538"}
{"Question": "ERA + HEAD = ORDER", "Answer": "706 + 9764 = 10470"}
{"Question": "ODD + CORN = FENCE", "Answer": "766 + 9724 = 10490"}
{"Question": "EGG + NEWS = STATE", "Answer": "766 + 9741 = 10507"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEST = TASTE", "Answer": "766 + 9751 = 10517"}
{"Question": "ILL + AIDE = DEAD", "Answer": "788 + 2735 = 3523"}
{"Question": "ILL + VIEW = NERVE", "Answer": "788 + 9702 = 10490"}
{"Question": "ADD + SALE = FLESH", "Answer": "788 + 9704 = 10492"}
{"Question": "ADD + HALF = LEVEL", "Answer": "788 + 9713 = 10501"}
{"Question": "ADD + PALM = LIMIT", "Answer": "788 + 9715 = 10503"}
{"Question": "ILL + RICE = EAGER", "Answer": "788 + 9731 = 10519"}
{"Question": "ADD + EARN = NURSE", "Answer": "788 + 9751 = 10539"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAKE = GREEN", "Answer": "788 + 9765 = 10553"}
{"Question": "EGG + HEAD = GRADE", "Answer": "811 + 9867 = 10678"}
{"Question": "ADD + GAME = DREAM", "Answer": "811 + 9876 = 10687"}
{"Question": "ADD + BACK = CLIMB", "Answer": "822 + 9817 = 10639"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOWL = HELLO", "Answer": "822 + 9846 = 10668"}
{"Question": "ILL + DISH = BASIS", "Answer": "822 + 9864 = 10686"}
{"Question": "ADD + CAMP = PITCH", "Answer": "822 + 9871 = 10693"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEAN = STATE", "Answer": "833 + 9875 = 10708"}
{"Question": "AND + EARN = DEER", "Answer": "847 + 6814 = 7661"}
{"Question": "ALL + CARD = ORDER", "Answer": "844 + 9806 = 10650"}
{"Question": "ADD + FATE = ENTER", "Answer": "844 + 9871 = 10715"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEAT = DATA", "Answer": "855 + 3872 = 4727"}
{"Question": "ODD + BOAT = DATA", "Answer": "855 + 4872 = 5727"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARE = PROOF", "Answer": "855 + 9807 = 10662"}
{"Question": "LOW + ALSO = STEEL", "Answer": "853 + 9815 = 10668"}
{"Question": "ILL + BITE = TREAT", "Answer": "855 + 9816 = 10671"}
{"Question": "TIE + STEP = PHOTO", "Answer": "835 + 9851 = 10686"}
{"Question": "ADD + LACK = EQUAL", "Answer": "855 + 9834 = 10689"}
{"Question": "ADD + HANG = TIGHT", "Answer": "855 + 9836 = 10691"}
{"Question": "ADD + RAIL = EXTRA", "Answer": "855 + 9843 = 10698"}
{"Question": "ILL + FIRE = EAGER", "Answer": "855 + 9861 = 10716"}
{"Question": "EGG + TEAM = DRAMA", "Answer": "855 + 9872 = 10727"}
{"Question": "ERA + BEAN = IRAQI", "Answer": "806 + 9865 = 10671"}
{"Question": "ODD + BONE = INDEX", "Answer": "866 + 9807 = 10673"}
{"Question": "ADD + FATE = TODAY", "Answer": "866 + 9817 = 10683"}
{"Question": "ADD + EACH = ORDER", "Answer": "866 + 9824 = 10690"}
{"Question": "EGG + HEAD = TIGHT", "Answer": "866 + 9825 = 10691"}
{"Question": "ADD + EARN = HONOR", "Answer": "866 + 9837 = 10703"}
{"Question": "EGG + HEAD = DRAMA", "Answer": "866 + 9871 = 10737"}
{"Question": "ADD + GAIN = BEING", "Answer": "866 + 9873 = 10739"}
{"Question": "AID + FADE = IDEA", "Answer": "847 + 3871 = 4718"}
{"Question": "EGG + TERM = ORDER", "Answer": "877 + 9803 = 10680"}
{"Question": "ADD + CARE = BREAK", "Answer": "877 + 9806 = 10683"}
{"Question": "ADD + HANG = NIGHT", "Answer": "877 + 9816 = 10693"}
{"Question": "ALL + RAIN = COLOR", "Answer": "877 + 9832 = 10709"}
{"Question": "DUE + IDEA = AHEAD", "Answer": "847 + 9871 = 10718"}
{"Question": "ILL + BIKE = SALES", "Answer": "877 + 9864 = 10741"}
{"Question": "ILL + RIDE = DEER", "Answer": "944 + 2938 = 3882"}
{"Question": "EGG + BEAR = AREA", "Answer": "955 + 2938 = 3893"}
{"Question": "ALL + BELL = INNER", "Answer": "288 + 9788 = 10076"}
{"Question": "ALL + HELL = THAT", "Answer": "366 + 1766 = 2132"}
{"Question": "ALL + BELL = LOAD", "Answer": "366 + 5766 = 6132"}
{"Question": "FEE + KNEE = NEAR", "Answer": "655 + 7855 = 8510"}
{"Question": "ALL + BILL = MEDIA", "Answer": "688 + 9788 = 10476"}
{"Question": "FEE + AREA = ROOF", "Answer": "255 + 7857 = 8112"}
{"Question": "YET + TREE = FIFTY", "Answer": "349 + 9844 = 10193"}
{"Question": "LET + TREE = ROLL", "Answer": "367 + 7866 = 8233"}
{"Question": "EGG + HIGH = ASSET", "Answer": "577 + 9479 = 10056"}
{"Question": "EGG + HIGH = AWARE", "Answer": "677 + 9479 = 10156"}
{"Question": "SEE + AREA = STAR", "Answer": "522 + 4624 = 5146"}
{"Question": "FLY + YELL = SALES", "Answer": "729 + 9522 = 10251"}
{"Question": "EGG + HIGH = LABEL", "Answer": "522 + 9829 = 10351"}
{"Question": "EGG + HIGH = BASIS", "Answer": "533 + 9739 = 10272"}
{"Question": "SEE + AREA = FOCUS", "Answer": "566 + 9869 = 10435"}
{"Question": "SEE + AREA = YOURS", "Answer": "677 + 9579 = 10256"}
{"Question": "SEE + AREA = CHEST", "Answer": "733 + 9639 = 10372"}
{"Question": "FEE + AREA = FALL", "Answer": "755 + 6856 = 7611"}
{"Question": "FEE + ITEM = TOOTH", "Answer": "855 + 9157 = 10012"}
{"Question": "ADD + CODE = ASSET", "Answer": "177 + 9875 = 10052"}
{"Question": "ADD + BODY = APPLE", "Answer": "177 + 9876 = 10053"}
{"Question": "ALL + RELY = AREA", "Answer": "244 + 1948 = 2192"}
{"Question": "YES + FLEE = APPLY", "Answer": "284 + 9788 = 10072"}
{"Question": "ADD + HIDE = IDEA", "Answer": "311 + 7812 = 8123"}
{"Question": "TEN + FLEE = EVENT", "Answer": "312 + 9811 = 10123"}
{"Question": "FEE + WHEN = TOOTH", "Answer": "655 + 9358 = 10013"}
{"Question": "SEE + WHEN = NEWS", "Answer": "411 + 2713 = 3124"}
{"Question": "FEE + OVER = ROOF", "Answer": "411 + 2813 = 3224"}
{"Question": "CEO + KNEE = COOK", "Answer": "412 + 3811 = 4223"}
{"Question": "FEE + IDEA = DEAD", "Answer": "433 + 8936 = 9369"}
{"Question": "ADD + BODY = ERROR", "Answer": "477 + 9573 = 10050"}
{"Question": "ADD + RIDE = SOLAR", "Answer": "477 + 9872 = 10349"}
{"Question": "SEA + TREE = APART", "Answer": "481 + 9688 = 10169"}
{"Question": "ALL + SELF = ELSE", "Answer": "722 + 4523 = 5245"}
{"Question": "ILL + BELT = SALES", "Answer": "633 + 9738 = 10371"}
{"Question": "HER + FLEE = HERE", "Answer": "850 + 7655 = 8505"}
{"Question": "TOO + IRON = NEVER", "Answer": "755 + 9651 = 10406"}
{"Question": "ADD + RIDE = THEIR", "Answer": "744 + 9845 = 10589"}
{"Question": "TEA + FLEE = AGENT", "Answer": "761 + 9866 = 10627"}
{"Question": "ADD + CODE = VIDEO", "Answer": "766 + 9862 = 10628"}
{"Question": "FEE + NONE = OCCUR", "Answer": "833 + 9193 = 10026"}
{"Question": "SEE + NONE = SOON", "Answer": "944 + 8284 = 9228"}
{"Question": "ITS + TOSS = RADIO", "Answer": "394 + 9844 = 10238"}
{"Question": "SEE + NINE = TEST", "Answer": "522 + 3732 = 4254"}
{"Question": "FEE + NINE = PROOF", "Answer": "633 + 9593 = 10226"}
{"Question": "FEE + NINE = SHELF", "Answer": "844 + 9594 = 10438"}
{"Question": "SEE + NINE = SOON", "Answer": "577 + 4647 = 5224"}
{"Question": "THE + HALL = TOOTH", "Answer": "197 + 9822 = 10019"}
{"Question": "ILL + RARE = INNER", "Answer": "155 + 9894 = 10049"}
{"Question": "PIE + ITEM = ADAPT", "Answer": "293 + 9835 = 10128"}
{"Question": "LIE + IDEA = AHEAD", "Answer": "892 + 9321 = 10213"}
{"Question": "EGG + AWAY = BUYER", "Answer": "344 + 9892 = 10236"}
{"Question": "SEA + NINE = AGAIN", "Answer": "381 + 9798 = 10179"}
{"Question": "HER + NINE = HERE", "Answer": "830 + 7473 = 8303"}
{"Question": "LET + RARE = TOTAL", "Answer": "651 + 9495 = 10146"}
{"Question": "ADD + NINE = IDEA", "Answer": "544 + 7871 = 8415"}
{"Question": "EGG + ARAB = COVER", "Answer": "566 + 9892 = 10458"}
{"Question": "TOO + RARE = TEAR", "Answer": "622 + 5753 = 6375"}
{"Question": "TOO + EVEN = TONE", "Answer": "855 + 7672 = 8527"}
{"Question": "EGG + ARAB = FLOOR", "Answer": "655 + 9792 = 10447"}
{"Question": "ONE + FREE = ROOF", "Answer": "174 + 8944 = 9118"}
{"Question": "ADD + USED = APPLE", "Answer": "177 + 9847 = 10024"}
{"Question": "SEE + ONCE = SOON", "Answer": "244 + 1874 = 2118"}
{"Question": "FEE + CODE = FOOD", "Answer": "977 + 8247 = 9224"}
{"Question": "TOO + HERO = OFFER", "Answer": "711 + 9321 = 10032"}
{"Question": "ALL + FUEL = ESSAY", "Answer": "322 + 9712 = 10034"}
{"Question": "ODD + LEAD = BIBLE", "Answer": "344 + 9854 = 10198"}
{"Question": "ODD + USED = ERROR", "Answer": "755 + 9315 = 10070"}
{"Question": "FEE + LIKE = FALL", "Answer": "366 + 2756 = 3122"}
{"Question": "EGG + DRAG = INNER", "Answer": "388 + 9648 = 10036"}
{"Question": "FEE + TALE = LEFT", "Answer": "411 + 2731 = 3142"}
{"Question": "ADD + WORD = ERROR", "Answer": "455 + 9605 = 10060"}
{"Question": "ALL + SOIL = PRIOR", "Answer": "455 + 9825 = 10280"}
{"Question": "ODD + LEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "677 + 9417 = 10094"}
{"Question": "EGG + FLAG = CABLE", "Answer": "477 + 9807 = 10284"}
{"Question": "EGG + DRAG = ASIDE", "Answer": "477 + 9817 = 10294"}
{"Question": "EGG + DRAG = AFTER", "Answer": "544 + 9814 = 10358"}
{"Question": "BUS + LESS = TASTE", "Answer": "574 + 9844 = 10418"}
{"Question": "TOO + ALSO = USUAL", "Answer": "588 + 9608 = 10196"}
{"Question": "ILL + REAL = AREA", "Answer": "722 + 3642 = 4364"}
{"Question": "FEE + RISE = BASIS", "Answer": "822 + 9642 = 10464"}
{"Question": "FEE + SHOE = HELL", "Answer": "655 + 7845 = 8500"}
{"Question": "FEE + COPE = PRIOR", "Answer": "655 + 9715 = 10370"}
{"Question": "EGG + LONG = UNCLE", "Answer": "688 + 9708 = 10396"}
{"Question": "ILL + DEAL = GRADE", "Answer": "744 + 9854 = 10598"}
{"Question": "ILL + DEAL = STATE", "Answer": "744 + 9864 = 10608"}
{"Question": "ADD + BEND = ORDER", "Answer": "755 + 9825 = 10580"}
{"Question": "TOO + DEAD = APART", "Answer": "344 + 9819 = 10163"}
{"Question": "TOO + ELSE = ASSET", "Answer": "788 + 9309 = 10097"}
{"Question": "ILL + ONTO = AGAIN", "Answer": "388 + 9749 = 10137"}
{"Question": "ILL + TEST = SALES", "Answer": "822 + 9419 = 10241"}
{"Question": "LET + TYPE = APPLY", "Answer": "659 + 9405 = 10064"}
{"Question": "LEG + GATE = TOTAL", "Answer": "459 + 9715 = 10174"}
{"Question": "EGG + THAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "755 + 9439 = 10194"}
{"Question": "ILL + AREA = THEIR", "Answer": "855 + 9429 = 10284"}
{"Question": "OIL + LESS = BIBLE", "Answer": "409 + 9788 = 10197"}
{"Question": "ILL + AREA = THERE", "Answer": "544 + 9839 = 10383"}
{"Question": "EGG + THAT = PLATE", "Answer": "566 + 9729 = 10295"}
{"Question": "ILL + ONTO = TRAIN", "Answer": "866 + 9519 = 10385"}
{"Question": "TAP + POLL = ADAPT", "Answer": "619 + 9577 = 10196"}
{"Question": "EGG + BOMB = MAYBE", "Answer": "677 + 9819 = 10496"}
{"Question": "EGG + BOSS = SHOE", "Answer": "466 + 7588 = 8054"}
{"Question": "ADD + BITE = ASSET", "Answer": "155 + 9872 = 10027"}
{"Question": "EGG + COAL = APPLE", "Answer": "255 + 9817 = 10072"}
{"Question": "EGG + BUSY = ISSUE", "Answer": "277 + 9805 = 10082"}
{"Question": "EGG + LOAD = APPLE", "Answer": "277 + 9815 = 10092"}
{"Question": "EGG + SHOP = LOOSE", "Answer": "388 + 9705 = 10093"}
{"Question": "TOO + HALF = FIFTH", "Answer": "388 + 9751 = 10139"}
{"Question": "ADD + HERO = OFFER", "Answer": "477 + 9581 = 10058"}
{"Question": "LAW + NEWS = STATE", "Answer": "437 + 9871 = 10308"}
{"Question": "ADD + BELT = TOTAL", "Answer": "522 + 9631 = 10153"}
{"Question": "TOO + BASE = SHEET", "Answer": "522 + 9813 = 10335"}
{"Question": "ADD + STOP = PHOTO", "Answer": "822 + 9531 = 10353"}
{"Question": "ADD + OVER = NERVE", "Answer": "577 + 9803 = 10380"}
{"Question": "OFF + IDEA = AHEAD", "Answer": "577 + 9841 = 10418"}
{"Question": "ADD + KING = LEGAL", "Answer": "588 + 9763 = 10351"}
{"Question": "EGG + BOWL = ANGLE", "Answer": "644 + 9782 = 10426"}
{"Question": "TOO + WHEN = TONE", "Answer": "855 + 7694 = 8549"}
{"Question": "ADD + FORM = MEDIA", "Answer": "655 + 9871 = 10526"}
{"Question": "ILL + DATE = TREAT", "Answer": "766 + 9815 = 10581"}
{"Question": "SIR + STIR = RISE", "Answer": "213 + 2913 = 3126"}
{"Question": "FAT + FLAT = TELL", "Answer": "394 + 3894 = 4288"}
{"Question": "TIP + TRIP = ROOT", "Answer": "618 + 6718 = 7336"}
{"Question": "FAT + FLAT = HALF", "Answer": "643 + 6843 = 7486"}
{"Question": "MAN + MEAN = NAME", "Answer": "738 + 7638 = 8376"}
{"Question": "COP + CROP = ROLL", "Answer": "761 + 7861 = 8622"}
{"Question": "TEN + THEN = HERE", "Answer": "763 + 7863 = 8626"}
{"Question": "BAR + BEAR = AREA", "Answer": "784 + 7684 = 8468"}
{"Question": "TEN + THEN = HATE", "Answer": "842 + 8942 = 9784"}
{"Question": "AID + ACID = BILL", "Answer": "861 + 8761 = 9622"}
{"Question": "TEN + THEN = SENSE", "Answer": "905 + 9605 = 10510"}
{"Question": "BAN + BEAN = ALONE", "Answer": "912 + 9412 = 10324"}
{"Question": "SAY + STAY = ADAPT", "Answer": "916 + 9216 = 10132"}
{"Question": "COP + CROP = PHOTO", "Answer": "921 + 9321 = 10242"}
{"Question": "AID + ACID = GUIDE", "Answer": "924 + 9324 = 10248"}
{"Question": "BAN + BEAN = PHONE", "Answer": "924 + 9824 = 10748"}
{"Question": "BAR + BEAR = START", "Answer": "925 + 9325 = 10250"}
{"Question": "CAT + COAT = HELLO", "Answer": "928 + 9628 = 10556"}
{"Question": "FAT + FLAT = TROOP", "Answer": "931 + 9731 = 10662"}
{"Question": "BAN + BEAN = CHASE", "Answer": "932 + 9432 = 10364"}
{"Question": "BAN + BEAN = ERROR", "Answer": "935 + 9135 = 10070"}
{"Question": "CAT + COAT = LEAVE", "Answer": "935 + 9435 = 10370"}
{"Question": "PAN + PLAN = FENCE", "Answer": "935 + 9635 = 10570"}
{"Question": "AID + ACID = FENCE", "Answer": "935 + 9735 = 10670"}
{"Question": "SIR + STIR = ADAPT", "Answer": "936 + 9236 = 10172"}
{"Question": "COP + CROP = ADAPT", "Answer": "937 + 9237 = 10174"}
{"Question": "BAN + BEAN = PLANE", "Answer": "937 + 9437 = 10374"}
{"Question": "FAT + FLAT = PHOTO", "Answer": "937 + 9537 = 10474"}
{"Question": "CAT + COAT = THEME", "Answer": "941 + 9341 = 10282"}
{"Question": "TEN + THEN = FIFTH", "Answer": "946 + 9246 = 10192"}
{"Question": "AID + ACID = TODAY", "Answer": "946 + 9746 = 10692"}
{"Question": "MAN + MEAN = DRAMA", "Answer": "947 + 9547 = 10494"}
{"Question": "COP + CROP = ELECT", "Answer": "948 + 9248 = 10196"}
{"Question": "BAN + BEAN = TRIBE", "Answer": "948 + 9648 = 10596"}
{"Question": "TIE + TRIP = PEER", "Answer": "462 + 4765 = 5227"}
{"Question": "GAS + GEAR = EASE", "Answer": "512 + 5614 = 6126"}
{"Question": "DAY + DEAR = YARD", "Answer": "647 + 6849 = 7496"}
{"Question": "DAY + DRAG = YARD", "Answer": "728 + 7529 = 8257"}
{"Question": "TIE + TAIL = ASSET", "Answer": "924 + 9125 = 10049"}
{"Question": "TEA + THEM = GREAT", "Answer": "924 + 9325 = 10249"}
{"Question": "CEO + CREW = SHORE", "Answer": "924 + 9528 = 10452"}
{"Question": "HAT + HEAR = BIRTH", "Answer": "924 + 9625 = 10549"}
{"Question": "FIT + FAIR = ELITE", "Answer": "925 + 9326 = 10251"}
{"Question": "BAD + BEAN = GRADE", "Answer": "925 + 9328 = 10253"}
{"Question": "BAR + BOAT = EXTRA", "Answer": "925 + 9827 = 10752"}
{"Question": "PIE + PAIN = EVENT", "Answer": "931 + 9236 = 10167"}
{"Question": "TEA + THEM = ADAPT", "Answer": "931 + 9238 = 10169"}
{"Question": "ITS + INTO = SHEET", "Answer": "931 + 9732 = 10663"}
{"Question": "SEX + STEP = ADAPT", "Answer": "935 + 9237 = 10172"}
{"Question": "BAN + BEAT = MONTH", "Answer": "935 + 9637 = 10572"}
{"Question": "BAD + BOAT = MEDIA", "Answer": "935 + 9638 = 10573"}
{"Question": "FEW + FUEL = BIBLE", "Answer": "936 + 9237 = 10173"}
{"Question": "CUP + CLUB = ADAPT", "Answer": "937 + 9238 = 10175"}
{"Question": "DNA + DENY = AGAIN", "Answer": "941 + 9243 = 10184"}
{"Question": "TIE + THIN = EVENT", "Answer": "941 + 9248 = 10189"}
{"Question": "TAP + THAN = PLANT", "Answer": "941 + 9548 = 10489"}
{"Question": "CEO + CHEF = KNOCK", "Answer": "946 + 9745 = 10691"}
{"Question": "SEA + STEP = CHASE", "Answer": "946 + 9748 = 10694"}
{"Question": "HIP + HELP = PIPE", "Answer": "738 + 7648 = 8386"}
{"Question": "BIT + BEST = SITE", "Answer": "832 + 8492 = 9324"}
{"Question": "SHE + SURE = USER", "Answer": "873 + 8963 = 9836"}
{"Question": "SIT + SHOT = FIFTH", "Answer": "906 + 9256 = 10162"}
{"Question": "TIE + TYPE = FIFTY", "Answer": "906 + 9286 = 10192"}
{"Question": "CAN + CORN = DANCE", "Answer": "906 + 9786 = 10692"}
{"Question": "TIE + TAKE = FIFTH", "Answer": "907 + 9287 = 10194"}
{"Question": "BAD + BEND = MAYBE", "Answer": "907 + 9487 = 10394"}
{"Question": "AND + ACID = INDEX", "Answer": "907 + 9817 = 10724"}
{"Question": "DUE + DARE = GUESS", "Answer": "907 + 9837 = 10744"}
{"Question": "RED + ROAD = AWARE", "Answer": "984 + 9214 = 10198"}
{"Question": "SHE + SAFE = FLESH", "Answer": "984 + 9514 = 10498"}
{"Question": "GOD + GLAD = ORDER", "Answer": "915 + 9625 = 10540"}
{"Question": "SIR + STAR = APART", "Answer": "946 + 9216 = 10162"}
{"Question": "SIT + SHOT = IRISH", "Answer": "916 + 9276 = 10192"}
{"Question": "TEN + TURN = EARTH", "Answer": "916 + 9876 = 10792"}
{"Question": "MAD + MIND = DRAMA", "Answer": "921 + 9371 = 10292"}
{"Question": "SET + SPOT = THOSE", "Answer": "921 + 9871 = 10792"}
{"Question": "ANY + ARMY = LEMON", "Answer": "926 + 9546 = 10472"}
{"Question": "OWN + OPEN = SCENE", "Answer": "927 + 9547 = 10474"}
{"Question": "BIT + BEAT = PLATE", "Answer": "928 + 9658 = 10586"}
{"Question": "COW + CREW = PIECE", "Answer": "928 + 9768 = 10696"}
{"Question": "CRY + CITY = ADAPT", "Answer": "937 + 9247 = 10184"}
{"Question": "SHE + SAKE = FLESH", "Answer": "942 + 9352 = 10294"}
{"Question": "CAN + CHIP = DANCE", "Answer": "905 + 9687 = 10592"}
{"Question": "AGE + AUTO = TREAT", "Answer": "973 + 9418 = 10391"}
{"Question": "AND + ABLE = GREEN", "Answer": "925 + 9847 = 10772"}
{"Question": "VIA + VOTE = ADAPT", "Answer": "931 + 9254 = 10185"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = BELL", "Answer": "561 + 6561 = 7122"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = ELECT", "Answer": "591 + 9591 = 10182"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = INTO", "Answer": "628 + 2628 = 3256"}
{"Question": "WAY + AWAY = GENE", "Answer": "641 + 4641 = 5282"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = HERO", "Answer": "673 + 7673 = 8346"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = PIANO", "Answer": "698 + 9698 = 10396"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = BEER", "Answer": "724 + 2724 = 3448"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = KNEE", "Answer": "750 + 5750 = 6500"}
{"Question": "WAY + AWAY = WELL", "Answer": "761 + 6761 = 7522"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = DEAD", "Answer": "816 + 1816 = 2632"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = FLEE", "Answer": "850 + 5850 = 6700"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = ONCE", "Answer": "870 + 7870 = 8740"}
{"Question": "WAY + AWAY = WALL", "Answer": "872 + 7872 = 8744"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = ONTO", "Answer": "879 + 7879 = 8758"}
{"Question": "ONE + NONE = AGENT", "Answer": "897 + 9897 = 10794"}
{"Question": "WAR + AWAY = YARD", "Answer": "624 + 2623 = 3247"}
{"Question": "RAW + ARAB = FIBER", "Answer": "792 + 9795 = 10587"}
{"Question": "ARM + RARE = THEIR", "Answer": "794 + 9795 = 10589"}
{"Question": "RAW + ARAB = WHERE", "Answer": "891 + 9896 = 10787"}
{"Question": "ARM + RARE = CLEAR", "Answer": "892 + 9897 = 10789"}
{"Question": "ARM + RARE = DEAD", "Answer": "947 + 4948 = 5895"}
{"Question": "ART + RARE = DATA", "Answer": "974 + 7975 = 8949"}
{"Question": "ACT + CAST = TOTAL", "Answer": "591 + 9561 = 10152"}
{"Question": "NUT + UNIT = TEEN", "Answer": "678 + 7658 = 8336"}
{"Question": "OLD + LOAD = DATA", "Answer": "712 + 1742 = 2454"}
{"Question": "USE + SURE = AREA", "Answer": "716 + 1746 = 2462"}
{"Question": "ICE + CITE = ITEM", "Answer": "761 + 6751 = 7512"}
{"Question": "ONE + NOSE = SEND", "Answer": "785 + 8795 = 9580"}
{"Question": "AGE + GATE = FLOAT", "Answer": "794 + 9784 = 10578"}
{"Question": "ONE + NOTE = TEEN", "Answer": "826 + 2836 = 3662"}
{"Question": "RUB + ARAB = BABY", "Answer": "807 + 6867 = 7674"}
{"Question": "USE + SURE = USER", "Answer": "873 + 7863 = 8736"}
{"Question": "AGE + GAME = AREA", "Answer": "879 + 7819 = 8698"}
{"Question": "RUB + ARAB = ENTER", "Answer": "824 + 9894 = 10718"}
{"Question": "ONE + NOSE = VIDEO", "Answer": "894 + 9854 = 10748"}
{"Question": "OLD + LOAD = PIANO", "Answer": "894 + 9874 = 10768"}
{"Question": "ICE + NINE = CHECK", "Answer": "817 + 9897 = 10714"}
{"Question": "ONE + NOSE = DRESS", "Answer": "897 + 9847 = 10744"}
{"Question": "NUT + UNIT = TINY", "Answer": "912 + 1982 = 2894"}
{"Question": "NUT + UNIT = DATA", "Answer": "914 + 1934 = 2848"}
{"Question": "AGE + GAME = MESS", "Answer": "928 + 2938 = 3866"}
{"Question": "AGE + GAME = TEAM", "Answer": "928 + 2968 = 3896"}
{"Question": "AGE + GAME = MEET", "Answer": "938 + 3948 = 4886"}
{"Question": "NUT + UNIT = ONTO", "Answer": "953 + 5983 = 6936"}
{"Question": "AGE + GAME = DEAD", "Answer": "958 + 5938 = 6896"}
{"Question": "ERA + REST = STAR", "Answer": "587 + 8591 = 9178"}
{"Question": "RUB + URGE = PAPER", "Answer": "592 + 9543 = 10135"}
{"Question": "GUN + UGLY = LUNG", "Answer": "625 + 2631 = 3256"}
{"Question": "END + NEAR = EARN", "Answer": "657 + 5628 = 6285"}
{"Question": "LAW + ALSO = WHEEL", "Answer": "691 + 9645 = 10336"}
{"Question": "AND + NAME = DRESS", "Answer": "691 + 9653 = 10344"}
{"Question": "END + NEAR = DOZEN", "Answer": "691 + 9678 = 10369"}
{"Question": "ACT + CAKE = FIELD", "Answer": "692 + 9683 = 10375"}
{"Question": "AGE + GAIN = DRESS", "Answer": "693 + 9684 = 10377"}
{"Question": "ACT + CARE = TEAR", "Answer": "712 + 1764 = 2476"}
{"Question": "END + NEAR = AREA", "Answer": "784 + 8795 = 9579"}
{"Question": "ETC + TEAR = FORCE", "Answer": "792 + 9735 = 10527"}
{"Question": "ACT + CARD = MEDIA", "Answer": "792 + 9745 = 10537"}
{"Question": "NOD + ONCE = GREEN", "Answer": "792 + 9765 = 10557"}
{"Question": "END + NEAR = THREE", "Answer": "792 + 9785 = 10577"}
{"Question": "ART + RAIL = ENTER", "Answer": "795 + 9724 = 10519"}
{"Question": "AND + NAME = GREEN", "Answer": "794 + 9765 = 10559"}
{"Question": "AND + NAME = CLEAN", "Answer": "794 + 9785 = 10579"}
{"Question": "ITS + PIPE = STEP", "Answer": "863 + 2829 = 3692"}
{"Question": "CAT + ACID = DATA", "Answer": "869 + 6827 = 7696"}
{"Question": "ITS + TIME = CHEST", "Answer": "892 + 9837 = 10729"}
{"Question": "ITS + TIME = MEET", "Answer": "935 + 3948 = 4883"}
{"Question": "PAY + AWAY = PIPE", "Answer": "213 + 1813 = 2026"}
{"Question": "LAB + ARAB = EVERY", "Answer": "293 + 9893 = 10186"}
{"Question": "TEN + EVEN = TENT", "Answer": "437 + 3937 = 4374"}
{"Question": "DAY + AWAY = WOOD", "Answer": "457 + 5657 = 6114"}
{"Question": "LAB + ARAB = INNER", "Answer": "592 + 9492 = 10084"}
{"Question": "HER + EVER = BIRTH", "Answer": "492 + 9792 = 10284"}
{"Question": "DAY + AWAY = YARD", "Answer": "834 + 3534 = 4368"}
{"Question": "MAY + AWAY = MALL", "Answer": "761 + 6861 = 7622"}
{"Question": "EAT + ARAB = BEER", "Answer": "471 + 7978 = 8449"}
{"Question": "DAY + ARAB = BAND", "Answer": "531 + 3834 = 4365"}
{"Question": "DRY + RARE = DEAR", "Answer": "541 + 4843 = 5384"}
{"Question": "DRY + RARE = DEER", "Answer": "873 + 7574 = 8447"}
{"Question": "TEN + EARN = TOOTH", "Answer": "193 + 9823 = 10016"}
{"Question": "HIM + ITEM = TOOTH", "Answer": "894 + 9124 = 10018"}
{"Question": "THE + HAVE = ASSET", "Answer": "894 + 9154 = 10048"}
{"Question": "DUE + URGE = DEER", "Answer": "871 + 7241 = 8112"}
{"Question": "TIE + NONE = INTO", "Answer": "324 + 1814 = 2138"}
{"Question": "ICE + CARE = AREA", "Answer": "379 + 7819 = 8198"}
{"Question": "FUN + UPON = ADAPT", "Answer": "392 + 9782 = 10174"}
{"Question": "LET + EAST = TELL", "Answer": "412 + 1732 = 2144"}
{"Question": "WIN + EVEN = WINE", "Answer": "718 + 6468 = 7186"}
{"Question": "ONE + NAME = MOON", "Answer": "468 + 6978 = 7446"}
{"Question": "THE + HIRE = TREE", "Answer": "870 + 7430 = 8300"}
{"Question": "SHE + HIDE = SEED", "Answer": "873 + 7463 = 8336"}
{"Question": "THE + HIDE = ASSET", "Answer": "492 + 9532 = 10024"}
{"Question": "TRY + RELY = ASSET", "Answer": "492 + 9562 = 10054"}
{"Question": "DUE + URGE = SPEED", "Answer": "492 + 9732 = 10224"}
{"Question": "SHE + HATE = DRESS", "Answer": "492 + 9752 = 10244"}
{"Question": "LAY + ARMY = MALL", "Answer": "839 + 3549 = 4388"}
{"Question": "SHE + HATE = SEAT", "Answer": "541 + 4621 = 5162"}
{"Question": "DUE + URGE = AHEAD", "Answer": "894 + 9524 = 10418"}
{"Question": "DAY + ARMY = BLOOD", "Answer": "693 + 9753 = 10446"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = TALL", "Answer": "372 + 2372 = 2744"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = ALLOW", "Answer": "519 + 9519 = 10038"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = INNER", "Answer": "539 + 9539 = 10078"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = BIBLE", "Answer": "569 + 9569 = 10138"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = HELL", "Answer": "594 + 4594 = 5188"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = BEER", "Answer": "614 + 4614 = 5228"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = HATE", "Answer": "625 + 5625 = 6250"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = CASH", "Answer": "628 + 8628 = 9256"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = BLACK", "Answer": "629 + 9629 = 10258"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = DIRTY", "Answer": "649 + 9649 = 10298"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = CLOCK", "Answer": "659 + 9659 = 10318"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = MEDIA", "Answer": "689 + 9689 = 10378"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = PLATE", "Answer": "749 + 9749 = 10498"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = CRACK", "Answer": "759 + 9759 = 10518"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = BOTH", "Answer": "824 + 4824 = 5648"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = BIRTH", "Answer": "849 + 9849 = 10698"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = COUCH", "Answer": "859 + 9859 = 10718"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = BALL", "Answer": "872 + 2872 = 3744"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = MATH", "Answer": "874 + 4874 = 5748"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAT = BEACH", "Answer": "879 + 9879 = 10758"}
{"Question": "RED + AREA = DEER", "Answer": "503 + 2502 = 3005"}
{"Question": "HOW + WHOM = TOOTH", "Answer": "509 + 9506 = 10015"}
{"Question": "AIR + RAIN = INNER", "Answer": "519 + 9510 = 10029"}
{"Question": "EAR + REAL = APPLY", "Answer": "519 + 9513 = 10032"}
{"Question": "EAR + READ = APPLE", "Answer": "519 + 9516 = 10035"}
{"Question": "EAR + READ = AIDE", "Answer": "521 + 1524 = 2045"}
{"Question": "END + DENY = EVEN", "Answer": "524 + 4528 = 5052"}
{"Question": "ITS + SITE = ERROR", "Answer": "539 + 9531 = 10070"}
{"Question": "ARM + MARK = INNER", "Answer": "539 + 9534 = 10073"}
{"Question": "EAR + READ = ISSUE", "Answer": "539 + 9536 = 10075"}
{"Question": "HIT + THIS = LOOSE", "Answer": "539 + 9537 = 10076"}
{"Question": "ITS + SITE = ADAPT", "Answer": "569 + 9567 = 10136"}
{"Question": "END + DENY = AWARE", "Answer": "589 + 9586 = 10175"}
{"Question": "RED + AREA = FADE", "Answer": "598 + 1591 = 2189"}
{"Question": "ITS + SITE = TEST", "Answer": "598 + 8591 = 9189"}
{"Question": "END + DENY = NINE", "Answer": "598 + 8597 = 9195"}
{"Question": "AIM + MAIL = ALLY", "Answer": "615 + 5612 = 6227"}
{"Question": "ITS + SITE = TREAT", "Answer": "619 + 9612 = 10231"}
{"Question": "AIM + MAIN = NINE", "Answer": "623 + 3624 = 4247"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEAM = MALL", "Answer": "627 + 7628 = 8255"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAN = DRAMA", "Answer": "629 + 9623 = 10252"}
{"Question": "EAR + READ = BLAME", "Answer": "629 + 9627 = 10256"}
{"Question": "EAR + READ = AREA", "Answer": "632 + 2631 = 3263"}
{"Question": "ICE + KICK = TREAT", "Answer": "632 + 9639 = 10271"}
{"Question": "AIR + RAIL = EXTRA", "Answer": "649 + 9647 = 10296"}
{"Question": "HIS + SHIP = CATCH", "Answer": "659 + 9657 = 10316"}
{"Question": "HIT + THIN = INTO", "Answer": "687 + 7683 = 8370"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEAD = AIDE", "Answer": "689 + 7687 = 8376"}
{"Question": "EAR + REAL = ALLY", "Answer": "721 + 1724 = 2445"}
{"Question": "END + DENY = AGREE", "Answer": "739 + 9738 = 10477"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEAR = RARE", "Answer": "748 + 8749 = 9497"}
{"Question": "HIT + THIN = ELITE", "Answer": "749 + 9742 = 10491"}
{"Question": "EAR + READ = SHARE", "Answer": "749 + 9748 = 10497"}
{"Question": "EAR + READ = DATA", "Answer": "752 + 2753 = 3505"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAN = COACH", "Answer": "759 + 9758 = 10517"}
{"Question": "END + TENT = DATA", "Answer": "763 + 2762 = 3525"}
{"Question": "RED + AREA = EASE", "Answer": "761 + 5765 = 6526"}
{"Question": "ASK + EASE = SELL", "Answer": "768 + 5765 = 6533"}
{"Question": "AIM + MAIL = DELAY", "Answer": "789 + 9785 = 10574"}
{"Question": "HIS + SHIP = IMPLY", "Answer": "819 + 9816 = 10635"}
{"Question": "OUT + TOUR = AGREE", "Answer": "829 + 9826 = 10655"}
{"Question": "EAR + READ = FREE", "Answer": "846 + 6842 = 7688"}
{"Question": "HAT + THAN = ELITE", "Answer": "849 + 9842 = 10691"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEAR = BIRTH", "Answer": "849 + 9846 = 10695"}
{"Question": "END + DENY = ASIAN", "Answer": "859 + 9856 = 10715"}
{"Question": "ITS + SITE = AGENT", "Answer": "869 + 9867 = 10736"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEAM = RARE", "Answer": "873 + 3875 = 4748"}
{"Question": "AIM + MAIN = ELITE", "Answer": "879 + 9872 = 10751"}
{"Question": "AIM + MAIN = SKILL", "Answer": "879 + 9876 = 10755"}
{"Question": "ARM + MARK = BEER", "Answer": "941 + 1943 = 2884"}
{"Question": "ASK + EASE = SAKE", "Answer": "950 + 4954 = 5904"}
{"Question": "END + DEAD = INNER", "Answer": "509 + 9549 = 10058"}
{"Question": "END + DEAD = ASSET", "Answer": "539 + 9519 = 10058"}
{"Question": "DIE + EDGE = INNER", "Answer": "519 + 9579 = 10098"}
{"Question": "END + DEAD = EARN", "Answer": "605 + 5625 = 6230"}
{"Question": "AGE + EASE = GIVEN", "Answer": "619 + 9679 = 10298"}
{"Question": "DIE + EDGE = ASIAN", "Answer": "639 + 9679 = 10318"}
{"Question": "EAT + TENT = DOZEN", "Answer": "679 + 9689 = 10368"}
{"Question": "END + DEAD = ANGRY", "Answer": "709 + 9719 = 10428"}
{"Question": "DUE + EDGE = FULLY", "Answer": "709 + 9739 = 10448"}
{"Question": "AGE + EASE = SHOOT", "Answer": "729 + 9719 = 10448"}
{"Question": "AGE + EASE = SKILL", "Answer": "769 + 9719 = 10488"}
{"Question": "AGE + EASE = VISIT", "Answer": "749 + 9759 = 10508"}
{"Question": "AGE + EASE = SEED", "Answer": "785 + 5765 = 6550"}
{"Question": "END + DEAD = ANGLE", "Answer": "809 + 9819 = 10628"}
{"Question": "EAT + TENT = DANCE", "Answer": "809 + 9869 = 10678"}
{"Question": "DIE + EDGE = GOOD", "Answer": "814 + 4854 = 5668"}
{"Question": "LIE + ELSE = SKILL", "Answer": "869 + 9819 = 10688"}
{"Question": "END + DEAD = ASIDE", "Answer": "879 + 9819 = 10698"}
{"Question": "END + DEAD = IDEA", "Answer": "856 + 6826 = 7682"}
{"Question": "END + DEAD = BLADE", "Answer": "829 + 9869 = 10698"}
{"Question": "END + DEAD = STATE", "Answer": "829 + 9879 = 10708"}
{"Question": "HIT + THAT = COACH", "Answer": "839 + 9879 = 10718"}
{"Question": "LIE + ELSE = LESS", "Answer": "897 + 7847 = 8744"}
{"Question": "END + DEAD = NAME", "Answer": "854 + 4874 = 5728"}
{"Question": "DUE + EDGE = USED", "Answer": "854 + 4894 = 5748"}
{"Question": "AGE + EASE = GANG", "Answer": "921 + 1981 = 2902"}
{"Question": "NEW + ONTO = TEEN", "Answer": "517 + 8598 = 9115"}
{"Question": "EAR + REST = APPLE", "Answer": "519 + 9526 = 10045"}
{"Question": "LEG + GLAD = APPLE", "Answer": "539 + 9514 = 10053"}
{"Question": "LAP + ELSE = APPLE", "Answer": "510 + 9549 = 10059"}
{"Question": "END + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "549 + 9516 = 10065"}
{"Question": "RED + DROP = AWARE", "Answer": "569 + 9587 = 10156"}
{"Question": "ARM + MAKE = TREAT", "Answer": "609 + 9652 = 10261"}
{"Question": "EAT + TEND = WASTE", "Answer": "609 + 9687 = 10296"}
{"Question": "AID + DARE = IDEA", "Answer": "632 + 2614 = 3246"}
{"Question": "AIM + MASK = STILL", "Answer": "629 + 9615 = 10244"}
{"Question": "AID + DATE = TREAT", "Answer": "649 + 9612 = 10261"}
{"Question": "ITS + SICK = THESE", "Answer": "619 + 9673 = 10292"}
{"Question": "ITS + SICK = CHEST", "Answer": "679 + 9618 = 10297"}
{"Question": "END + DESK = STATE", "Answer": "689 + 9617 = 10306"}
{"Question": "ARM + MAKE = AREA", "Answer": "635 + 5681 = 6316"}
{"Question": "RED + DRAG = EDGE", "Answer": "643 + 3671 = 4314"}
{"Question": "EAR + REST = SAUCE", "Answer": "709 + 9718 = 10427"}
{"Question": "ACT + TALK = ELITE", "Answer": "789 + 9702 = 10491"}
{"Question": "HAT + THIS = WASTE", "Answer": "709 + 9784 = 10493"}
{"Question": "HIT + THAN = IRAQI", "Answer": "719 + 9742 = 10461"}
{"Question": "ACT + TALK = LEGAL", "Answer": "759 + 9712 = 10471"}
{"Question": "ACT + TAKE = CHEAP", "Answer": "719 + 9754 = 10473"}
{"Question": "AND + DARE = NEAR", "Answer": "721 + 1754 = 2475"}
{"Question": "EAR + RELY = AREA", "Answer": "754 + 4721 = 5475"}
{"Question": "RED + DRAG = THERE", "Answer": "749 + 9725 = 10474"}
{"Question": "END + DEAL = STATE", "Answer": "749 + 9758 = 10507"}
{"Question": "END + DEAR = RARE", "Answer": "793 + 3754 = 4547"}
{"Question": "ART + TASK = STAR", "Answer": "806 + 6874 = 7680"}
{"Question": "ACT + TAPE = PRESS", "Answer": "839 + 9816 = 10655"}
{"Question": "ACT + TALE = LOCAL", "Answer": "869 + 9812 = 10681"}
{"Question": "ITS + SICK = TRUST", "Answer": "819 + 9872 = 10691"}
{"Question": "OIL + LOSE = SHELF", "Answer": "879 + 9816 = 10695"}
{"Question": "ACT + TAKE = BREAK", "Answer": "829 + 9856 = 10685"}
{"Question": "LEG + GLAD = IMAGE", "Answer": "829 + 9863 = 10692"}
{"Question": "ARM + MALE = COLOR", "Answer": "829 + 9873 = 10702"}
{"Question": "HOT + THIN = INTO", "Answer": "892 + 2837 = 3729"}
{"Question": "AGE + EDGE = GOOD", "Answer": "154 + 4854 = 5008"}
{"Question": "BAD + DEAD = APPLE", "Answer": "219 + 9819 = 10038"}
{"Question": "SEA + AREA = OCCUR", "Answer": "239 + 9839 = 10078"}
{"Question": "SAD + DEAD = ELSE", "Answer": "841 + 1241 = 2082"}
{"Question": "SEA + AREA = LOOSE", "Answer": "789 + 9289 = 10078"}
{"Question": "AGE + EDGE = DEAD", "Answer": "891 + 1291 = 2182"}
{"Question": "SEA + AREA = SEED", "Answer": "302 + 2702 = 3004"}
{"Question": "BAD + DEAD = ASSET", "Answer": "719 + 9319 = 10038"}
{"Question": "CAT + THAT = FIFTH", "Answer": "349 + 9849 = 10198"}
{"Question": "TEA + AREA = TALL", "Answer": "372 + 2872 = 3244"}
{"Question": "SEA + AREA = EASE", "Answer": "421 + 1721 = 2142"}
{"Question": "AGE + EDGE = GLAD", "Answer": "632 + 2432 = 3064"}
{"Question": "BAD + DEAD = INNER", "Answer": "479 + 9579 = 10058"}
{"Question": "SEA + AREA = EARN", "Answer": "543 + 3843 = 4386"}
{"Question": "AGE + EDGE = HEAD", "Answer": "634 + 4834 = 5468"}
{"Question": "MAD + DEAD = GAME", "Answer": "738 + 8638 = 9376"}
{"Question": "SEA + AREA = CLEAR", "Answer": "649 + 9849 = 10498"}
{"Question": "EAT + THAT = COACH", "Answer": "659 + 9859 = 10518"}
{"Question": "SEA + AREA = BASE", "Answer": "684 + 4784 = 5468"}
{"Question": "TEA + AREA = RATE", "Answer": "947 + 7847 = 8794"}
{"Question": "LET + THEM = LOOSE", "Answer": "169 + 9867 = 10036"}
{"Question": "RUB + BLUE = UPPER", "Answer": "219 + 9813 = 10032"}
{"Question": "RAW + WEAK = INNER", "Answer": "289 + 9783 = 10072"}
{"Question": "LAB + BEAN = APPLE", "Answer": "319 + 9718 = 10037"}
{"Question": "ASK + ELSE = SELL", "Answer": "723 + 1421 = 2144"}
{"Question": "DAY + YEAR = BOARD", "Answer": "429 + 9825 = 10254"}
{"Question": "ART + TERM = INNER", "Answer": "479 + 9578 = 10057"}
{"Question": "ITS + ONTO = SOON", "Answer": "713 + 2512 = 3225"}
{"Question": "BAD + DEAR = RARE", "Answer": "523 + 3724 = 4247"}
{"Question": "CEO + AREA = CORE", "Answer": "924 + 8528 = 9452"}
{"Question": "RED + DIET = AWARE", "Answer": "529 + 9623 = 10152"}
{"Question": "CAN + NEAR = PLACE", "Answer": "529 + 9728 = 10257"}
{"Question": "ARM + MORE = CLEAR", "Answer": "529 + 9823 = 10352"}
{"Question": "OWN + NEWS = SNOW", "Answer": "631 + 1532 = 2163"}
{"Question": "BIG + GAIN = CLIMB", "Answer": "539 + 9836 = 10375"}
{"Question": "BAR + READ = AREA", "Answer": "543 + 3841 = 4384"}
{"Question": "BET + THEM = FIFTH", "Answer": "549 + 9647 = 10196"}
{"Question": "SET + AREA = STAR", "Answer": "572 + 4674 = 5246"}
{"Question": "FAN + NEAR = FREE", "Answer": "584 + 4682 = 5266"}
{"Question": "HIS + STIR = ELITE", "Answer": "639 + 9732 = 10371"}
{"Question": "EAR + ROAD = SHARE", "Answer": "649 + 9847 = 10496"}
{"Question": "BAN + NEAR = EARN", "Answer": "657 + 7850 = 8507"}
{"Question": "HAT + TEAM = COACH", "Answer": "659 + 9857 = 10516"}
{"Question": "YES + AREA = BABY", "Answer": "732 + 5835 = 6567"}
{"Question": "TOE + EASE = TOSS", "Answer": "302 + 2742 = 3044"}
{"Question": "DUE + ELSE = USUAL", "Answer": "319 + 9809 = 10128"}
{"Question": "AGE + ELSE = USUAL", "Answer": "329 + 9809 = 10138"}
{"Question": "THE + EASE = SHOOT", "Answer": "809 + 9419 = 10228"}
{"Question": "LAB + BOMB = MALL", "Answer": "412 + 2732 = 3144"}
{"Question": "DIE + EASE = SEED", "Answer": "492 + 2732 = 3224"}
{"Question": "TAP + PICK = ADAPT", "Answer": "319 + 9874 = 10193"}
{"Question": "DIE + EACH = TIRED", "Answer": "509 + 9786 = 10295"}
{"Question": "ARM + MENU = THREE", "Answer": "529 + 9748 = 10277"}
{"Question": "DNA + ALSO = SPEED", "Answer": "629 + 9817 = 10446"}
{"Question": "OWN + DOWN = ALLOW", "Answer": "526 + 9526 = 10052"}
{"Question": "ARM + FARM = INNER", "Answer": "542 + 9542 = 10084"}
{"Question": "WIN + TWIN = INTO", "Answer": "591 + 8591 = 9182"}
{"Question": "HOT + SHOT = COACH", "Answer": "608 + 9608 = 10216"}
{"Question": "AGE + PAGE = GREEN", "Answer": "612 + 9612 = 10224"}
{"Question": "ACT + FACT = CHEEK", "Answer": "614 + 9614 = 10228"}
{"Question": "ARM + FARM = AREA", "Answer": "623 + 5623 = 6246"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEAR = CARD", "Answer": "624 + 8624 = 9248"}
{"Question": "AIR + FAIR = SHIRT", "Answer": "624 + 9624 = 10248"}
{"Question": "EAR + YEAR = BABY", "Answer": "627 + 4627 = 5254"}
{"Question": "EAT + SEAT = EASE", "Answer": "628 + 5628 = 6256"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEAR = RACE", "Answer": "628 + 7628 = 8256"}
{"Question": "RAW + DRAW = WHERE", "Answer": "631 + 9631 = 10262"}
{"Question": "ACT + FACT = METAL", "Answer": "632 + 9632 = 10264"}
{"Question": "ASK + TASK = STAR", "Answer": "634 + 2634 = 3268"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEAR = ABLE", "Answer": "638 + 2638 = 3276"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEAR = RIDE", "Answer": "638 + 7638 = 8276"}
{"Question": "END + BEND = DRAMA", "Answer": "641 + 9641 = 10282"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEAR = GUIDE", "Answer": "648 + 9648 = 10296"}
{"Question": "ICE + RICE = FREE", "Answer": "650 + 3650 = 4300"}
{"Question": "RAW + DRAW = FEWER", "Answer": "653 + 9653 = 10306"}
{"Question": "NOW + KNOW = ASIAN", "Answer": "658 + 9658 = 10316"}
{"Question": "EAR + GEAR = URGE", "Answer": "673 + 4673 = 5346"}
{"Question": "ACT + FACT = EXTRA", "Answer": "673 + 9673 = 10346"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEAR = THREE", "Answer": "683 + 9683 = 10366"}
{"Question": "ICE + RICE = AREA", "Answer": "687 + 3687 = 4374"}
{"Question": "OIL + SOIL = ODDS", "Answer": "723 + 6723 = 7446"}
{"Question": "ONE + BONE = NEED", "Answer": "724 + 1724 = 2448"}
{"Question": "AGE + PAGE = CHEEK", "Answer": "724 + 9724 = 10448"}
{"Question": "EAT + BEAT = ORDER", "Answer": "735 + 9735 = 10470"}
{"Question": "EAT + BEAT = DRAMA", "Answer": "742 + 9742 = 10484"}
{"Question": "OWN + DOWN = FENCE", "Answer": "765 + 9765 = 10530"}
{"Question": "END + BEND = ORDER", "Answer": "785 + 9785 = 10570"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEAR = ARAB", "Answer": "795 + 8795 = 9590"}
{"Question": "EAT + HEAT = THAN", "Answer": "796 + 5796 = 6592"}
{"Question": "EAT + BEAT = CATCH", "Answer": "806 + 9806 = 10612"}
{"Question": "AGE + PAGE = GIVEN", "Answer": "812 + 9812 = 10624"}
{"Question": "END + TEND = DATA", "Answer": "813 + 2813 = 3626"}
{"Question": "ASK + MASK = SCENE", "Answer": "813 + 9813 = 10626"}
{"Question": "ACT + FACT = TOPIC", "Answer": "821 + 9821 = 10642"}
{"Question": "AIR + FAIR = EXTRA", "Answer": "824 + 9824 = 10648"}
{"Question": "ART + PART = STIR", "Answer": "826 + 3826 = 4652"}
{"Question": "ARM + FARM = ROOF", "Answer": "831 + 2831 = 3662"}
{"Question": "ACT + FACT = TROOP", "Answer": "831 + 9831 = 10662"}
{"Question": "LAY + PLAY = STEEL", "Answer": "834 + 9834 = 10668"}
{"Question": "ICE + NICE = BASIS", "Answer": "843 + 9843 = 10686"}
{"Question": "EAR + TEAR = BIRTH", "Answer": "846 + 9846 = 10692"}
{"Question": "LAY + PLAY = CIVIL", "Answer": "854 + 9854 = 10708"}
{"Question": "ICE + NICE = AHEAD", "Answer": "857 + 9857 = 10714"}
{"Question": "ART + PART = TREE", "Answer": "872 + 1872 = 2744"}
{"Question": "EAT + SEAT = MASS", "Answer": "872 + 4872 = 5744"}
{"Question": "AIR + FAIR = BILL", "Answer": "872 + 5872 = 6744"}
{"Question": "AIR + FAIR = SKILL", "Answer": "872 + 9872 = 10744"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEAR = RARE", "Answer": "874 + 3874 = 4748"}
{"Question": "EAR + BEAR = SHARE", "Answer": "874 + 9874 = 10748"}
{"Question": "EAR + NEAR = RANK", "Answer": "876 + 5876 = 6752"}
{"Question": "EAT + BEAT = TREE", "Answer": "894 + 3894 = 4788"}
{"Question": "AGE + PAGE = GEAR", "Answer": "948 + 3948 = 4896"}
{"Question": "AGE + PAGE = DEAD", "Answer": "948 + 5948 = 6896"}
{"Question": "ART + PART = TAPE", "Answer": "976 + 5976 = 6952"}
{"Question": "EAR + DEAL = APPLE", "Answer": "513 + 9512 = 10025"}
{"Question": "ERA + HERO = APPLE", "Answer": "531 + 9534 = 10065"}
{"Question": "AGO + PAGE = OFFER", "Answer": "531 + 9536 = 10067"}
{"Question": "ARM + CARE = INNER", "Answer": "536 + 9537 = 10073"}
{"Question": "END + MENU = ISSUE", "Answer": "538 + 9537 = 10075"}
{"Question": "TIP + STIR = ADAPT", "Answer": "562 + 9563 = 10125"}
{"Question": "TEA + STEP = ADAPT", "Answer": "571 + 9574 = 10145"}
{"Question": "ICE + RICH = HEEL", "Answer": "612 + 4615 = 5227"}
{"Question": "USE + DUST = SPEED", "Answer": "612 + 9617 = 10229"}
{"Question": "EAT + NEAR = EARN", "Answer": "621 + 5624 = 6245"}
{"Question": "ART + DARK = TIRED", "Answer": "621 + 9628 = 10249"}
{"Question": "TEA + STEP = PLATE", "Answer": "632 + 9631 = 10263"}
{"Question": "ACT + LACK = TRIAL", "Answer": "631 + 9638 = 10269"}
{"Question": "ACT + RACE = TOWER", "Answer": "641 + 9648 = 10289"}
{"Question": "ART + EARN = TENT", "Answer": "654 + 3650 = 4304"}
{"Question": "AIM + WAIT = METER", "Answer": "651 + 9653 = 10304"}
{"Question": "AIM + RAIL = METER", "Answer": "651 + 9658 = 10309"}
{"Question": "ARM + EARN = HONOR", "Answer": "652 + 9653 = 10305"}
{"Question": "HOW + SHOP = FEWER", "Answer": "653 + 9654 = 10307"}
{"Question": "AID + FAIR = EXTRA", "Answer": "672 + 9674 = 10346"}
{"Question": "SEA + USED = CHASE", "Answer": "683 + 9685 = 10368"}
{"Question": "SET + USER = EARTH", "Answer": "712 + 9714 = 10426"}
{"Question": "TAP + STAR = ADOPT", "Answer": "712 + 9715 = 10427"}
{"Question": "HEY + THEM = MYTH", "Answer": "714 + 2713 = 3427"}
{"Question": "RAW + DRAG = ANGER", "Answer": "713 + 9714 = 10427"}
{"Question": "AGO + PAGE = GHOST", "Answer": "714 + 9718 = 10432"}
{"Question": "ACT + PACE = TROOP", "Answer": "721 + 9728 = 10449"}
{"Question": "AGO + PAGE = TROOP", "Answer": "724 + 9725 = 10449"}
{"Question": "END + MENU = ORDER", "Answer": "734 + 9736 = 10470"}
{"Question": "ART + EARN = TEAR", "Answer": "735 + 4738 = 5473"}
{"Question": "ART + DARE = TIRED", "Answer": "741 + 9748 = 10489"}
{"Question": "ARM + CARE = AREA", "Answer": "748 + 6749 = 7497"}
{"Question": "ARM + EARN = MINOR", "Answer": "761 + 9765 = 10526"}
{"Question": "AIR + WAIT = EXTRA", "Answer": "762 + 9765 = 10527"}
{"Question": "OWE + TOWN = ONTO", "Answer": "782 + 6785 = 7567"}
{"Question": "AID + WAIT = EXTRA", "Answer": "782 + 9785 = 10567"}
{"Question": "AND + HANG = LEGAL", "Answer": "786 + 9785 = 10571"}
{"Question": "TEA + STEP = EASE", "Answer": "795 + 8794 = 9589"}
{"Question": "ITS + CITY = THESE", "Answer": "812 + 9814 = 10626"}
{"Question": "ART + EARN = ROUTE", "Answer": "812 + 9817 = 10629"}
{"Question": "ITS + BITE = TREAT", "Answer": "815 + 9816 = 10631"}
{"Question": "USE + BUSY = SHELL", "Answer": "816 + 9817 = 10633"}
{"Question": "OWE + BOWL = SALES", "Answer": "825 + 9826 = 10651"}
{"Question": "ITS + BITE = SHOOT", "Answer": "831 + 9832 = 10663"}
{"Question": "POT + UPON = ONTO", "Answer": "837 + 2836 = 3673"}
{"Question": "EAT + BEAR = TREE", "Answer": "842 + 1846 = 2688"}
{"Question": "AND + HANG = TIGHT", "Answer": "845 + 9846 = 10691"}
{"Question": "ACT + EACH = OFTEN", "Answer": "846 + 9847 = 10693"}
{"Question": "AID + RAIL = COLOR", "Answer": "852 + 9857 = 10709"}
{"Question": "ITS + BITE = AHEAD", "Answer": "856 + 9857 = 10713"}
{"Question": "ARM + CARD = MEDIA", "Answer": "861 + 9867 = 10728"}
{"Question": "EAT + HEAR = BIRTH", "Answer": "862 + 9867 = 10729"}
{"Question": "HIT + CHIP = ELITE", "Answer": "875 + 9876 = 10751"}
{"Question": "AND + PANT = TEEN", "Answer": "941 + 2943 = 3884"}
{"Question": "AID + TAIL = DATA", "Answer": "987 + 6982 = 7969"}
{"Question": "AID + WAIT = DATA", "Answer": "983 + 2986 = 3969"}
{"Question": "OWE + HOLE = ALLOW", "Answer": "547 + 9507 = 10054"}
{"Question": "LEG + FLAG = APPLE", "Answer": "542 + 9512 = 10054"}
{"Question": "NET + UNIT = ISSUE", "Answer": "584 + 9514 = 10098"}
{"Question": "ONE + VOTE = TEEN", "Answer": "521 + 8591 = 9112"}
{"Question": "TAP + STEP = LOOSE", "Answer": "528 + 9568 = 10096"}
{"Question": "ICE + LIFE = CELL", "Answer": "531 + 2591 = 3122"}
{"Question": "ICE + FINE = AGAIN", "Answer": "574 + 9584 = 10158"}
{"Question": "OUT + SOFT = FULLY", "Answer": "607 + 9617 = 10224"}
{"Question": "ACT + FAST = OCEAN", "Answer": "607 + 9657 = 10264"}
{"Question": "EAT + BELT = FALSE", "Answer": "608 + 9628 = 10236"}
{"Question": "EAT + BELT = WASTE", "Answer": "608 + 9678 = 10286"}
{"Question": "AGE + BAKE = GUESS", "Answer": "612 + 9632 = 10244"}
{"Question": "TAP + STOP = ADOPT", "Answer": "613 + 9623 = 10236"}
{"Question": "GAY + UGLY = AWFUL", "Answer": "614 + 9684 = 10298"}
{"Question": "OUT + BOAT = UNION", "Answer": "615 + 9645 = 10260"}
{"Question": "TOP + STEP = PHOTO", "Answer": "621 + 9641 = 10262"}
{"Question": "PET + SPOT = THESE", "Answer": "621 + 9671 = 10292"}
{"Question": "EAT + BEST = PLATE", "Answer": "628 + 9658 = 10286"}
{"Question": "KEY + OKAY = CHECK", "Answer": "638 + 9678 = 10316"}
{"Question": "ART + EAST = VOTER", "Answer": "642 + 9652 = 10294"}
{"Question": "USE + RULE = LESS", "Answer": "705 + 8795 = 9500"}
{"Question": "ART + FACT = CROSS", "Answer": "706 + 9716 = 10422"}
{"Question": "ARM + PALM = CRIME", "Answer": "706 + 9756 = 10462"}
{"Question": "ACT + PANT = OCEAN", "Answer": "708 + 9768 = 10476"}
{"Question": "ONE + MODE = DRAMA", "Answer": "782 + 9712 = 10494"}
{"Question": "ACT + EAST = CHIEF", "Answer": "713 + 9783 = 10496"}
{"Question": "ICE + SITE = CHEST", "Answer": "714 + 9784 = 10498"}
{"Question": "AGE + HAVE = GIVEN", "Answer": "716 + 9746 = 10462"}
{"Question": "ICE + FIRE = COVER", "Answer": "718 + 9768 = 10486"}
{"Question": "LEG + FLAG = GRADE", "Answer": "721 + 9741 = 10462"}
{"Question": "END + HEAD = DOZEN", "Answer": "721 + 9751 = 10472"}
{"Question": "ARM + PALM = SOLAR", "Answer": "726 + 9746 = 10472"}
{"Question": "ACT + WAIT = TRIAL", "Answer": "731 + 9741 = 10472"}
{"Question": "NEW + SNOW = THESE", "Answer": "742 + 9752 = 10494"}
{"Question": "AND + CARD = UNDER", "Answer": "806 + 9826 = 10632"}
{"Question": "LAP + SLIP = HAPPY", "Answer": "806 + 9856 = 10662"}
{"Question": "EAT + BELT = WATER", "Answer": "806 + 9876 = 10682"}
{"Question": "HOT + SHUT = ROUTE", "Answer": "807 + 9867 = 10674"}
{"Question": "ACT + PART = COVER", "Answer": "812 + 9842 = 10654"}
{"Question": "ITS + AIDS = THESE", "Answer": "813 + 9823 = 10636"}
{"Question": "TAP + STEP = ADOPT", "Answer": "814 + 9834 = 10648"}
{"Question": "OIL + SOUL = UNION", "Answer": "865 + 9815 = 10680"}
{"Question": "ARM + PALM = RELAX", "Answer": "817 + 9867 = 10684"}
{"Question": "NET + UNIT = NINE", "Answer": "821 + 7861 = 8682"}
{"Question": "ITS + AIDS = SHEET", "Answer": "821 + 9841 = 10662"}
{"Question": "ARM + PALM = MORAL", "Answer": "861 + 9821 = 10682"}
{"Question": "ART + EAST = TOWER", "Answer": "821 + 9871 = 10692"}
{"Question": "OIL + COAL = PEACE", "Answer": "825 + 9865 = 10690"}
{"Question": "ONE + CODE = GREEN", "Answer": "826 + 9836 = 10662"}
{"Question": "ACT + SALT = METAL", "Answer": "856 + 9826 = 10682"}
{"Question": "ARM + PALM = COLOR", "Answer": "826 + 9876 = 10702"}
{"Question": "END + HEAD = STATE", "Answer": "834 + 9874 = 10708"}
{"Question": "ACT + PANT = HUMAN", "Answer": "837 + 9847 = 10684"}
{"Question": "ART + CAST = METER", "Answer": "847 + 9857 = 10704"}
{"Question": "ART + CAST = ENTER", "Answer": "847 + 9867 = 10714"}
{"Question": "ACT + PART = THREE", "Answer": "851 + 9871 = 10722"}
{"Question": "ONE + LOVE = EVEN", "Answer": "863 + 2873 = 3736"}
{"Question": "RID + TRUE = INNER", "Answer": "517 + 9568 = 10085"}
{"Question": "LET + ALSO = TITLE", "Answer": "571 + 9586 = 10157"}
{"Question": "AID + CAST = ELITE", "Answer": "623 + 9658 = 10281"}
{"Question": "EAR + NEWS = STATE", "Answer": "635 + 9671 = 10306"}
{"Question": "ETC + RELY = COLOR", "Answer": "671 + 9638 = 10309"}
{"Question": "DOG + IDEA = AHEAD", "Answer": "685 + 9631 = 10316"}
{"Question": "LET + PLUS = TASTE", "Answer": "641 + 9673 = 10314"}
{"Question": "ARM + FADE = DRESS", "Answer": "708 + 9714 = 10422"}
{"Question": "EAT + BEND = LATER", "Answer": "704 + 9768 = 10472"}
{"Question": "RUN + CREW = FENCE", "Answer": "784 + 9706 = 10490"}
{"Question": "ETC + HEAD = TRADE", "Answer": "712 + 9745 = 10457"}
{"Question": "AGE + BAND = GREEN", "Answer": "714 + 9728 = 10442"}
{"Question": "AGE + BACK = GREAT", "Answer": "714 + 9758 = 10472"}
{"Question": "ARM + HALF = REFER", "Answer": "716 + 9785 = 10501"}
{"Question": "AID + GAME = DREAM", "Answer": "721 + 9754 = 10475"}
{"Question": "AIM + PART = METER", "Answer": "741 + 9765 = 10506"}
{"Question": "ETC + HELP = CATCH", "Answer": "751 + 9768 = 10519"}
{"Question": "EAT + BEND = TRACE", "Answer": "751 + 9786 = 10537"}
{"Question": "ARM + BAKE = ORDER", "Answer": "807 + 9823 = 10630"}
{"Question": "ITS + FIRE = TREAT", "Answer": "815 + 9806 = 10621"}
{"Question": "ONE + COAL = SALES", "Answer": "845 + 9806 = 10651"}
{"Question": "ARM + BAKE = TREAT", "Answer": "805 + 9876 = 10681"}
{"Question": "AIR + FADE = DIRTY", "Answer": "806 + 9817 = 10623"}
{"Question": "ERA + BELT = GRASS", "Answer": "806 + 9827 = 10633"}
{"Question": "AND + HATE = THEN", "Answer": "812 + 6879 = 7691"}
{"Question": "LIE + ALSO = STEEL", "Answer": "856 + 9812 = 10668"}
{"Question": "ASK + GAIN = SWING", "Answer": "812 + 9867 = 10679"}
{"Question": "OUT + ROLE = LATER", "Answer": "826 + 9813 = 10639"}
{"Question": "OLD + SONG = LEGAL", "Answer": "815 + 9826 = 10641"}
{"Question": "OIL + NOSE = SALES", "Answer": "836 + 9815 = 10651"}
{"Question": "ITS + AIDE = TREAT", "Answer": "815 + 9876 = 10691"}
{"Question": "SIT + USED = THESE", "Answer": "821 + 9865 = 10686"}
{"Question": "AGO + EARN = OWNER", "Answer": "821 + 9876 = 10697"}
{"Question": "ETC + READ = CHART", "Answer": "831 + 9862 = 10693"}
{"Question": "ARM + PATH = METER", "Answer": "831 + 9872 = 10703"}
{"Question": "LEG + BLOW = ANGLE", "Answer": "836 + 9847 = 10683"}
{"Question": "AGE + HUGE = ASSET", "Answer": "162 + 9862 = 10024"}
{"Question": "LET + DIET = LOOSE", "Answer": "163 + 9863 = 10026"}
{"Question": "AIM + SWIM = ALLOW", "Answer": "164 + 9864 = 10028"}
{"Question": "EAT + FLAT = ERROR", "Answer": "165 + 9865 = 10030"}
{"Question": "EAT + FLAT = APPLE", "Answer": "814 + 9214 = 10028"}
{"Question": "EAR + STAR = LOOSE", "Answer": "246 + 9846 = 10092"}
{"Question": "EAR + STAR = TREE", "Answer": "261 + 7861 = 8122"}
{"Question": "DRY + VERY = DEER", "Answer": "963 + 8263 = 9226"}
{"Question": "TEA + IDEA = APART", "Answer": "271 + 9871 = 10142"}
{"Question": "AND + TEND = DATA", "Answer": "276 + 5976 = 6252"}
{"Question": "AND + BOND = ERROR", "Answer": "285 + 9785 = 10070"}
{"Question": "BET + POET = ERROR", "Answer": "715 + 9315 = 10030"}
{"Question": "BAR + YEAR = BABY", "Answer": "316 + 2816 = 3132"}
{"Question": "SEA + IDEA = AIDE", "Answer": "342 + 1842 = 2184"}
{"Question": "DUE + TRUE = UPPER", "Answer": "612 + 9412 = 10024"}
{"Question": "TAP + SNAP = ADAPT", "Answer": "412 + 9712 = 10124"}
{"Question": "TEA + IDEA = DATE", "Answer": "421 + 6721 = 7142"}
{"Question": "LET + POET = TITLE", "Answer": "421 + 9721 = 10142"}
{"Question": "MAD + GLAD = DRAMA", "Answer": "421 + 9821 = 10242"}
{"Question": "EAR + STAR = RARE", "Answer": "437 + 6937 = 7374"}
{"Question": "ROW + BLOW = FEWER", "Answer": "452 + 9752 = 10204"}
{"Question": "HER + USER = RUSH", "Answer": "482 + 1682 = 2164"}
{"Question": "BAD + READ = DARE", "Answer": "513 + 2613 = 3126"}
{"Question": "SAD + LOAD = ALSO", "Answer": "528 + 1628 = 2156"}
{"Question": "BAD + READ = AREA", "Answer": "542 + 3842 = 4384"}
{"Question": "FLY + RELY = AWARE", "Answer": "548 + 9648 = 10196"}
{"Question": "AGE + URGE = SOLAR", "Answer": "578 + 9678 = 10256"}
{"Question": "COW + GROW = WHERE", "Answer": "581 + 9681 = 10262"}
{"Question": "AGE + URGE = GEAR", "Answer": "634 + 2834 = 3468"}
{"Question": "AGE + URGE = CLEAR", "Answer": "634 + 9834 = 10468"}
{"Question": "SIN + JOIN = PRIOR", "Answer": "635 + 9735 = 10370"}
{"Question": "DAY + GRAY = YARD", "Answer": "643 + 2843 = 3486"}
{"Question": "ASK + RISK = EXTRA", "Answer": "648 + 9748 = 10396"}
{"Question": "SEA + IDEA = CHASE", "Answer": "684 + 9784 = 10468"}
{"Question": "CAN + LOAN = FENCE", "Answer": "735 + 9835 = 10570"}
{"Question": "BAR + DEAR = AREA", "Answer": "847 + 3947 = 4794"}
{"Question": "ETC + AUTO = ERROR", "Answer": "167 + 9863 = 10030"}
{"Question": "AGO + URGE = OFFER", "Answer": "281 + 9786 = 10067"}
{"Question": "DIE + TRIP = INNER", "Answer": "312 + 9715 = 10027"}
{"Question": "AGO + URGE = FLOOR", "Answer": "462 + 9765 = 10227"}
{"Question": "EAR + BOAT = THREE", "Answer": "473 + 9871 = 10344"}
{"Question": "ACT + NICE = BREAD", "Answer": "472 + 9873 = 10345"}
{"Question": "EAT + GLAD = TRADE", "Answer": "521 + 9724 = 10245"}
{"Question": "ARM + BORN = MINOR", "Answer": "541 + 9843 = 10384"}
{"Question": "CAR + THAN = REACT", "Answer": "631 + 9738 = 10369"}
{"Question": "GAS + BEAN = STATE", "Answer": "651 + 9857 = 10508"}
{"Question": "CEO + DIET = KNOCK", "Answer": "735 + 9836 = 10571"}
{"Question": "AGE + BITE = ASSET", "Answer": "173 + 9863 = 10036"}
{"Question": "ARM + POEM = ERROR", "Answer": "805 + 9215 = 10020"}
{"Question": "END + ACID = INNER", "Answer": "207 + 9817 = 10024"}
{"Question": "ASK + BUCK = ESSAY", "Answer": "308 + 9728 = 10036"}
{"Question": "AGO + HERO = OFFER", "Answer": "351 + 9721 = 10072"}
{"Question": "EAT + SHOT = LOOSE", "Answer": "487 + 9607 = 10094"}
{"Question": "THE + BASE = SHOOT", "Answer": "407 + 9817 = 10224"}
{"Question": "DIE + ABLE = TIRED", "Answer": "407 + 9867 = 10274"}
{"Question": "EAT + DIRT = AGREE", "Answer": "417 + 9827 = 10244"}
{"Question": "OWN + BEAN = AWARE", "Answer": "508 + 9618 = 10126"}
{"Question": "TIE + SHOE = FIFTH", "Answer": "508 + 9648 = 10156"}
{"Question": "OIL + DEAL = BIBLE", "Answer": "508 + 9678 = 10186"}
{"Question": "AGE + BITE = GREAT", "Answer": "512 + 9742 = 10254"}
{"Question": "CAP + STEP = ADAPT", "Answer": "513 + 9623 = 10136"}
{"Question": "AGO + INTO = GREEN", "Answer": "514 + 9824 = 10338"}
{"Question": "CAP + STOP = ADOPT", "Answer": "514 + 9834 = 10348"}
{"Question": "CAT + DEBT = BASIC", "Answer": "608 + 9718 = 10326"}
{"Question": "THE + ABLE = SHOOT", "Answer": "608 + 9728 = 10336"}
{"Question": "HER + TOUR = EARTH", "Answer": "613 + 9783 = 10396"}
{"Question": "EAR + FOUR = SHARE", "Answer": "638 + 9748 = 10386"}
{"Question": "CAN + OPEN = FENCE", "Answer": "765 + 9805 = 10570"}
{"Question": "GOD + BEND = ORDER", "Answer": "715 + 9865 = 10580"}
{"Question": "BET + UNIT = ASIAN", "Answer": "754 + 9864 = 10618"}
